<root><OPHeading1>Business Today: Chamber</OPHeading1>
<DebateTimingRubric>11.30am Prayers</DebateTimingRubric>
<DebateTimingRubric>Followed by</DebateTimingRubric>
<OPHeading2>Questions</OPHeading2>
<QUESTIONS/>
<OPHeading2>Urgent Questions and Statements</OPHeading2>
<DebateTimingRubric>12.30pm</DebateTimingRubric>
<DebateTimingRubric>Urgent Questions (if any)</DebateTimingRubric>
<DebateTimingRubric>Ministerial Statements (if any)</DebateTimingRubric>
<OPHeading2>Presentation of Bills</OPHeading2>
<DebateTimingRubric>No debate <SOReference>(Standing Order No. 57)</SOReference></DebateTimingRubric>
<Heading3Underlined>Post Office (Horizon System) Offences</Heading3Underlined>
<MotionSponsor>Kemi Badenoch</MotionSponsor>
<MotionText><from_cdata><p class="MsoNormal" style="text-align: justify;"><span class="MotionTextChar">Bill to provide for the quashing of convictions in England and Wales for certain offences alleged to have been committed while the Horizon system was in use by the Post Office; to make provision about the deletion of cautions given in England and Wales for such offences; and for connected purposes. </span><span class="MotionTextChar"><span style="mso-fareast-font-family: Calibri; mso-fareast-theme-font: minor-latin;"/></span></p></from_cdata></MotionText>
<OPHeading2>Business of the Day</OPHeading2>
<BusinessItemHeadingNumbered>Sites of special scientific interest (designation): Ten Minute Rule Motion</BusinessItemHeadingNumbered>
<DebateTimingRubric>Up to 20 minutes<SOReference> (Standing Order No. 23)</SOReference></DebateTimingRubric>
<MotionSponsor>Derek Thomas</MotionSponsor>
<MotionText><from_cdata>That leave be given to bring in a Bill <span style="font-family: Calibri, sans-serif; font-size: 11pt;">to transfer the power to designate sites of special scientific interest</span><span style="font-family: Calibri, sans-serif; font-size: 11pt;"> from Natural England to the Secretary of State; to make provision about the exercise of that power by the Secretary of State; and for connected purposes.</span></from_cdata></MotionText>
<NoteHeading>Notes:</NoteHeading>
<NoteText><from_cdata><p>The Member moving and a Member opposing this Motion may each speak for up to 10 minutes.</p></from_cdata></NoteText>
<Line_Interstitial> </Line_Interstitial>
<BusinessItemHeadingNumbered>NATIONAL INSURANCE CONTRIBUTIONS (REDUCTION IN RATES) (NO. 2) BILL: ALLOCATION OF TIME</BusinessItemHeadingNumbered>
<DebateTimingRubric>Up to three hours<SOReference> (Standing Order No. 83)</SOReference></DebateTimingRubric>
<MotionSponsor>Jeremy Hunt</MotionSponsor>
<MotionText><from_cdata>That the following provisions shall apply to the proceedings on the National Insurance Contributions (Reduction in Rates) (No. 2) Bill:
Timetable
(1) (a) Proceedings on Second Reading and in Committee of the whole House, any proceedings on Consideration and proceedings on Third Reading shall be taken at today&#8217;s sitting in accordance with this Order.
(b) Proceedings on Second Reading shall (so far as not previously concluded) be brought to a conclusion three hours after the commencement of proceedings on the Motion for this Order.
(c) Proceedings in Committee of the whole House, any proceedings on Consideration and proceedings on Third Reading shall (so far as not previously concluded) be brought to a conclusion four hours after the commencement of proceedings on the Motion for this Order.
Timing of proceedings and Questions to be put
(2) When the Bill has been read a second time:
(a) it shall, despite Standing Order No. 63 (Committal of bills not subject to a programme order), stand committed to a Committee of the whole House without any Question being put;
(b) proceedings on the Bill shall stand postponed while the Question is put, in accordance with Standing Order No. 52(1) (Money resolutions and ways and means resolutions in connection with bills), on any financial resolution relating to the Bill;
(c) on the conclusion of proceedings on any financial resolution relating to the Bill, proceedings on the Bill shall be resumed and the Speaker shall leave the Chair whether or not notice of an Instruction has been given.
(3) (a) On the conclusion of proceedings in Committee of the whole House, the Chair shall report the Bill to the House without putting any Question.
(b) If the Bill is reported with amendments, the House shall proceed to consider the Bill as amended without any Question being put.
(4) For the purpose of bringing any proceedings to a conclusion in accordance with paragraph (1), the Chair or Speaker shall forthwith put the following Questions in the same order as they would fall to be put if this Order did not apply:
(a) any Question already proposed from the chair;
(b) any Question necessary to bring to a decision a Question so proposed;
(c) the Question on any amendment, new Clause or new Schedule selected by the Chair or Speaker for separate decision;
(d) the Question on any amendment moved or Motion made by a Minister of the Crown;
(e) any other Question necessary for the disposal of the business to be concluded;
and shall not put any other questions, other than the question on any motion described in paragraph (15)(a) of this Order.
(5) On a Motion so made for a new Clause or a new Schedule, the Chair or Speaker shall put only the Question that the Clause or Schedule be added to the Bill.
(6) If two or more Questions would fall to be put under paragraph (4)(d) on successive amendments moved or Motions made by a Minister of the Crown, the Chair or Speaker shall instead put a single Question in relation to those amendments or Motions.
(7) If two or more Questions would fall to be put under paragraph (4)(e) in relation to successive provisions of the Bill, the Chair shall instead put a single Question in relation to those provisions, except that the Question shall be put separately on any Clause of or Schedule to the Bill which a Minister of the Crown has signified an intention to leave out.
Consideration of Lords Amendments
(8) (a) Any Lords Amendments to the Bill may be considered forthwith without any Question being put; and any proceedings interrupted for that purpose shall be suspended accordingly.
(b) Proceedings on consideration of Lords Amendments shall (so far as not previously concluded) be brought to a conclusion one hour after their commencement; and any proceedings suspended under sub-paragraph (a) shall thereupon be resumed.
(9) Paragraphs (2) to (7) of Standing Order No. 83F (Programme orders: conclusion of proceedings on consideration of Lords amendments) apply for the purposes of bringing any proceedings to a conclusion in accordance with paragraph (8) of this Order.
Subsequent stages
(10) (a) Any further Message from the Lords on the Bill may be considered forthwith without any Question being put; and any proceedings interrupted for that purpose shall be suspended accordingly.
(b) Proceedings on any further Message from the Lords shall (so far as not previously concluded) be brought to a conclusion one hour after their commencement; and any proceedings suspended under sub-paragraph (a) shall thereupon be resumed.
(11)  Paragraphs (2) to (5) of Standing Order No. 83G (Programme orders: conclusion of proceedings on further messages from the Lords) apply for the purposes of bringing any proceedings to a conclusion in accordance with paragraph (10) of this Order.
Reasons Committee
(12) Paragraphs (2) to (6) of Standing Order No. 83H (Programme orders: reasons committee) apply in relation to any committee to be appointed to draw up reasons after proceedings have been brought to a conclusion in accordance with this Order. 
Miscellaneous
(13) Standing Order No. 15(1) (Exempted business) shall apply to proceedings on the Bill.
(14) Standing Order No. 82 (Business Committee) shall not apply in relation to any proceedings to which this Order applies.
(15) (a) No Motion shall be made, except by a Minister of the Crown, to alter the order in which any proceedings on the Bill are taken, to recommit the Bill or to vary or supplement the provisions of this Order.
(b) No notice shall be required of such a Motion.
(c) Such a Motion may be considered forthwith without any Question being put; and any proceedings interrupted for that purpose shall be suspended accordingly.
(d) The Question on such a Motion shall be put forthwith; and any proceedings suspended under sub-paragraph (c) shall thereupon be resumed.
(e) Standing Order No. 15(1) (Exempted business) shall apply to proceedings on such a Motion.
(16) (a) No dilatory Motion shall be made in relation to proceedings to which this Order applies except by a Minister of the Crown.
(b) The Question on any such Motion shall be put forthwith.
(17) (a) The start of any debate under Standing Order No. 24 (Emergency debates) to be held on a day on which the Bill has been set down to be taken as an Order of the Day shall be postponed until the conclusion of any proceedings on that day to which this Order applies.
(b) Standing Order No. 15(1) (Exempted business) shall apply in respect of any such debate.
(18) Proceedings to which this Order applies shall not be interrupted under any Standing Order relating to the sittings of the House.
(19) (a) Any private business which has been set down for consideration at a time falling after the commencement of proceedings on this Order or on the Bill on a day on which the Bill has been set down to be taken as an Order of the Day shall, instead of being considered as provided by Standing Orders or by any Order of the House, be considered at the conclusion of the proceedings on the Bill on that day.
(b) Standing Order No. 15(1) (Exempted business) shall apply to the private business so far as necessary for the purpose of securing that the business may be considered for a period of three hours.</from_cdata></MotionText>
<OPHeading2>Business to be Taken at 7.00pm</OPHeading2>
<DebateTimingRubric>BUSINESS OF THE HOUSE</DebateTimingRubric>
<DebateTimingRubric>No debate.<SOReference> (Standing Order No. 15(1))</SOReference></DebateTimingRubric>
<MotionSponsor>Rishi Sunak</MotionSponsor>
<MotionText><from_cdata><span style="font-size: 12pt; font-family: Lora, serif; background-color: transparent; font-variant-numeric: normal; font-variant-east-asian: normal; font-variant-alternates: normal; font-variant-position: normal; vertical-align: baseline; white-space-collapse: preserve;">That, at this day&#8217;s sitting, proceedings on the motion in the name of the Chancellor of the Exchequer relating to the National Insurance Contributions (Reduction in Rates) (No. 2) Bill: Allocation of Time may be entered upon and proceeded with, though opposed, at any hour.</span></from_cdata></MotionText>
<OPHeading2>Business of the Day</OPHeading2>
<BusinessItemHeadingNumbered>NATIONAL INSURANCE CONTRIBUTIONS (REDUCTION IN RATES) (NO. 2) BILL: Second Reading</BusinessItemHeadingNumbered>
<DebateTimingRubric>Up to three hours after the start of proceedings on the National Insurance Contributions (Reduction in Rates) (No. 2) Bill: Allocation of Time motion (if that motion is agreed to)</DebateTimingRubric>
<Line_Interstitial> </Line_Interstitial>
<BusinessItemHeadingNumbered>No title </BusinessItemHeadingNumbered>
<MotionSponsor>Caroline Lucas</MotionSponsor>
<MotionText><from_cdata><p class="xmsonormal" style="margin: 0cm 0cm 8.0pt 0cm;"><span style="font-size: 14.0pt; color: black;">That this House, while supporting the Government&#8217;s stated aim of making the tax system fairer, declines to give the National Insurance Contributions (Reduction in Rates) (No. 2) Bill a Second Reading because it is highly regressive, the proposed reductions to National Insurance contributions being worth less than &#163;50 a year for a person earning &#163;15,000 from employment compared to around &#163;750 a year for someone earning over &#163;50,000, worsening existing inequalities at a time when lower-income households are struggling with the cost of living, and because the majority of people in the UK believe that the Government should prioritise funding public services over cutting taxes.</span></p></from_cdata></MotionText>
<Line_Interstitial> </Line_Interstitial>
<BusinessItemHeadingNumbered>No title </BusinessItemHeadingNumbered>
<MotionSponsor>Drew Hendry</MotionSponsor>
<MotionSponsor>Stephen Flynn</MotionSponsor>
<MotionSponsor>Kirsty Blackman</MotionSponsor>
<MotionSponsor>Steven Bonnar</MotionSponsor>
<MotionSponsor>Chris Stephens</MotionSponsor>
<MotionSponsor>Owen Thompson</MotionSponsor>
<MotionSponsorGroup>Pete Wishart	Stewart Hosie	Ian Blackford	Hannah Bardell	Mhairi Black	Deidre Brock	Alan Brown	Amy Callaghan	Douglas Chapman	Joanna Cherry	Ronnie Cowan	Angela Crawley	Martyn Day	Martin Docherty-Hughes	Dave Doogan	Allan Dorans	Marion Fellows	Patricia Gibson	Patrick Grady	Peter Grant	Chris Law	David Linden	Stewart Malcolm McDonald	Stuart C McDonald	Anne McLaughlin	John McNally	Carol Monaghan	Gavin Newlands	John Nicolson	Brendan O&#8217;Hara	Kirsten Oswald	Ms Anum Qaisar	Tommy Sheppard	Alyn Smith	Alison Thewliss	Richard Thomson	Dr Philippa Whitford	</MotionSponsorGroup>&#8233;
<MotionText><from_cdata><p class="xxmsonormal" style="margin: 0cm;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt; font-family: 'Calibri',sans-serif; color: #212121;">That this House </span><span style="font-size: 11.0pt; font-family: 'Calibri',sans-serif;">declines to give a Second Reading to the National Insurance Contributions (Reduction in Rates) (No. 2) Bill because, while acknowledging that the measures in the Bill reduce the National Insurance Contributions (NIC) burden on some employees, it considers the Government should prioritise investment in public services spending over yet more cuts in spending which would be the result of lowering tax revenue by reducing NIC rates.</span></p></from_cdata></MotionText>
<Line_Interstitial> </Line_Interstitial>
<BusinessItemHeadingNumbered>NATIONAL INSURANCE CONTRIBUTIONS (REDUCTION IN RATES) (NO. 2) BILL: MONEY</BusinessItemHeadingNumbered>
<DebateTimingRubric>No debate<SOReference> (Standing Order No. 52(1)(a))</SOReference></DebateTimingRubric>
<MotionSponsor>Nigel Huddleston</MotionSponsor>
<MotionText><from_cdata>That, for the purposes of any Act resulting from the National Insurance Contributions (Reduction in Rates) (No. 2) Bill, it is expedient to authorise the payment out of money provided by Parliament of any increase in the sums payable under any other Act out of money so provided that is attributable to:
a)<span style="white-space: pre;"> </span>reducing the main primary percentage for Class 1 primary national insurance contributions to 8% (and reducing the percentage specified in regulation 131 of the Social Security Contributions Regulations 2001 to 1.85%), and
b)<span style="white-space: pre;"> </span>reducing the main Class 4 percentage for Class 4 national insurance contributions to 6%.</from_cdata></MotionText>
<NoteHeading>Notes:</NoteHeading>
<NoteText><from_cdata><p><span class="Italic"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt; line-height: 107%; font-family: 'Calibri',sans-serif; mso-fareast-font-family: 'Times New Roman'; mso-bidi-font-family: 'Times New Roman'; mso-ansi-language: EN-GB; mso-fareast-language: EN-GB; mso-bidi-language: AR-SA;">King&#8217;s Recommendation signified.</span></span></p></from_cdata></NoteText>
<Line_Interstitial> </Line_Interstitial>
<BusinessItemHeadingNumbered>NATIONAL INSURANCE CONTRIBUTIONS (REDUCTION IN RATES) (NO. 2) BILL: COMMITTEE AND REMAINING STAGES</BusinessItemHeadingNumbered>
<DebateTimingRubric>Up to four hours after the start of proceedings on the National Insurance Contributions (Reduction in Rates) (No. 2) Bill: Allocation of Time motion (if that motion is agreed to)</DebateTimingRubric>
<NoteHeading>Notes:</NoteHeading>
<NoteText><from_cdata><p class="MsoNormal"><span style="font-family: National; color: #4d4d4d; background: white;">For New Clauses relating to Committee of the whole House, see </span><span style="font-family: National; color: black; mso-color-alt: windowtext; background: white;">separate pape</span><span style="font-family: National; color: #4d4d4d; background: white;">r (also available on the publications webpage for the Bill).</span></p></from_cdata></NoteText>
<Line_Interstitial> </Line_Interstitial>
<BusinessItemHeadingNumbered>Local Government</BusinessItemHeadingNumbered>
<DebateTimingRubric>No debate<SOReference> (Standing Order No. 118(6))</SOReference></DebateTimingRubric>
<MotionSponsor>Jacob Young</MotionSponsor>
<NoteHeading>Notes:</NoteHeading>
<NoteText><from_cdata><p><span style="color: #4d4d4d; font-family: National, Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif; font-size: 16px;">If this item is opposed after 7.00pm, the division will be deferred.</span></p></from_cdata></NoteText>
<Line_Interstitial> </Line_Interstitial>
<BusinessItemHeadingNumbered>Trade Unions</BusinessItemHeadingNumbered>
<DebateTimingRubric>No debate<SOReference> (Standing Order No. 118(6))</SOReference></DebateTimingRubric>
<MotionSponsor>James Cleverly</MotionSponsor>
<MotionText><from_cdata>That the draft Strikes (Minimum Service Levels: Fire and Rescue Services) (England) Regulations 2024, which were laid before this House on 8 February, be approved.</from_cdata></MotionText>
<NoteHeading>Notes:</NoteHeading>
<NoteText><from_cdata><p><strong/><span style="color: #4d4d4d; font-family: National, Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif; font-size: 16px;">If this item is opposed after 7.00pm, the division will be deferred.</span></p></from_cdata></NoteText>
<Line_Interstitial> </Line_Interstitial>
<BusinessItemHeadingNumbered>Sea Fisheries</BusinessItemHeadingNumbered>
<DebateTimingRubric>No debate<SOReference> (Standing Order No. 118(6))</SOReference></DebateTimingRubric>
<MotionSponsor>Steve Barclay</MotionSponsor>
<MotionText><from_cdata>That the draft Sea Fisheries (International Commission for the Conservation of Atlantic Tunas) (Amendment) Regulations 2024,<span style="color: #333333; font-family: Arial, Verdana, sans-serif; font-size: 14px;"> </span>which were laid before this House on 12 December 2023, be approved.</from_cdata></MotionText>
<NoteHeading>Notes:</NoteHeading>
<NoteText><from_cdata><p><span style="color: #4d4d4d; font-family: National, Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif; font-size: 16px;">If this item is opposed after 7.00pm, the division will be deferred.</span></p></from_cdata></NoteText>
<OPHeading2>Presentation of Public Petitions</OPHeading2>
<DebateTimingRubric>No debate or decision <SOReference>(Standing Order No. 153)</SOReference></DebateTimingRubric>
<MotionText>Immigration health surcharge : <PresenterSponsor>Martyn Day [R]</PresenterSponsor></MotionText>
<OPHeading2>Adjournment Debate</OPHeading2>
<DebateTimingRubric>Until 7.30pm or for half an hour (whichever is later)<SOReference> (Standing Order No. 9(7))</SOReference></DebateTimingRubric>
<MotionText>Review into the presumption of parental involvement in child arrangements: <PresenterSponsor>Kate Kniveton</PresenterSponsor></MotionText>
<OPHeading1>Business Today: Westminster Hall</OPHeading1>
<OPHeading2>Order of Business</OPHeading2>
<DebateTimingRubric>The first part of the sitting will last for two hours. The second part of the sitting will last for three hours (Standing Order No. 10(1)).</DebateTimingRubric>
<DebateTimingRubric>9.30am</DebateTimingRubric>
<MotionText>That this House has considered reform of the planning system: <PresenterSponsor>Sir Simon Clarke</PresenterSponsor></MotionText>
<DebateTimingRubric>11.00am</DebateTimingRubric>
<MotionText>That this House has considered the duty solicitor scheme: <PresenterSponsor>Kevin Foster</PresenterSponsor></MotionText>
<NoteHeading>Notes:</NoteHeading>
<NoteText><from_cdata><p>The sitting will be suspended from 11.30am to 2.30pm.</p></from_cdata></NoteText>
<DebateTimingRubric>2.30pm</DebateTimingRubric>
<MotionText>That this House has considered gambling advertising in sport: <PresenterSponsor>Ronnie Cowan</PresenterSponsor></MotionText>
<DebateTimingRubric>4.00pm</DebateTimingRubric>
<MotionText>That this House has considered the impact of 5G mast installations on communities in Greater Manchester: <PresenterSponsor>Jim McMahon</PresenterSponsor></MotionText>
<DebateTimingRubric>4.30pm</DebateTimingRubric>
<MotionText>That this House has considered children&#8217;s cancer care in the South East: <PresenterSponsor>Munira Wilson</PresenterSponsor></MotionText>
<NoteHeading>Notes:</NoteHeading>
<NoteText><from_cdata><p><span style="color: #333333; font-family: 'helvetica neue', Helvetica, Arial, sans-serif; font-size: 14px;">The debate at 4.30pm will last for up to an hour.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #333333; font-family: 'helvetica neue', Helvetica, Arial, sans-serif; font-size: 14px;">The sitting will be suspended and time added if divisions take place in the main Chamber (Standing Order No. 10(3)).</span></p></from_cdata></NoteText>
<OPHeading1>Written Statements</OPHeading1>
<OPHeading2>Statements to be Made Today</OPHeading2>
<MotionCrossHeading>The Chancellor of the Exchequer</MotionCrossHeading>
<MinisterialStatement>Post Office redress</MinisterialStatement>
<NoteHeading>Notes:</NoteHeading>
<NoteText>Texts of Written Statements are available from the Vote Office and on the internet at https://questions-statements.parliament.uk/ .</NoteText></root>