<root><OPHeading1>Announcements</OPHeading1>
<OPHeading2>Forthcoming End of Day Adjournment Debates</OPHeading2>
<MotionText><from_cdata>Applications for 30-minute end of day adjournment debates should be made to the Table Office by 7.00pm or rise of the House, whichever is the earlier, on the Wednesdays listed below. Members can submit their application via MemberHub, from their own email account or in hard copy. Application forms are available on the Table Office page on ParliNet. The ballot takes place the day after the deadline. Members who are successful will be contacted by the Speaker&#8217;s Office.
<strong/></from_cdata></MotionText>
<DebateTimingRubric>Tuesday 30 April to Thursday 2 May (deadline Wednesday 24 April 7.00pm or the rise of the House, whichever is earlier)</DebateTimingRubric>
<DebateTimingRubric>Tuesday 7 to Monday 13 May (deadline Wednesday 1 May 7.00pm or the rise of the House, whichever is earlier)</DebateTimingRubric>
<DebateTimingRubric>Tuesday 14 to Monday 20 May (deadline Wednesday 8 May 7.00pm or the rise of the House, whichever is earlier)</DebateTimingRubric>
<OPHeading2>Forthcoming Westminster Hall Debates</OPHeading2>
<MotionText><from_cdata>The rota for answering Departments is listed below. Applications for 90, 60 and 30-minute debates should be made to the Table Office by 10.00pm or the rise of the House, whichever is the earlier, on the Mondays listed below. Members can submit their application via MemberHub, from their own email account or in hard copy. Application forms are available on the Table Office page on ParliNet. The ballot takes place the day after the deadline. Members who are successful will be contacted by the Speaker&#8217;s Office.</from_cdata></MotionText>
<DebateTimingRubric>Tuesday 30 April and Wednesday 1 May (ballot closed)</DebateTimingRubric>
<MotionText><from_cdata><p class="paraMotionText" style="box-sizing: border-box; margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 18px; color: #4d4d4d; font-family: National, Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif; font-size: 18px;">The ballot for Tuesday 30 April and Wednesday 1 May will take place today. The deadline for making an application to this ballot has now passed.</p></from_cdata></MotionText>
<DebateTimingRubric>Tuesday 7 and Wednesday 8 May (deadline Monday 29 April 10.00pm or the rise of the House, whichever is earlier)</DebateTimingRubric>
<MotionText><from_cdata><span style="color: #333333; font-family: 'helvetica neue', Helvetica, Arial, sans-serif; font-size: 14px;">The following Departments will answer: </span>
<p style="margin: 0cm;"/>
<p style="margin: 0cm;"><span style="font-size: 10.0pt; font-family: Lora; color: black;">Business and Trade; Culture, Media and Sport; Education; Energy Security and Net Zero; Foreign, Commonwealth and Development; Home Office; Science, Innovation and Technology; Scotland; Transport; Women and Equalities; Work and Pensions</span></p></from_cdata></MotionText>
<OPHeading2>Election of the Chair of the Public Administration and Constitutional Affairs Committee</OPHeading2>
<DebateTimingRubric>Nominations and ballot</DebateTimingRubric>
<MotionText><from_cdata>Nominations must be handed in to the Table Office or Public Bill Office on days when the House is sitting and at the latest by <span style="text-decoration: underline;"><strong>12 noon</strong></span> on Tuesday 7 May. Nomination forms are available in those offices and in the Vote Office.
Only members of the Conservative Party may be candidates in this election.
Each nomination shall consist of a signed declaration made by the candidate declaring their willingness to stand for election, accompanied by the signatures of 15 Members elected to the House as members of the same party as the candidate. Nominations may (optionally) be accompanied by signatures of up to five Members elected to the House as members of any party other than that to which the candidate belongs, or members of no party.
No Member may sign more than one candidate&#8217;s nomination paper; if any Member does so, their signature will be invalidated for all nominations. Nominations may (optionally) be accompanied by a supporting statement of no more than 500 words: supporting statements are published online and in an election day booklet.
If there is more than one candidate, the ballot will take place between 11.00am and 2.30pm on Wednesday 8 May in the Aye division lobby.
As soon as practicable after the votes have been counted the Speaker will announce to the House the results of the ballot.</from_cdata></MotionText></root>