<root><OPHeading1>Announcements</OPHeading1>
<OPHeading2>Forthcoming End of Day Adjournment Debates</OPHeading2>
<MotionText><from_cdata>Applications for 30-minute end of day adjournment debates should be made to the Table Office by 7.00pm or rise of the House, whichever is the earlier, on the Wednesdays listed below. Members can submit their application via MemberHub, from their own email account or in hard copy. Application forms are available on the Table Office page on ParliNet. The ballot takes place on the day following the deadline. Members who are successful will be contacted by the Speaker&#8217;s Office.
<strong/></from_cdata></MotionText>
<DebateTimingRubric>Tuesday 5 to Monday 11 March (deadline Wednesday 28 February 7.00pm or the rise of the House, whichever is earlier)</DebateTimingRubric>
<DebateTimingRubric>Tuesday 12 to Monday 18 March (deadline Wednesday 6 March 7.00pm or the rise of the House, whichever is earlier)</DebateTimingRubric>
<DebateTimingRubric>Tuesday 19 to Tuesday 26 March (deadline Wednesday 13 March 7.00pm or the rise of the House, whichever is earlier)</DebateTimingRubric>
<DebateTimingRubric>Monday 15 to Monday 22 April (deadline Wednesday 20 March 7.00pm or the rise of the House, whichever is earlier)</DebateTimingRubric>
<OPHeading2>Forthcoming Westminster Hall Debates</OPHeading2>
<MotionText><from_cdata>The rota for answering Departments is listed below. Applications for 90, 60 and 30-minute debates should be made to the Table Office by 10.00pm or the rise of the House, whichever is the earlier, on the Mondays listed below. Members can submit their application via MemberHub, from their own email account or in hard copy. Application forms are available on the Table Office page on ParliNet. The ballot takes place on the day following the deadline. Members who are successful will be contacted by the Speaker&#8217;s Office.</from_cdata></MotionText>
<DebateTimingRubric>Tuesday 5 and Wednesday 6 March (ballot closed)</DebateTimingRubric>
<MotionText><from_cdata><span style="color: #4d4d4d; font-family: National, Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif; font-size: 18px;">The ballot for Tuesday 5 and Wednesday 6 March will take place today. The deadline for making an application to this ballot has now passed.</span></from_cdata></MotionText>
<DebateTimingRubric>Tuesday 12 and Wednesday 13 March (deadline Monday 4 March 10.00pm or the rise of the House, whichever is earlier)</DebateTimingRubric>
<MotionText><from_cdata><span style="color: #333333; font-family: 'helvetica neue', Helvetica, Arial, sans-serif; font-size: 14px;">The following Departments will answer: </span>
<p style="margin: 0cm;"/>
<p style="margin: 0cm;">Business and Trade; Culture, Media and Sport; Defence; Health and Social Care; Justice; Levelling Up, Housing and Communities; Science, Innovation and Technology; Scotland; Women and Equalities; Work and Pensions</p></from_cdata></MotionText></root>