<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<root><Heading3Underlined>Oral Questions to the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport</Heading3Underlined>
<QuestionRestart number="1"><Member>Dame Diana Johnson</Member><Constit> (Kingston upon Hull North)</Constit> <QnText>What discussions she has had with the BBC on its proposed cuts to local radio services.</QnText><UIN> (904659)</UIN></QuestionRestart>
<Question number="2"><Member>Mr Louie French</Member><Constit> (Old Bexley and Sidcup)</Constit> <QnText>What steps her Department is taking to encourage community participation in the celebration of the coronation of His Majesty King Charles III.</QnText><UIN> (904660)</UIN></Question>
<Question number="3"><Member>Rob Roberts</Member><Constit> (Delyn)</Constit> <QnText>What steps her Department is taking to increase children’s participation in grassroots sport.</QnText><UIN> (904661)</UIN></Question>
<Question number="4"><Member>Nicola Richards</Member><Constit> (West Bromwich East)</Constit> <QnText>What steps her Department is taking to support grassroots sport.</QnText><UIN> (904663)</UIN></Question>
<Question number="5"><Member>Dr Rupa Huq</Member><Constit> (Ealing Central and Acton)</Constit> <QnText>What steps she is taking to support musicians from Ukraine and Europe to tour in the UK.</QnText><UIN> (904664)</UIN></Question>
<Question number="6"><Member>Esther McVey</Member><Constit> (Tatton)</Constit> <QnText>What steps her Department is taking to support grassroots sport.</QnText><UIN> (904668)</UIN></Question>
<Question number="7"><Member>Mary Kelly Foy</Member><Constit> (City of Durham)</Constit> <QnText>What steps she is taking to support cultural and charitable organisations with increases in the cost of living.</QnText><UIN> (904669)</UIN></Question>
<Question number="8"><Member>Nickie Aiken</Member><Constit> (Cities of London and Westminster)</Constit> <QnText>What steps her Department is taking to encourage community participation in the celebration of the coronation of His Majesty King Charles III.</QnText><UIN> (904675)</UIN></Question>
<Times>At 10.00am</Times>
<Heading3Underlined>Topical Questions to the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport</Heading3Underlined>
<TopicalQuestionRestart number="T1"><Member>Kevin Brennan</Member><Constit> (Cardiff West)</Constit> <QnText>If she will make a statement on her departmental responsibilities.</QnText><UIN> (904676)</UIN></TopicalQuestionRestart>
<TopicalQuestion number="T2"><Member>Andrew Lewer</Member><Constit> (Northampton South)</Constit><QnText/><UIN> (904680)</UIN></TopicalQuestion>
<TopicalQuestion number="T3"><Member>Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck</Member><Constit> (South Shields)</Constit><QnText/><UIN> (904681)</UIN></TopicalQuestion>
<TopicalQuestion number="T4"><Member>Peter Aldous</Member><Constit> (Waveney)</Constit><QnText/><UIN> (904682)</UIN></TopicalQuestion>
<TopicalQuestion number="T5"><Member>Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi</Member><Constit> (Slough)</Constit><QnText/><UIN> (904683)</UIN></TopicalQuestion>
<Times>At 10.10am</Times>
<Heading3Underlined>Oral Questions to the hon. Member for Lancaster and Fleetwood, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission and the Member for South West Bedfordshire, representing the Church Commissioners</Heading3Underlined>
<QuestionRestart number="1"><Member>Tim Loughton</Member><Constit> (East Worthing and Shoreham)</Constit> <QnText>To ask the hon. Member for South West Bedfordshire, representing the Church Commissioners, what discussions the Church of England has had with international counterparts on the desecration of religious sites in the Holy Land.</QnText><UIN> (904699)</UIN></QuestionRestart>
<Question number="2"><Member>Fiona Bruce</Member><Constit> (Congleton)</Constit> <QnText>To ask the hon. Member for South West Bedfordshire, representing the Church Commissioners, what discussions the Church of England has had with the Church of Nigeria on the killing and abduction of Christians in that country.</QnText><UIN> (904700)</UIN></Question>
<Question number="3"><Member>Kevin Brennan</Member><Constit> (Cardiff West)</Constit> <QnText>To ask the hon. Member for Lancaster and Fleetwood, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what recent discussions the Committee has had with the Electoral Commission on the security of postal votes.</QnText><UIN> (904701)</UIN></Question>
<Question number="4"><Member>Sir Desmond Swayne</Member><Constit> (New Forest West)</Constit> <QnText>To ask the hon. Member for South West Bedfordshire, representing the Church Commissioners, what discussions the Church of England has had with international counterparts on the desecration of religious sites in the Holy Land.</QnText><UIN> (904702)</UIN></Question>
<Question number="5"><Member>Selaine Saxby</Member><Constit> (North Devon)</Constit> <QnText>To ask the hon. Member for South West Bedfordshire, representing the Church Commissioners, how the Church of England plans to spend grant funding from local authorities.</QnText><UIN> (904703)</UIN></Question>
<Question number="6"><Member>Martin Vickers</Member><Constit> (Cleethorpes)</Constit> <QnText>To ask the hon. Member for South West Bedfordshire, representing the Church Commissioners, what steps the Church of England is taking to strengthen its parish ministry.</QnText><UIN> (904704)</UIN></Question>
<Question number="7"><Member>Mr Philip Hollobone</Member><Constit> (Kettering)</Constit> <QnText>To ask the hon. Member for South West Bedfordshire, representing the Church Commissioners, whether the Church of England is taking steps to plant more trees on its land.</QnText><UIN> (904705)</UIN></Question>
<Question number="8"><Member>Kirsten Oswald</Member><Constit> (East Renfrewshire)</Constit> <QnText>To ask the hon. Member for Lancaster and Fleetwood, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what recent discussions the Committee has had with the Electoral Commission on the implementation of voter ID in (a) Scotland, (b) Wales and (c) England ahead of local and national elections.</QnText><UIN> (904707)</UIN></Question>
<Question number="9"><Member>Jerome Mayhew</Member><Constit> (Broadland)</Constit> <QnText>To ask the hon. Member for South West Bedfordshire, representing the Church Commissioners, how the Church of England plans to spend grant funding from local authorities.</QnText><UIN> (904708)</UIN></Question>
<Question number="10"><Member>Michael Fabricant</Member><Constit> (Lichfield)</Constit> <QnText>To ask the hon. Member for South West Bedfordshire, representing the Church Commissioners, what steps the Church of England plans to take to mark the coronation of His Majesty King Charles III in (a) cathedrals and (b) other places of worship outside of London; and if he will make a statement.</QnText><UIN> (904709)</UIN></Question>
</root>