<root><OPHeading1>Business Today: Chamber</OPHeading1>
<DebateTimingRubric>11.30am Prayers</DebateTimingRubric>
<DebateTimingRubric>Followed by</DebateTimingRubric>
<OPHeading2>Questions</OPHeading2>
<QUESTIONS/>
<OPHeading2>Urgent Questions and Statements</OPHeading2>
<DebateTimingRubric>12.30pm</DebateTimingRubric>
<BusinessItemHeadingBulleted>Urgent Questions (if any)</BusinessItemHeadingBulleted>
<BusinessItemHeadingBulleted>Ministerial Statements (if any)</BusinessItemHeadingBulleted>
<OPHeading2>Presentation of Bills</OPHeading2>
<DebateTimingRubric>No debate<SOReference> (Standing Order No. 57)</SOReference></DebateTimingRubric>
<Heading3Underlined>Tobacco and Vapes </Heading3Underlined>
<MotionSponsor>Victoria Atkins</MotionSponsor>
<MotionText><from_cdata>Bill to make provision about the supply of tobacco, vapes and other products, including provision prohibiting the sale of tobacco to people born on or after 1 January 2009; and to enable product requirements to be imposed in connection with tobacco, vapes and other products.</from_cdata></MotionText>
<Heading3Underlined>Private Parking (Regulator)</Heading3Underlined>
<MotionSponsor>Emma Hardy</MotionSponsor>
<MotionText><from_cdata><p class="MsoNormal"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt; font-family: 'Calibri',sans-serif; mso-fareast-font-family: Calibri; mso-fareast-theme-font: minor-latin; mso-ligatures: standardcontextual; mso-ansi-language: EN-GB; mso-fareast-language: EN-US; mso-bidi-language: AR-SA;">Bill to establish a regulator of privately-owned car parks; to make provision about the powers and duties of that regulator; and for connected purposes.</span></p></from_cdata></MotionText>
<OPHeading2>Business of the Day</OPHeading2>
<BusinessItemHeadingNumbered>Standards in Public Life (Codes of Conduct): Ten Minute Rule Motion</BusinessItemHeadingNumbered>
<DebateTimingRubric>Up to 20 minutes<SOReference> (Standing Order No. 23)</SOReference></DebateTimingRubric>
<MotionSponsor>Debbie Abrahams</MotionSponsor>
<MotionText><from_cdata>That leave be given to bring in a Bill to provide for a statutory code of conduct for Ministers of the Crown; for a statutory code of conduct for Members of the House of Commons and Members of the House of Lords; for a statutory code of conduct for councillors in England; and for connected purposes.</from_cdata></MotionText>
<NoteHeading>Notes:</NoteHeading>
<NoteText><from_cdata><p>The Member moving and a Member opposing this Motion may each speak for up to 10 minutes.</p></from_cdata></NoteText>
<Line_Interstitial> </Line_Interstitial>
<BusinessItemHeadingNumbered>Post Office (Horizon System) Offences Bill: Second Reading</BusinessItemHeadingNumbered>
<DebateTimingRubric>Until 7.00pm <SOReference> (Standing Order No. 9(3) )</SOReference></DebateTimingRubric>
<NoteHeading>Relevant Documents:</NoteHeading>
<NoteText><from_cdata><p class="MsoNormal">Third Report of the Business and Trade Committee, Post Office and Horizon redress: Instruction to deliver, HC 477</p></from_cdata></NoteText>
<Line_Interstitial> </Line_Interstitial>
<BusinessItemHeadingNumbered>POST OFFICE (HORIZON SYSTEM) OFFENCES BILL: PROGRAMME</BusinessItemHeadingNumbered>
<DebateTimingRubric>No debate<SOReference> (Standing Order No. 83A(7))</SOReference></DebateTimingRubric>
<MotionSponsor>Kemi Badenoch</MotionSponsor>
<MotionText><from_cdata>That the following provisions shall apply to the Post Office (Horizon System) Offences Bill:
<strong>Committal</strong>
(1) The Bill shall be committed to a Committee of the whole House.
<strong>Proceedings in Committee of the whole House, on Consideration and on Third Reading</strong>
(2) Proceedings in Committee of the whole House, any proceedings on Consideration and proceedings on Third Reading shall be completed either in one day or in two days, in accordance with the following provisions of this Order.
(3) Proceedings in Committee of the whole House shall (so far as not previously concluded) be brought to a conclusion five hours after their commencement.
(4) If there are no proceedings on Consideration, proceedings on Third Reading&#8212;
   (a) shall be taken on the day on which proceedings in Committee commenced, and
   (b) shall (so far as not previously concluded) be brought to a conclusion one hour after the commencement of proceedings on Third Reading.
(5) If there are proceedings on Consideration&#8212;
   (a) those proceedings shall be taken on the second day, and shall (so far as not previously concluded) be brought to a conclusion one hour before the moment of interruption on that day, and
   (b) proceedings on Third Reading shall (so far as not previously concluded) be brought to a conclusion at the moment of interruption on that day.
<strong>Programming committee</strong>
(6) Standing Order No. 83B (Programming committees) shall not apply to proceedings in Committee of the whole House, to any proceedings on Consideration or to proceedings on Third Reading.
<strong>Other proceedings</strong>
(7) Any other proceedings on the Bill may be programmed.</from_cdata></MotionText>
<Line_Interstitial> </Line_Interstitial>
<BusinessItemHeadingNumbered>POST OFFICE (HORIZON SYSTEM) OFFENCES BILL: MONEY</BusinessItemHeadingNumbered>
<DebateTimingRubric>No debate<SOReference> (Standing Order No. 52(1)(a) )</SOReference></DebateTimingRubric>
<MotionSponsor>Nigel Huddleston</MotionSponsor>
<MotionText><from_cdata>That, for the purposes of any Act resulting from the Post Office (Horizon System) Offences Bill, it is expedient to authorise the payment out of money provided by Parliament of any expenditure incurred by the Secretary of State by virtue of the Act.</from_cdata></MotionText>
<NoteHeading>Notes:</NoteHeading>
<NoteText><from_cdata><p><span style="color: #4d4d4d; font-family: National, Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif; font-size: 16px;">King&#8217;s Recommendation signified.</span></p></from_cdata></NoteText>
<OPHeading2>Presentation of Public Petitions</OPHeading2>
<DebateTimingRubric>No debate or decision <SOReference>(Standing Order No. 153)</SOReference></DebateTimingRubric>
<MotionText>Proposed Mallard Pass solar plant: <PresenterSponsor>Alicia Kearns</PresenterSponsor></MotionText>
<MotionText>Sharlotte&#8217;s Law: <PresenterSponsor>Jonathan Gullis</PresenterSponsor></MotionText>
<MotionText>Recommendations of the Infected Blood Inquiry: <PresenterSponsor>Chris Stephens</PresenterSponsor></MotionText>
<MotionText>Recommendations of the Infected Blood Inquiry: <PresenterSponsor>Andrew Gwynne</PresenterSponsor></MotionText>
<MotionText>Recommendations of the Infected Blood Inquiry: <PresenterSponsor>Rachael Maskell</PresenterSponsor></MotionText>
<MotionText>Barclays Bank closure in Suffolk: <PresenterSponsor>Dr Th&#233;r&#232;se Coffey</PresenterSponsor></MotionText>
<MotionText>Access to GP appointments: <PresenterSponsor>Fleur Anderson</PresenterSponsor></MotionText>
<OPHeading2>Adjournment Debate</OPHeading2>
<DebateTimingRubric>Until 7.30pm or for half an hour (whichever is later)<SOReference> (Standing Order No. 9(7))</SOReference></DebateTimingRubric>
<MotionText>Scrutiny of Secretaries of State in the House of Lords: <PresenterSponsor>Patrick Grady</PresenterSponsor></MotionText>
<OPHeading1>Business Today: Westminster Hall</OPHeading1>
<OPHeading2>Order of Business</OPHeading2>
<DebateTimingRubric>The first part of the sitting will last for two hours. The second part of the sitting will last for three hours (Standing Order No. 10(1)).</DebateTimingRubric>
<DebateTimingRubric>9.30am</DebateTimingRubric>
<MotionText>That this House has considered access to migraine treatment: <PresenterSponsor>Dehenna Davison</PresenterSponsor></MotionText>
<DebateTimingRubric>11.00am</DebateTimingRubric>
<MotionText>That this House has considered the conduct of elections: <PresenterSponsor>Wendy Chamberlain</PresenterSponsor></MotionText>
<NoteHeading>Notes:</NoteHeading>
<NoteText><from_cdata><p>The sitting will be suspended from 11.30am to 2.30pm.</p></from_cdata></NoteText>
<DebateTimingRubric>2.30pm</DebateTimingRubric>
<MotionText>That this House has considered human rights in Sri Lanka: <PresenterSponsor>Elliot Colburn</PresenterSponsor></MotionText>
<DebateTimingRubric>4.00pm</DebateTimingRubric>
<MotionText>That this House has considered public access to defibrillators: <PresenterSponsor>Jonathan Gullis</PresenterSponsor></MotionText>
<DebateTimingRubric>4.30pm</DebateTimingRubric>
<MotionText>That this House has considered lessons learned from the Terance Radford Prevention of Future Deaths Report: <PresenterSponsor>Lee Anderson</PresenterSponsor></MotionText>
<NoteHeading>Notes:</NoteHeading>
<NoteText><from_cdata><p><span style="color: #333333; font-family: 'helvetica neue', Helvetica, Arial, sans-serif; font-size: 14px;">The debate at 4.30pm will last for up to an hour.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #333333; font-family: 'helvetica neue', Helvetica, Arial, sans-serif; font-size: 14px;">The sitting will be suspended and time added if divisions take place in the main Chamber (Standing Order No. 10(3)).</span></p></from_cdata></NoteText></root>