<root><OPHeading1>Business Today: Chamber</OPHeading1>
<DebateTimingRubric>2.30pm Prayers</DebateTimingRubric>
<DebateTimingRubric>Followed by</DebateTimingRubric>
<OPHeading2>Questions</OPHeading2>
<QUESTIONS/>
<OPHeading2>Urgent Questions and Statements</OPHeading2>
<DebateTimingRubric>3.30pm</DebateTimingRubric>
<BusinessItemHeadingBulleted>Urgent Questions (if any)</BusinessItemHeadingBulleted>
<BusinessItemHeadingBulleted>Ministerial Statements (if any)</BusinessItemHeadingBulleted>
<OPHeading2>Presentation of Bills</OPHeading2>
<DebateTimingRubric>No debate<SOReference> (Standing Order No. 57)</SOReference></DebateTimingRubric>
<Heading3Underlined>Fixed-term Parliaments</Heading3Underlined>
<MotionSponsor>Ed Davey</MotionSponsor>
<MotionText><from_cdata><span style="mso-fareast-language: EN-US;">Bill to make provision about the dissolution of Parliament and the determination of polling days for parliamentary general elections; and for connected purposes.</span></from_cdata></MotionText>
<OPHeading2>Business of the Day</OPHeading2>
<BusinessItemHeadingNumbered>OFFSHORE PETROLEUM LICENSING BILL: SECOND READING</BusinessItemHeadingNumbered>
<DebateTimingRubric>Until 10.00pm<SOReference> (Standing Order No. 9(3) )</SOReference></DebateTimingRubric>
<Line_Interstitial> </Line_Interstitial>
<BusinessItemHeadingNumbered>No title </BusinessItemHeadingNumbered>
<MotionSponsor>Caroline Lucas</MotionSponsor>
<MotionSponsor>Alex Sobel</MotionSponsor>
<MotionSponsor>Tommy Sheppard</MotionSponsor>
<MotionSponsor>Zarah Sultana</MotionSponsor>
<MotionText><from_cdata><p class="MsoNormal">That this House declines to give a Second Reading to the Offshore Petroleum Licensing Bill because, whilst it provides for changes to the North Sea oil and gas licensing regime, the North Sea Transition Authority is clear that legislation to mandate annual licensing rounds is not needed, the Bill will not deliver energy security for the UK which would be better achieved by unleashing cheap and abundant renewable energy and delivering a nationwide, street by street, energy efficiency programme, will not reduce household energy bills, as any oil and gas will be sold on global markets to the highest bidder, fails to respond to the urgency of the climate crisis, to warnings that governments already plan to produce double the amount of fossil fuels&#8239;in 2030&#8239;than would be consistent with limiting global heating to 1.5&#176;C, and to the signal from COP28 in Dubai that the fossil fuel era is over, undermines UK climate targets, with the Climate Change Committee observing that expansion of fossil fuel production is not in line with net zero, proposes weaker tests than those included in the flawed Climate Compatibility Checkpoint, could lead to significant costs to the Treasury, including the risk of stranded assets, and fails to rule out new oil and gas licences, amend the Petroleum Act 1998 in order to remove the duty to maximise economic recovery of petroleum, or set a new duty for the North Sea Transition Authority to deliver an orderly and just phase-out of oil and gas.</p></from_cdata></MotionText>
<Line_Interstitial> </Line_Interstitial>
<BusinessItemHeadingNumbered>No title </BusinessItemHeadingNumbered>
<MotionSponsor>Keir Starmer</MotionSponsor>
<MotionSponsor>Angela Rayner</MotionSponsor>
<MotionSponsor>Edward Miliband</MotionSponsor>
<MotionSponsor>Dr Alan Whitehead</MotionSponsor>
<MotionSponsor>Lucy Powell</MotionSponsor>
<MotionSponsor>Sir Alan Campbell</MotionSponsor>
<MotionText><from_cdata><p class="MsoNormal"><span style="color: black; mso-ligatures: none;">That this House, while affirming the need for urgent action to tackle the UK&#8217;s energy insecurity, the cost of living crisis, and the climate crisis, and for a managed, fair, and prosperous transition for workers and communities, declines to give a Second Reading to the Offshore Petroleum Licensing Bill because mandating annual oil and gas licensing rounds will not reduce energy costs for households and businesses as the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero has stated, will not enhance energy security, offers no plan for the future of the UK&#8217;s offshore energy communities, will ensure the UK remains at the mercy of petrostates and dictators who control fossil fuel markets, is entirely incompatible with the UK&#8217;s international climate change commitments and is a totally unnecessary piece of legislation which will do nothing to serve the UK&#8217;s national interest.</span><span style="font-size: 10.0pt; color: #212121; mso-ligatures: none;"/></p></from_cdata></MotionText>
<Line_Interstitial> </Line_Interstitial>
<BusinessItemHeadingNumbered>No title </BusinessItemHeadingNumbered>
<MotionSponsor>Wera Hobhouse</MotionSponsor>
<MotionText><from_cdata><span style="font-size: 12pt; font-family: Aptos, sans-serif;">That this House declines to give a Second Reading to the Offshore Petroleum Licensing Bill because, notwithstanding the need to ensure a secure supply of energy, it confers a duty to do what can already be done at least annually and as often as the Government wants, it fails to take vital steps to grow the UK renewable energy sector and reduce energy bills, and it fails to form a coherent path to net zero.</span></from_cdata></MotionText>
<Line_Interstitial> </Line_Interstitial>
<BusinessItemHeadingNumbered>No title</BusinessItemHeadingNumbered>
<MotionSponsor>Dave Doogan</MotionSponsor>
<MotionSponsor>Stephen Flynn</MotionSponsor>
<MotionSponsor>Stewart Hosie</MotionSponsor>
<MotionSponsor>Drew Hendry</MotionSponsor>
<MotionSponsor>David Linden</MotionSponsor>
<MotionSponsor>Owen Thompson</MotionSponsor>
<MotionText><from_cdata><p class="MsoNormal"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt; color: #212121;">That this House, while acknowledging the role of the exploitation of fossil fuels in ensuring a just transition, and noting that the independent Committee on Climate Change is clear that in reaching net zero by 2050 oil and gas will still be required, declines to give a Second Reading to the Offshore Petroleum Licensing Bill because the Bill does not provide an evidence-based assessment of all licences on a case-by-case basis based on an ability to simultaneously deliver cheaper energy bills, energy security, job security, net zero commitments and concurrent investment in renewable energy projects, fails to outline a transition away from fossil fuels as per the agreed resolution at COP28, does not acknowledge the climate emergency and does not seek to address the necessity for a reduction in domestic demand.</span><span style="color: #212121;"/></p></from_cdata></MotionText>
<Line_Interstitial> </Line_Interstitial>
<BusinessItemHeadingNumbered>OFFSHORE PETROLEUM LICENSING BILL: PROGRAMME</BusinessItemHeadingNumbered>
<DebateTimingRubric>No debate<SOReference> (Standing Order No. 83A(7))</SOReference></DebateTimingRubric>
<MotionSponsor>Claire Coutinho</MotionSponsor>
<MotionText><from_cdata>That the following provisions shall apply to the Offshore Petroleum Licensing Bill:
<strong>Committal</strong>
(1) The Bill shall be committed to a Committee of the whole House.
<strong>Proceedings in Committee, on Consideration and on Third Reading</strong>
(2) Proceedings in Committee of the whole House shall (so far as not previously concluded) be brought to a conclusion three hours after their commencement.
(3) Any proceedings on Consideration and proceedings on Third Reading shall (so far as not previously concluded) be brought to a conclusion four hours after the commencement of proceedings in Committee of the whole House.
(4) Standing Order No. 83B (Programming committees) shall not apply to proceedings in Committee of the whole House, to any proceedings on Consideration or to proceedings on Third Reading.
<strong>Other proceedings</strong>
(5) Any other proceedings on the Bill may be programmed.</from_cdata></MotionText>
<Line_Interstitial> </Line_Interstitial>
<BusinessItemHeadingNumbered>Disclosure of Information</BusinessItemHeadingNumbered>
<DebateTimingRubric>No debate<SOReference> (Standing Order No. 118(6))</SOReference></DebateTimingRubric>
<MotionSponsor>Alex Burghart</MotionSponsor>
<MotionText><from_cdata>That the draft Digital Government (Disclosure of Information) (Identity Verification Services) Regulations 2023, which were laid before this House on 19 September 2023, in the last Session of Parliament, be approved.</from_cdata></MotionText>
<NoteHeading>Notes:</NoteHeading>
<NoteText><from_cdata><p>If this item is opposed after 10.00pm, the division will be deferred.</p></from_cdata></NoteText>
<Line_Interstitial> </Line_Interstitial>
<BusinessItemHeadingNumbered>Buildings and Buildings</BusinessItemHeadingNumbered>
<DebateTimingRubric>No debate<SOReference> (Standing Order No. 118(6))</SOReference></DebateTimingRubric>
<MotionSponsor>Lee Rowley</MotionSponsor>
<MotionText><from_cdata>That the draft Higher-Risk Buildings (Keeping and Provision of Information etc.) (England) Regulations 2023<span style="color: #333333; font-family: Arial, Verdana, sans-serif; font-size: 14px;">, </span>which were laid before this House on 9 November 2023, be approved.</from_cdata></MotionText>
<NoteHeading>Notes:</NoteHeading>
<NoteText><from_cdata><p><span style="color: #4d4d4d; font-family: National, Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif; font-size: 16px;">If this item is opposed after 10.00pm, the division will be deferred.</span></p></from_cdata></NoteText>
<OPHeading2>Adjournment Debate</OPHeading2>
<DebateTimingRubric>Until 10.30pm or for half an hour (whichever is later)<SOReference> (Standing Order No. 9(7))</SOReference></DebateTimingRubric>
<MotionText>Rural transport: <PresenterSponsor>Sir Bill Wiggin</PresenterSponsor></MotionText>
<OPHeading1>Written Statements</OPHeading1>
<OPHeading2>Statements to be Made Today</OPHeading2>
<MotionCrossHeading>Secretary of State for Business and Trade</MotionCrossHeading>
<MinisterialStatement>UK&#8217;s cheese market access in Canada</MinisterialStatement>
<MinisterialStatement>Update on Electric Vehicle Rules of Origin Extension</MinisterialStatement>
<MinisterialStatement>Wine Quantities and Units of Measurement Update</MinisterialStatement>
<MotionCrossHeading>Deputy Foreign Secretary</MotionCrossHeading>
<MinisterialStatement>UK Delegation to the Parliamentary Assembly of the Council of Europe</MinisterialStatement>
<MotionCrossHeading>Secretary of State for Defence</MotionCrossHeading>
<MinisterialStatement>Red Sea Update</MinisterialStatement>
<MotionCrossHeading>Secretary of State for Justice</MotionCrossHeading>
<MinisterialStatement>HMP Wandsworth Update</MinisterialStatement>
<NoteHeading>Notes:</NoteHeading>
<NoteText>Texts of Written Statements are available from the Vote Office and on the internet at https://questions-statements.parliament.uk/ .</NoteText></root>