<root><OPHeading1>Business Today: Chamber</OPHeading1>
<DebateTimingRubric>11.30am Prayers</DebateTimingRubric>
<DebateTimingRubric>Followed by</DebateTimingRubric>
<OPHeading2>Questions</OPHeading2>
<QUESTIONS/>
<OPHeading2>Urgent Questions and Statements</OPHeading2>
<DebateTimingRubric>12.30pm</DebateTimingRubric>
<BusinessItemHeadingBulleted>Urgent Questions (if any)</BusinessItemHeadingBulleted>
<BusinessItemHeadingBulleted>Ministerial Statements (if any)</BusinessItemHeadingBulleted>
<OPHeading2>Presentation of Bills</OPHeading2>
<DebateTimingRubric>No debate<SOReference> (Standing Order No. 57)</SOReference></DebateTimingRubric>
<Heading3Underlined> Children Not in School (National Register and Support) </Heading3Underlined>
<MotionSponsor>Bridget Phillipson</MotionSponsor>
<MotionText><from_cdata><p class="MsoNormal">Bill to provide for a national register of children who are not pupils at any school; to require local authorities to provide data about such children in their area for the purpose of maintaining that register; to make provision about the support that local authorities provide to such children; and for connected purposes.</p></from_cdata></MotionText>
<OPHeading2>Business of the Day</OPHeading2>
<BusinessItemHeadingNumbered>Offensive weapons: Ten Minute Rule Motion</BusinessItemHeadingNumbered>
<DebateTimingRubric>Up to 20 minutes<SOReference> (Standing Order No. 23)</SOReference></DebateTimingRubric>
<MotionSponsor>Helen Hayes</MotionSponsor>
<MotionText><from_cdata>That leave be given to bring in a Bill to make provision about the weapons to which section 141 of the Criminal Justice Act 1988 applies; and for connected purposes.</from_cdata></MotionText>
<NoteHeading>Notes:</NoteHeading>
<NoteText><from_cdata><p>The Member moving and a Member opposing this Motion may each speak for up to 10 minutes.</p></from_cdata></NoteText>
<Line_Interstitial> </Line_Interstitial>
<BusinessItemHeadingNumbered>Opposition Day (3rd allotted day)</BusinessItemHeadingNumbered>
<DebateTimingRubric>Until 7.00pm<SOReference> (Standing Order No. 9(3) )</SOReference></DebateTimingRubric>
<NumberedHeadingIndented>Children not in school (national register and support)</NumberedHeadingIndented>
<MotionSponsorIndented>Keir Starmer</MotionSponsorIndented>
<MotionSponsorIndented>Angela Rayner</MotionSponsorIndented>
<MotionSponsorIndented>Bridget Phillipson</MotionSponsorIndented>
<MotionSponsorIndented>Catherine McKinnell</MotionSponsorIndented>
<MotionSponsorIndented>Lucy Powell</MotionSponsorIndented>
<MotionSponsorIndented>Sir Alan Campbell</MotionSponsorIndented>
<MotionTextIndented><from_cdata>That this House condemns the Secretary of State for Education for her failure to tackle the crisis of persistent school absence; calls on the Government to immediately introduce legislation to amend the Education Act 1996 in order to establish a mandatory duty on local authorities in England to maintain a register of eligible children not in school, as set out in Part 3 of the Schools Bill [Lords] published in the 2022-23 Parliamentary session; and therefore makes provision as set out in this Order:
(1) On Wednesday 7 February 2024:
(a) Standing Order No. 14(1) (which provides that government business shall have precedence at every sitting save as provided in that order) shall not apply;
(b) any proceedings governed by this order may be proceeded with until any hour, though opposed, and shall not be interrupted;
(c) the Speaker may not propose the question on the previous question, and may not put any question under Standing Order No. 36 (Closure of debate) or Standing Order No. 163 (Motion to sit in private);
(d) at 3.00pm, the Speaker shall interrupt any business prior to the business governed by this order and, notwithstanding the practice of this House as regards to proceeding on a Bill without notice, call the Member for Houghton and Sunderland South or another Member on her behalf to move the order of the day that the Children Not in School (National Register and Support) Bill be now read a second time;
(e) in respect of that Bill, notices of Amendments, new Clauses and new Schedules to be moved in Committee may be accepted by the Clerks at the Table before the Bill has been read a second time.
(f) any proceedings interrupted or superseded by this order may be resumed or (as the case may be) entered upon and proceeded with after the moment of interruption.
(2) The provisions of paragraphs (3) to (18) of this order shall apply to and in connection with the proceedings on the Children Not in School (National Register and Support) Bill in the present Session of Parliament.
Timetable for the Bill on Wednesday 7 February 2024
(3) (a) Proceedings on Second Reading and in Committee of the whole House, any proceedings on Consideration and proceedings up to and including Third Reading shall be taken at the sitting on Wednesday 7 February 2024 in accordance with this Order.
(b) Proceedings on Second Reading shall be brought to a conclusion (so far as not previously concluded) at 5.00pm.
(c) Proceedings on any money resolution which may be moved by a Minister of the Crown in relation to the Bill shall be taken without debate immediately after Second Reading.
(d) Proceedings in Committee of the whole House, any proceedings on Consideration and proceedings up to and including Third Reading shall be brought to a conclusion (so far as not previously concluded) at 7.00pm.
Timing of proceedings and Questions to be put on Wednesday 7 February 2024
(4) When the Bill has been read a second time:
(a) it shall, notwithstanding Standing Order No. 63 (Committal of bills not subject to a programme order), stand committed to a Committee of the whole House without any Question being put;
(b) the Speaker shall leave the Chair whether or not notice of an Instruction has been given.
(5) (a) On the conclusion of proceedings in Committee of the whole House, the Chairman shall report the Bill to the House without putting any Question.
(b) If the Bill is reported with amendments, the House shall proceed to consider the Bill as amended without any Question being put.
(6) For the purpose of bringing any proceedings to a conclusion in accordance with paragraph (3), the Chairman or Speaker shall forthwith put the following Questions in the same order as they would fall to be put if this Order did not apply&#8212;
(a) any Question already proposed from the Chair;
(b) any Question necessary to bring to a decision a Question so proposed;
(c) the Question on any amendment, new clause or new schedule selected by the Chairman or Speaker for separate decision;
(d) the Question on any amendment moved or Motion made by a designated Member;
(e) any other Question necessary for the disposal of the business to be concluded;
and shall not put any other Questions, other than the Question on any motion described in paragraph (15) of this Order.
(7) On a Motion made for a new Clause or a new Schedule, the Chairman or Speaker shall put only the Question that the Clause or Schedule be added to the Bill.
Consideration of Lords Amendments and Messages on a subsequent day
(8) If any message on the Bill (other than a message that the House of Lords agrees with the Bill without amendment or agrees with any message from this House) is expected from the House of Lords on any future sitting day, the House shall not adjourn until that message has been received and any proceedings under paragraph (9) have been concluded.
(9) On any day on which such a message is received, if a designated Member indicates to the Speaker an intention to proceed to consider that message&#8212;
(a) notwithstanding Standing Order No. 14(1) (which provides that government business shall have precedence at every sitting save as provided in that order), any Lords Amendments to the Bill or any further Message from the Lords on the Bill may be considered forthwith without any Question being put; and any proceedings interrupted for that purpose shall be suspended accordingly;
(b) proceedings on consideration of Lords Amendments or on any further Message from the Lords shall (so far as not previously concluded) be brought to a conclusion one hour after their commencement; and any proceedings suspended under subparagraph (a) shall thereupon be resumed;
(c) the Speaker may not propose the question on the previous question, and may not put any question under Standing Order No. 36 (Closure of debate) or Standing Order No. 163 (Motion to sit in private) in the course of those proceedings. 
(10) Paragraphs (2) to (7) of Standing Order No. 83F (Programme orders: conclusion of proceedings on consideration of Lords amendments) apply for the purposes of bringing any proceedings on consideration of Lords Amendments to a conclusion as if: 
(a) any reference to a Minister of the Crown were a reference to a designated Member; 
(b) after paragraph (4)(a) there is inserted&#8212;
<span style="white-space: normal;"><span style="white-space: pre;"> </span>&#8220;(aa) the question on any amendment or motion selected by the Speaker for separate decision;&#8221;.</span>
(11) Paragraphs (2) to (5) of Standing Order No. 83G (Programme orders: conclusion of proceedings on further messages from the Lords) apply for the purposes of bringing any proceedings on consideration of a Lords Message to a conclusion as if any reference to a Minister of the Crown were a reference to a designated Member.
Reasons Committee
(12) Paragraphs (2) to (6) of Standing Order No. 83H (Programme orders: reasons committee) apply in relation to any committee to be appointed to draw up reasons after proceedings have been brought to a conclusion in accordance with this Order as if any reference to a Minister of the Crown were a reference to a designated Member.
Miscellaneous 
(13) Standing Order No. 82 (Business Committee) shall not apply in relation to any proceedings on the Bill to which this Order applies. 
(14) (a) No Motion shall be made, except by a designated Member, to alter the order in which any proceedings on the Bill are taken, to recommit the Bill or to vary or supplement the provisions of this Order. 
(b) No notice shall be required of such a Motion.
(c) Such a Motion may be considered forthwith without any Question being put; and any proceedings interrupted for that purpose shall be suspended accordingly.
(d) The Question on such a Motion shall be put forthwith; and any proceedings suspended under sub-paragraph (c) shall thereupon be resumed.
(e) Standing Order No. 15(1) (Exempted business) shall apply to proceedings on such a Motion.
(15) (a) No dilatory Motion shall be made in relation to proceedings on the Bill to which this Order applies except by a designated Member. 
(b) The Question on any such Motion shall be put forthwith. 
(16) Proceedings to which this Order applies shall not be interrupted under any Standing Order relating to the sittings of the House. 
(17) No private business may be considered at any sitting to which the provisions of this order apply. 
(18) (a) The start of any debate under Standing Order No. 24 (Emergency debates) to be held on a day on which proceedings to which this Order applies are to take place shall be postponed until the conclusion of any proceedings to which this Order applies.
(b) Standing Order 15(1) (Exempted business) shall apply in respect of any such debate.
(19) In this Order, &#8220;a designated Member&#8221; means&#8212; 
(a) the Member for Houghton and Sunderland South; and 
(b) any other Member acting on behalf of the Member for Houghton and Sunderland South.</from_cdata></MotionTextIndented>
<Line_Interstitial_Indented> </Line_Interstitial_Indented>
<NumberedHeadingIndented>Protecting steel in the UK</NumberedHeadingIndented>
<MotionSponsorIndented>Keir Starmer</MotionSponsorIndented>
<MotionSponsorIndented>Angela Rayner</MotionSponsorIndented>
<MotionSponsorIndented>Jonathan Reynolds</MotionSponsorIndented>
<MotionSponsorIndented>Sarah Jones</MotionSponsorIndented>
<MotionSponsorIndented>Jo Stevens</MotionSponsorIndented>
<MotionSponsorIndented>Sir Alan Campbell</MotionSponsorIndented>
<MotionTextIndented><from_cdata><p class="MsoNormal"><span style="font-family: 'Aptos',sans-serif;">That this House recognises the need to decarbonise steel production; appreciates the pride that local communities have in their historic steelworks; regrets that the Government has pushed through plans for decarbonising steel in the UK which will result in thousands of steelworkers losing their jobs and risk leaving the UK as the first developed country in the world without the capacity to produce primary steel; further regrets that the Government has failed to produce an industrial strategy which could have included a plan for the whole steel sector; believes that primary steel is a sovereign capability and is therefore concerned about the impact that the Government&#8217;s plans could have on national security; also believes that steel production can have a bright future in the UK; therefore calls on the Government to work with industry and workers to achieve a transition that secures jobs and primary steelmaking for decades to come; and further calls on the Secretary of State for Business and Trade to report to Parliament by 27 February 2024 with an assessment of the impact on the UK of the loss of primary steel production capabilities.</span></p></from_cdata></MotionTextIndented>
<NoteHeading>Notes:</NoteHeading>
<NoteText><from_cdata><p>The selection of the matters to be debated has been made by the Leader of the Opposition (Standing Order No.14(2)).</p></from_cdata></NoteText>
<Line_Interstitial_Indented> </Line_Interstitial_Indented>
<BusinessItemHeadingNumbered>Sanctions</BusinessItemHeadingNumbered>
<DebateTimingRubric>No debate <SOReference> (Standing Order No. 118(6))</SOReference></DebateTimingRubric>
<MotionSponsor>Anne-Marie Trevelyan</MotionSponsor>
<MotionText><from_cdata>That the Iran (Sanctions) Regulations 2023 (SI, 2023, No. 1314), dated 11 December 2023, a copy of which was laid before this House on 13 December 2023, be approved.</from_cdata></MotionText>
<NoteHeading>Notes:</NoteHeading>
<NoteText><from_cdata><p><span style="color: #4d4d4d; font-family: National, Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif; font-size: 16px;"><span style="color: #000000; font-family: 'Helvetica Neue', Helvetica, Arial, sans-serif; font-size: 13px;">If this item is opposed after 7.00pm, the division will be deferred.</span></span></p></from_cdata></NoteText>
<Line_Interstitial> </Line_Interstitial>
<BusinessItemHeadingNumbered>Sanctions</BusinessItemHeadingNumbered>
<DebateTimingRubric>No debate <SOReference> (Standing Order No. 118(6))</SOReference></DebateTimingRubric>
<MotionSponsor>Anne-Marie Trevelyan</MotionSponsor>
<MotionText><from_cdata>That the Russia (Sanctions) (EU Exit) (Amendment) (No. 5) Regulations 2023 (SI, 2023, No. 1367), dated 12 December 2023, a copy of which was laid before this House on 14 December 2023, be approved.</from_cdata></MotionText>
<NoteHeading>Notes:</NoteHeading>
<NoteText><from_cdata><p><span style="color: #4d4d4d; font-family: National, Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif; font-size: 16px;"><span style="color: #000000; font-family: 'Helvetica Neue', Helvetica, Arial, sans-serif; font-size: 13px;">If this item is opposed after 7.00pm, the division will be deferred. </span></span></p></from_cdata></NoteText>
<Line_Interstitial> </Line_Interstitial>
<BusinessItemHeadingNumbered>Sanctions</BusinessItemHeadingNumbered>
<DebateTimingRubric>No debate <SOReference> (Standing Order No. 118(6))</SOReference></DebateTimingRubric>
<MotionSponsor>Anne-Marie Trevelyan</MotionSponsor>
<MotionText><from_cdata>That the Russia (Sanctions) (EU Exit) (Amendment) (No. 4) Regulations 2023 (SI, 2023, No. 1364), dated 12 December 2023, a copy of which was laid before this House on 14 December 2023, be approved.</from_cdata></MotionText>
<NoteHeading>Notes:</NoteHeading>
<NoteText><from_cdata><p>If this item is opposed after 7.00pm, the division will be deferred.</p></from_cdata></NoteText>
<OPHeading2>Presentation of Public Petitions</OPHeading2>
<DebateTimingRubric>No debate or decision <SOReference>(Standing Order No. 153)</SOReference></DebateTimingRubric>
<MotionText>Standing charges on energy bills: <PresenterSponsor>Martyn Day</PresenterSponsor></MotionText>
<MotionText>Local businesses and the closure of the Botley Road in Oxford : <PresenterSponsor>Layla Moran</PresenterSponsor></MotionText>
<OPHeading2>Adjournment Debate</OPHeading2>
<DebateTimingRubric>Until 7.30pm or for half an hour (whichever is later)<SOReference> (Standing Order No. 9(7))</SOReference></DebateTimingRubric>
<MotionText>Revised National Planning Policy Framework: <PresenterSponsor>Dame Maria Miller</PresenterSponsor></MotionText>
<OPHeading1>Business Today: Westminster Hall</OPHeading1>
<OPHeading2>Order of Business</OPHeading2>
<DebateTimingRubric>The first part of the sitting will last for two hours. The second part of the sitting will last for three hours (Standing Order No. 10(1)).</DebateTimingRubric>
<DebateTimingRubric>9.30am</DebateTimingRubric>
<MotionText>That this House has considered the future of Girlguiding UK in the British Overseas Territories: <PresenterSponsor>Jim Shannon</PresenterSponsor></MotionText>
<NoteHeading>Notes:</NoteHeading>
<NoteText><from_cdata><p>The subject for this debate was determined by the Backbench Business Committee.</p>
</from_cdata></NoteText>
<DebateTimingRubric>11.00am</DebateTimingRubric>
<MotionText>That this House has considered the regulation of heather burning on peatlands: <PresenterSponsor>Olivia Blake</PresenterSponsor></MotionText>
<NoteHeading>Notes:</NoteHeading>
<NoteText><from_cdata><p>The sitting will be suspended from 11.30am to 2.30pm.</p></from_cdata></NoteText>
<DebateTimingRubric>2.30pm</DebateTimingRubric>
<MotionText>That this House has considered the future of human rights in Hong Kong: <PresenterSponsor>Tim Loughton</PresenterSponsor></MotionText>
<DebateTimingRubric>4.00pm</DebateTimingRubric>
<MotionText>That this House has considered the civil nuclear roadmap and Wylfa: <PresenterSponsor>Virginia Crosbie</PresenterSponsor></MotionText>
<NoteHeading>Relevant Documents:</NoteHeading>
<NoteText><from_cdata><p>Third Report of the Welsh Affairs Committee of Session 2022-23, Nuclear energy in Wales, HC 240, and the Government response, HC 1656</p></from_cdata></NoteText>
<DebateTimingRubric>4.30pm</DebateTimingRubric>
<MotionText>That this House has considered school attendance: <PresenterSponsor>Vicky Ford</PresenterSponsor></MotionText>
<NoteHeading>Notes:</NoteHeading>
<NoteText><from_cdata><p><span style="color: #333333; font-family: 'helvetica neue', Helvetica, Arial, sans-serif;"><span style="font-size: 14px;">The debate at 4.30pm will last for up to an hour.</span></span></p>
<p><span style="color: #333333; font-family: 'helvetica neue', Helvetica, Arial, sans-serif;"><span style="font-size: 14px;"/></span><span style="color: #333333; font-family: 'helvetica neue', Helvetica, Arial, sans-serif;"><span style="font-size: 14px;">The sitting will be suspended and time added if divisions take place in the main Chamber (Standing Order No. 10(3)).</span></span></p></from_cdata></NoteText></root>