<root><OPHeading1>Business Today: Chamber</OPHeading1>
<DebateTimingRubric>11.30am Prayers</DebateTimingRubric>
<DebateTimingRubric>Followed by</DebateTimingRubric>
<OPHeading2>Questions</OPHeading2>
<QUESTIONS/>
<OPHeading2>Urgent Questions and Statements</OPHeading2>
<BusinessItemHeadingBulleted>Urgent Questions (if any)</BusinessItemHeadingBulleted>
<BusinessItemHeadingBulleted>Ministerial Statements (if any)</BusinessItemHeadingBulleted>
<OPHeading2>Presentation of Bills</OPHeading2>
<Heading3Underlined>Northern Ireland (Executive Formation)</Heading3Underlined>
<MotionSponsor>Chris Heaton-Harris</MotionSponsor>
<MotionText><from_cdata><p class="MsoNormal" style="text-align: justify; line-height: normal; tab-stops: right 323.25pt; mso-layout-grid-align: none; text-autospace: none; margin: 14.0pt 0cm 14.0pt 0cm;"><span class="MotionTextChar">Bill to make provision to extend the period following the Northern Ireland Assembly election of 5 May 2022 during which Ministers may be appointed.</span><span style="mso-bidi-font-size: 10.0pt; font-family: 'Frutiger LT Std 55 Roman',sans-serif; color: black; mso-fareast-language: EN-GB;"/></p></from_cdata></MotionText>
<DebateTimingRubric>No debate<SOReference> (Standing Order No. 57)</SOReference></DebateTimingRubric>
<Heading3Underlined>Whistleblowing</Heading3Underlined>
<MotionSponsor>Mary Robinson</MotionSponsor>
<MotionText><from_cdata>Bill to establish an independent Office of the Whistleblower to protect whistleblowers and whistleblowing in accordance with the public interest; to make provision for the Office of the Whistleblower to set, monitor and enforce standards for the management of whistleblowing cases, to provide disclosure and advice services, to direct whistleblowing investigations and to order redress of detriment suffered by whistleblowers; to create offences relating to the treatment of whistleblowers and the handling of whistleblowing cases; to repeal the Public Interest Disclosure Act 1998; and for connected purposes.</from_cdata></MotionText>
<OPHeading2>Business of the Day</OPHeading2>
<BusinessItemHeadingNumbered>Road traffic and street works: Ten Minute Rule Motion</BusinessItemHeadingNumbered>
<DebateTimingRubric>Up to 20 minutes<SOReference> (Standing Order No. 23)</SOReference></DebateTimingRubric>
<MotionSponsor>Kit Malthouse</MotionSponsor>
<MotionText><from_cdata>That leave be given to bring in a Bill <span style="font-family: Calibri, sans-serif; font-size: 11pt;">to make provision about speeding offences on roads to which a 20mph limit applies; to make provision about the enforcement of moving traffic offences; to require 24 hour staffing of works on specified public roads; and for connected purposes.</span></from_cdata></MotionText>
<NoteHeading>Notes:</NoteHeading>
<NoteText><from_cdata><p>The Member moving and a Member opposing this Motion may each speak for up to 10 minutes.</p></from_cdata></NoteText>
<Line_Interstitial> </Line_Interstitial>
<BusinessItemHeadingNumbered>NORTHERN IRELAND (EXECUTIVE FORMATION) BILL: BUSINESS OF THE HOUSE MOTION</BusinessItemHeadingNumbered>
<DebateTimingRubric>Until any hour (if the 7.00pm Business of the House motion is agreed to)</DebateTimingRubric>
<MotionSponsor>Chris Heaton-Harris</MotionSponsor>
<MotionText><from_cdata>That the following provisions shall apply to the proceedings on the Northern Ireland (Executive Formation) Bill:
Timetable
(1) (a) Proceedings on Second Reading and in Committee of the whole House, any proceedings on Consideration and proceedings on Third Reading shall be taken at today&#8217;s sitting in accordance with this Order.
(b) Notices of Amendments, new Clauses or new Schedules to be moved in Committee of the whole House may be accepted by the Clerks at the Table before the Bill has been read a second time. 
(c) Proceedings on Second Reading shall (so far as not previously concluded) be brought to a conclusion two hours after the commencement of proceedings on the Motion for this Order.
(d) Proceedings in Committee of the whole House, any proceedings on Consideration and proceedings on Third Reading shall (so far as not previously concluded) be brought to a conclusion three hours after the commencement of proceedings on the Motion for this Order.
Timing of proceedings and Questions to be put
(2) As soon as the proceedings on the Motion for this Order have been concluded, the Order for the Second Reading of the Bill shall be read. 
(3) When the Bill has been read a second time:
(a) it shall, despite Standing Order No. 63 (Committal of bills not subject to a programme order), stand committed to a Committee of the whole House without any Question being put;
(b) the Speaker shall leave the chair whether or not notice of an Instruction has been given.
(4) (a) On the conclusion of proceedings in Committee of the whole House, the Chair shall report the Bill to the House without putting any Question.
(b) If the Bill is reported with amendments, the House shall proceed to consider the Bill as amended without any Question being put.
(5) For the purpose of bringing any proceedings to a conclusion in accordance with paragraph (1), the Chair or Speaker shall forthwith put the following Questions in the same order as they would fall to be put if this Order did not apply:
(a) any Question already proposed from the chair;
(b) any Question necessary to bring to a decision a Question so proposed;
(c) the Question on any amendment moved or Motion made by a Minister of the Crown;
(d) the Question on any amendment, new Clause or new Schedule selected by the Chair or Speaker for separate decision;
(e) any other Question necessary for the disposal of the business to be concluded;
and shall not put any other questions, other than the Question on any motion described in paragraph (16)(a) of this Order.
(6) On a Motion so made for a new Clause or a new Schedule, the Chair or Speaker shall put only the Question that the Clause or Schedule be added to the Bill.
(7) If two or more Questions would fall to be put under paragraph (5)(c) on successive amendments moved or Motions made by a Minister of the Crown, the Chair or Speaker shall instead put a single Question in relation to those amendments or Motions.
(8) If two or more Questions would fall to be put under paragraph (5)(e) in relation to successive provisions of the Bill, the Chair shall instead put a single Question in relation to those provisions, except that the Question shall be put separately on any Clause of or Schedule to the Bill which a Minister of the Crown has signified an intention to leave out.
Consideration of Lords Amendments
(9) (a) Any Lords Amendments to the Bill may be considered forthwith without any Question being put; and any proceedings interrupted for that purpose shall be suspended accordingly.
(b) Proceedings on consideration of Lords Amendments shall (so far as not previously concluded) be brought to a conclusion one hour after their commencement; and any proceedings suspended under sub-paragraph (a) shall thereupon be resumed.
(10) Paragraphs (2) to (7) of Standing Order No. 83F (Programme orders: conclusion of proceedings on consideration of Lords amendments) apply for the purposes of bringing any proceedings to a conclusion in accordance with paragraph (9) of this Order.
Subsequent stages
(11) (a) Any further Message from the Lords on the Bill may be considered forthwith without any Question being put; and any proceedings interrupted for that purpose shall be suspended accordingly.
(b) Proceedings on any further Message from the Lords shall (so far as not previously concluded) be brought to a conclusion one hour after their commencement; and any proceedings suspended under sub-paragraph (a) shall thereupon be resumed.
(12) Paragraphs (2) to (5) of Standing Order No. 83G (Programme orders: conclusion of proceedings on further messages from the Lords) apply for the purposes of bringing any proceedings to a conclusion in accordance with paragraph (11) of this Order.
Reasons Committee
(13) Paragraphs (2) to (6) of Standing Order No. 83H (Programme orders: reasons committee) apply in relation to any committee to be appointed to draw up reasons after proceedings have been brought to a conclusion in accordance with this Order. 
Miscellaneous
(14) Standing Order No. 15(1) (Exempted business) shall apply to proceedings on the Bill.
(15) Standing Order No. 82 (Business Committee) shall not apply in relation to any proceedings to which this Order applies.
(16) (a) No Motion shall be made, except by a Minister of the Crown, to alter the order in which any proceedings on the Bill are taken, to recommit the Bill or to vary or supplement the provisions of this Order.
(b) No notice shall be required of such a Motion.
(c) Such a Motion may be considered forthwith without any Question being put; and any proceedings interrupted for that purpose shall be suspended accordingly.
(d) The Question on such a Motion shall be put forthwith; and any proceedings suspended under sub-paragraph (c) shall thereupon be resumed.
(e) Standing Order No. 15(1) (Exempted business) shall apply to proceedings on such a Motion.
(17) (a) No dilatory Motion shall be made in relation to proceedings to which this Order applies except by a Minister of the Crown.
(b) The Question on any such Motion shall be put forthwith.
(18) (a) The start of any debate under Standing Order No. 24 (Emergency debates) to be held on a day on which the Bill has been set down to be taken as an Order of the Day shall be postponed until the conclusion of any proceedings on that day to which this Order applies.
(b) Standing Order No. 15(1) (Exempted business) shall apply to proceedings in respect of such a debate.
(19) Proceedings to which this Order applies shall not be interrupted under any Standing Order relating to the sittings of the House.</from_cdata></MotionText>
<OPHeading2>Business to be Taken at 7.00pm</OPHeading2>
<BusinessItemHeadingBulleted>BUSINESS OF THE HOUSE</BusinessItemHeadingBulleted>
<DebateTimingRubric>No debate<SOReference> (Standing Order Nos. 15 and 41A)</SOReference></DebateTimingRubric>
<MotionSponsor>Rishi Sunak</MotionSponsor>
<MotionText><from_cdata><span style="font-size: 12pt; font-family: Lora, serif; background-color: transparent; font-variant-numeric: normal; font-variant-east-asian: normal; font-variant-alternates: normal; font-variant-position: normal; vertical-align: baseline; white-space-collapse: preserve;">That, at this day&#8217;s sitting, the Motion in the name of Secretary Chris Heaton-Harris, relating to Northern Ireland (Executive Formation) Bill: Business of the House, may be proceeded with, though opposed, until any hour and Standing Order No. 41A (Deferred divisions) shall not apply.</span></from_cdata></MotionText>
<OPHeading2>Business of the Day</OPHeading2>
<BusinessItemHeadingNumbered>Northern Ireland (Executive Formation) Bill: Second Reading</BusinessItemHeadingNumbered>
<DebateTimingRubric>Up to two hours after commencement of proceedings on the Northern Ireland (Executive Formation) Bill: Business of the House motion (if that motion is agreed to)</DebateTimingRubric>
<Line_Interstitial> </Line_Interstitial>
<BusinessItemHeadingNumbered>Northern Ireland (Executive Formation) Bill: Committee and Remaining Stages</BusinessItemHeadingNumbered>
<DebateTimingRubric>Up to three hours after commencement of proceedings on the Northern Ireland (Executive Formation) Bill: Business of the House motion (if that motion is agreed to, and if the Bill is read a second time)</DebateTimingRubric>
<NoteHeading>Notes:</NoteHeading>
<NoteText><from_cdata><p><span style="font-size: 11.0pt; font-family: 'Calibri',sans-serif; mso-fareast-font-family: Calibri; mso-fareast-theme-font: minor-latin; mso-ansi-language: EN-GB; mso-fareast-language: EN-US; mso-bidi-language: AR-SA;">If the Bill is not amended in Committee, Third Reading will follow immediately after Committee stage. If the Bill is amended in Committee, there will be a Report (Consideration) stage, followed by Third Reading. </span></p></from_cdata></NoteText>
<Line_Interstitial> </Line_Interstitial>
<BusinessItemHeadingNumbered>General debate on the situation in the Red Sea</BusinessItemHeadingNumbered>
<DebateTimingRubric>Until 7.00pm <SOReference> (Standing Order No. 9(3) )</SOReference></DebateTimingRubric>
<MotionSponsor>Rishi Sunak</MotionSponsor>
<MotionText><from_cdata><span style="font-size: 12pt; font-family: Lora, serif; background-color: transparent; font-variant-numeric: normal; font-variant-east-asian: normal; font-variant-alternates: normal; font-variant-position: normal; vertical-align: baseline; white-space-collapse: preserve;">That this House has considered the situation in the Red Sea.</span></from_cdata></MotionText>
<Line_Interstitial> </Line_Interstitial>
<BusinessItemHeadingNumbered>Church of England (General Synod) (Measures)</BusinessItemHeadingNumbered>
<DebateTimingRubric>No debate<SOReference> (Standing Order No. 118(6))</SOReference></DebateTimingRubric>
<MotionSponsor>Andrew Selous</MotionSponsor>
<MotionText><from_cdata><p class="MsoNormal">That the Church of England (Miscellaneous Provisions) Measure (HC 341), passed by the General Synod of the Church of England, be presented to His Majesty for his Royal Assent in the form in which it was laid before Parliament.</p></from_cdata></MotionText>
<NoteHeading>Notes:</NoteHeading>
<NoteText><from_cdata><p class="MsoListParagraph" style="text-indent: -18.0pt; mso-list: l0 level1 lfo1;">If this item is opposed after 7.00pm, the division will be deferred.</p></from_cdata></NoteText>
<NoteHeading>Relevant Documents:</NoteHeading>
<NoteText><from_cdata><p><span class="TextRun SCXW245436758 BCX0" style="margin: 0px; padding: 0px; user-select: text; -webkit-user-drag: none; -webkit-tap-highlight-color: transparent; text-indent: 48px; white-space-collapse: preserve; font-size: 11pt; line-height: 19.425px; font-family: Calibri, Calibri_EmbeddedFont, Calibri_MSFontService, sans-serif; font-variant-ligatures: none !important;" data-contrast="auto"><span class="NormalTextRun SpellingErrorV2Themed SCXW245436758 BCX0" style="margin: 0px; padding: 0px; user-select: text; -webkit-user-drag: none; -webkit-tap-highlight-color: transparent; background-repeat: repeat-x; background-position: left bottom; background-image: var(--urlSpellingErrorV2, ); border-bottom: 1px solid transparent;">245th</span><span class="NormalTextRun SCXW245436758 BCX0" style="margin: 0px; padding: 0px; user-select: text; -webkit-user-drag: none; -webkit-tap-highlight-color: transparent;"> Report of the Ecclesiastical Committee, HC 340</span></span></p></from_cdata></NoteText>
<Line_Interstitial> </Line_Interstitial>
<BusinessItemHeadingNumbered>Church of England (General Synod) (Measures)</BusinessItemHeadingNumbered>
<DebateTimingRubric>No debate<SOReference> (Standing Order No. 118(6))</SOReference></DebateTimingRubric>
<MotionSponsor>Andrew Selous</MotionSponsor>
<MotionText><from_cdata><p class="MsoNormal">That the Church of England Pensions (Application of Capital Funds) Measure (HC 342), passed by the General Synod of the Church of England, be presented to His Majesty for his Royal Assent in the form in which it was laid before Parliament.</p></from_cdata></MotionText>
<NoteHeading>Notes:</NoteHeading>
<NoteText><from_cdata><p class="MsoListParagraph" style="text-indent: -18.0pt; mso-list: l0 level1 lfo1;">If this item is opposed after 7.00pm, the division will be deferred.</p></from_cdata></NoteText>
<NoteHeading>Relevant Documents:</NoteHeading>
<NoteText><from_cdata><p><span class="TextRun SCXW245436758 BCX0" style="margin: 0px; padding: 0px; user-select: text; -webkit-user-drag: none; -webkit-tap-highlight-color: transparent; text-indent: 48px; white-space-collapse: preserve; font-size: 11pt; line-height: 19.425px; font-family: Calibri, Calibri_EmbeddedFont, Calibri_MSFontService, sans-serif; font-variant-ligatures: none !important;" data-contrast="auto"><span class="NormalTextRun SpellingErrorV2Themed SCXW245436758 BCX0" style="margin: 0px; padding: 0px; user-select: text; -webkit-user-drag: none; -webkit-tap-highlight-color: transparent; background-repeat: repeat-x; background-position: left bottom; background-image: var(--urlSpellingErrorV2, ); border-bottom: 1px solid transparent;">245th</span><span class="NormalTextRun SCXW245436758 BCX0" style="margin: 0px; padding: 0px; user-select: text; -webkit-user-drag: none; -webkit-tap-highlight-color: transparent;"> Report of the Ecclesiastical Committee, HC 340</span></span></p></from_cdata></NoteText>
<OPHeading2>Presentation of Public Petitions</OPHeading2>
<DebateTimingRubric>No debate or decision <SOReference>(Standing Order No. 153)</SOReference></DebateTimingRubric>
<MotionText>Ceasefire in Gaza: <PresenterSponsor>Afzal Khan</PresenterSponsor></MotionText>
<OPHeading2>Adjournment Debate</OPHeading2>
<DebateTimingRubric>Until 7.30pm or for half an hour (whichever is later)<SOReference> (Standing Order No. 9(7))</SOReference></DebateTimingRubric>
<MotionText>Parliamentary scrutiny of nuclear defence infrastructure: <PresenterSponsor>Martin Docherty-Hughes</PresenterSponsor></MotionText>
<OPHeading1>Business Today: Westminster Hall</OPHeading1>
<OPHeading2>Order of Business</OPHeading2>
<DebateTimingRubric>The first part of the sitting will last for two hours. The second part of the sitting will last for three hours (Standing Order No. 10(1)).</DebateTimingRubric>
<DebateTimingRubric>9.30am</DebateTimingRubric>
<MotionText>That this House has considered legal protections for hedgerows: <PresenterSponsor>Selaine Saxby</PresenterSponsor></MotionText>
<DebateTimingRubric>11.00am</DebateTimingRubric>
<MotionText>That this House has considered the availability of books in primary schools: <PresenterSponsor>Gill Furniss</PresenterSponsor></MotionText>
<NoteHeading>Notes:</NoteHeading>
<NoteText><from_cdata><p>The sitting will be suspended from 11.30am to 2.30pm.</p></from_cdata></NoteText>
<DebateTimingRubric>2.30pm</DebateTimingRubric>
<MotionText>That this House has considered the UK response to international human rights abuses: <PresenterSponsor>Sarah Owen</PresenterSponsor></MotionText>
<DebateTimingRubric>4.00pm</DebateTimingRubric>
<MotionText>That this House has considered the matter of mentoring: <PresenterSponsor>Dr Lisa Cameron</PresenterSponsor></MotionText>
<DebateTimingRubric>4.30pm</DebateTimingRubric>
<MotionText>That this House has considered the implementation of the Shared Rural Network: <PresenterSponsor>Helen Morgan</PresenterSponsor></MotionText>
<NoteHeading>Notes:</NoteHeading>
<NoteText><from_cdata><p><span style="color: #333333; font-family: 'helvetica neue', Helvetica, Arial, sans-serif; font-size: 14px;"><span style="color: #333333; font-family: 'helvetica neue', Helvetica, Arial, sans-serif;"><span style="font-size: 14px;">The debate at 4.30pm will last for up to an hour.</span></span></span></p>
<p><span style="color: #333333; font-family: 'helvetica neue', Helvetica, Arial, sans-serif; font-size: 14px;">The sitting will be suspended and time added if divisions take place in the main Chamber (Standing Order No. 10(3)).</span></p></from_cdata></NoteText>
<OPHeading1>Written Statements</OPHeading1>
<OPHeading2>Statements to be Made Today</OPHeading2>
<MotionCrossHeading>Secretary of State for Business and Trade</MotionCrossHeading>
<MinisterialStatement>Government response to the consultation &#8216;smarter regulation: improving price transparency and product information for consumers&#8217; </MinisterialStatement>
<MinisterialStatement>Product Safety and Metrology etc. (Amendment) Regulations 2024</MinisterialStatement>
<MotionCrossHeading>Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport</MotionCrossHeading>
<MinisterialStatement>Media Update </MinisterialStatement>
<MotionCrossHeading>Secretary of State for Levelling Up, Housing and Communities</MotionCrossHeading>
<MinisterialStatement>Local Government Finance Update</MinisterialStatement>
<MotionCrossHeading>Secretary of State for the Home Department</MotionCrossHeading>
<MinisterialStatement>2022/23 Annual Report of the Biometrics and Surveillance Camera Commissioner</MinisterialStatement>
<MinisterialStatement>Alcohol Licensing &#8211; Age Verification: Digital identity, technology and remote sales &#8211; Consultation on amending the Licensing Act</MinisterialStatement>
<NoteHeading>Notes:</NoteHeading>
<NoteText>Texts of Written Statements are available from the Vote Office and on the internet at https://questions-statements.parliament.uk/ .</NoteText></root>