<root><OPHeading1>Business Today: Chamber</OPHeading1>
<DebateTimingRubric>2.30pm Prayers</DebateTimingRubric>
<DebateTimingRubric>Followed by</DebateTimingRubric>
<OPHeading2>Questions</OPHeading2>
<QUESTIONS/>
<OPHeading2>Urgent Questions and Statements</OPHeading2>
<DebateTimingRubric>3.30pm</DebateTimingRubric>
<BusinessItemHeadingBulleted>Urgent Questions (if any)</BusinessItemHeadingBulleted>
<BusinessItemHeadingBulleted>Ministerial Statements (if any)</BusinessItemHeadingBulleted>
<OPHeading2>Business of the Day</OPHeading2>
<BusinessItemHeadingNumbered>Finance Bill: Ways and Means</BusinessItemHeadingNumbered>
<DebateTimingRubric>Up to 45 minutes<SOReference> (Standing Order No. 52(1)(b))</SOReference></DebateTimingRubric>
<MotionSponsor>Jeremy Hunt</MotionSponsor>
<MotionText><from_cdata><p class="B1BodyCommons"><span style="mso-font-width: 100%;">That provision may be made for the electricity generator levy not to apply to new generating plant.</span></p></from_cdata></MotionText>
<Line_Interstitial> </Line_Interstitial>
<BusinessItemHeadingNumbered>Finance Bill: Remaining Stages</BusinessItemHeadingNumbered>
<DebateTimingRubric>Until 10.00pm (Order of 13 December 2023)</DebateTimingRubric>
<MotionText><from_cdata>Not amended in Committee and Public Bill Committee, to be considered.</from_cdata></MotionText>
<NoteHeading>Notes:</NoteHeading>
<NoteText><from_cdata><p>For amendments, see separate paper (also available on the publications webpage for the Bill). Proceedings on Consideration will (so far as not previously concluded) be brought to a conclusion at 9.00pm; and proceedings on Third Reading will (so far as not previously concluded) be brought to a conclusion at 10.00pm (Order of 13 December 2023).</p>
<p>This Bill is expected to be certified as a Money Bill.</p></from_cdata></NoteText>
<NoteHeading>Relevant Documents:</NoteHeading>
<NoteText><from_cdata><p>Nineteenth Report of the Treasury Committee of Session 2022&#8211;23, Venture Capital, HC 134, and the Government response, HC 1876<br/>Sixteenth Report of the Treasury Committee of Session 2022&#8211;23, Tax Simplification, HC 1425, and the Government response <br/>Oral evidence taken before the Treasury Committee on 29 November 2023, on the Autumn Statement 2023, HC 286 <br/>Oral evidence taken before the Treasury Committee on the afternoon of 28 November 2023, on the Autumn Statement 2023, HC 286 <br/>Oral evidence taken before the Treasury Committee on the morning of 28 November 2023, on the Autumn Statement 2023, HC 286 <br/>Oral evidence taken before the Treasury Committee on 18 November 2023, on the Work of HMRC, HC 783 <br/>Correspondence from the Chancellor of the Exchequer to the Treasury Committee, on the Autumn Statement 2023, reported to the House on 9 January 2024 <br/>Correspondence from the Financial Secretary to the Treasury to the Treasury Committee, on tax simplification, reported to the House on 13 December 2023 <br/>Correspondence from the Financial Secretary to the Treasury to the Treasury Committee, on tax simplification, reported to the House on 5 September 2023</p></from_cdata></NoteText>
<Line_Interstitial> </Line_Interstitial>
<BusinessItemHeadingNumbered>Local Government</BusinessItemHeadingNumbered>
<DebateTimingRubric>No debate<SOReference> (Standing Order No. 118(6))</SOReference></DebateTimingRubric>
<MotionSponsor>Jacob Young</MotionSponsor>
<MotionText><from_cdata>That the draft Combined Authorities (Mayoral Elections) Order 2017 (Amendment) Regulations 2024,<span style="color: #333333; font-family: Arial, Verdana, sans-serif; font-size: 14px;"> </span>which were laid before this House on 11 December 2023, be approved.</from_cdata></MotionText>
<NoteHeading>Notes:</NoteHeading>
<NoteText><from_cdata><p>If this item is opposed after 10.00pm, the division will be deferred.</p></from_cdata></NoteText>
<Line_Interstitial> </Line_Interstitial>
<BusinessItemHeadingNumbered>Local Government</BusinessItemHeadingNumbered>
<DebateTimingRubric>No debate<SOReference> (Standing Order No. 118(6))</SOReference></DebateTimingRubric>
<MotionSponsor>Jacob Young</MotionSponsor>
<MotionText><from_cdata>That the draft Combined Authorities (Mayors) Filling of Vacancies Order 2017 (Amendment) Regulations 2024,<span style="color: #333333; font-family: Arial, Verdana, sans-serif; font-size: 14px;"> </span>which were laid before this House on 11 December 2023, be approved.</from_cdata></MotionText>
<NoteHeading>Notes:</NoteHeading>
<NoteText><from_cdata><p>If this item is opposed after 10.00pm, the division will be deferred.</p></from_cdata></NoteText>
<Line_Interstitial> </Line_Interstitial>
<BusinessItemHeadingNumbered>Animals</BusinessItemHeadingNumbered>
<DebateTimingRubric>No debate<SOReference> (Standing Order No. 118(6))</SOReference></DebateTimingRubric>
<MotionSponsor>Steve Barclay</MotionSponsor>
<MotionText><from_cdata>That the draft Animal Welfare (Primate Licences) (England) Regulations 2023, which were laid before this House on 14 December 2023, be approved.</from_cdata></MotionText>
<NoteHeading>Notes:</NoteHeading>
<NoteText><from_cdata><p>If this item is opposed after 10.00pm, the division will be deferred.</p></from_cdata></NoteText>
<Line_Interstitial> </Line_Interstitial>
<BusinessItemHeadingNumbered>BUSINESS OF THE HOUSE (7 FEBRUARY)</BusinessItemHeadingNumbered>
<DebateTimingRubric>No debate after 10.00pm<SOReference> (Standing Order No. 9(6))</SOReference></DebateTimingRubric>
<MotionSponsor>Penny Mordaunt</MotionSponsor>
<MotionText><from_cdata>That at the sitting on Wednesday 7 February, notwithstanding the provisions of Standing Order No. 16 (Proceedings under an Act or on European Union documents), the Speaker shall put the Questions necessary to dispose of proceedings on 
(1) the Motion in the name of Secretary James Cleverly relating to Police Grant Report not later than three hours after the commencement of proceedings on that Motion, and 
(2) the Motions in the name of Secretary Michael Gove relating to Local Government Finance not later than three hours after the commencement of proceedings on the first such Motion or six hours after the commencement of proceedings relating to Police Grant Report, whichever is the later; 
proceedings on those Motions may continue, though opposed, after the moment of interruption; and Standing Order No. 41A (Deferred divisions) shall not apply.</from_cdata></MotionText>
<OPHeading2>Adjournment Debate</OPHeading2>
<DebateTimingRubric>Until 10.30pm or for half an hour (whichever is later)<SOReference> (Standing Order No. 9(7))</SOReference></DebateTimingRubric>
<MotionText>Tri-service safety officers in Devon and Cornwall: <PresenterSponsor>Steve Double</PresenterSponsor></MotionText>
<OPHeading1>Business Today: Westminster Hall</OPHeading1>
<MotionText><from_cdata>Westminster Hall will not be sitting.</from_cdata></MotionText>: 
<OPHeading1>Written Statements</OPHeading1>
<OPHeading2>Statements to be Made Today</OPHeading2>
<MotionCrossHeading>Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport</MotionCrossHeading>
<MinisterialStatement>Update on the Sports Grounds Safety Authority licence fee</MinisterialStatement>
<MotionCrossHeading>Secretary of State for Levelling Up, Housing and Communities</MotionCrossHeading>
<MinisterialStatement>Local Government Finance Update</MinisterialStatement>
<MotionCrossHeading>Secretary of State for Health and Social Care</MotionCrossHeading>
<MinisterialStatement>Local authority funding update</MinisterialStatement>
<MotionCrossHeading>Secretary of State for the Home Department</MotionCrossHeading>
<MinisterialStatement>Protect Duty update</MinisterialStatement>
<MotionCrossHeading>Secretary of State for Work and Pensions</MotionCrossHeading>
<MinisterialStatement>Publication of the Disability Action Plan</MinisterialStatement>
<NoteHeading>Notes:</NoteHeading>
<NoteText>Texts of Written Statements are available from the Vote Office and on the internet at https://questions-statements.parliament.uk/ .</NoteText></root>