<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<root><Heading4>Questions for Answer on Wednesday 22 May</Heading4> <Heading5>Questions for Written Answer</Heading5> <WQuestionRestart><memberName>Sir Chris Bryant</memberName> (Rhondda): To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the cost to the public purse is of the Great Futures programme in Saudi Arabia.	⁣<Transfer>[Transferred] </Transfer><UIN>(26972)</UIN></WQuestionRestart> <WQuestion><memberName>Damien Moore</memberName> (Southport): To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what steps the Government is taking to support independent jewellers in Southport constituency.	⁣<Transfer>[Transferred] </Transfer><UIN>(27140)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Andrew Rosindell</memberName> (Romford): To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department is taking to support Scouting and Girlguiding in the British Overseas Territories.	⁣<Transfer>[Transferred] </Transfer><UIN>(26979)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Julian Knight</memberName> (Solihull): To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many staff have left Ofqual in each year since its creation.	⁣<Transfer>[Transferred] </Transfer><UIN>(27070)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Daisy Cooper</memberName> (St Albans): To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the Seventh Report of the Environment, Food and Rural Affairs Committee of Session 2022-23 on Food Security, HC622, published on 28 July 2023, whether he has undertaken a comprehensive review of Departmental responsibilities and structures on food policy.	⁣<Transfer>[Transferred] </Transfer><UIN>(27206)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Mark Pritchard</memberName> (The Wrekin): To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will take enforcement action against UK-based retailers that are selling imported electric scooters which perform at road speeds beyond the permitted limits.	⁣<Transfer>[Transferred] </Transfer><UIN>(27001)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Sir Robert Buckland</memberName> (South Swindon): To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if she will make an estimate of the number and proportion of working-aged adults that have not received adult social care following an approach to their local authority in the last 12 months.	⁣<Transfer>[Transferred] </Transfer><UIN>(27034)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Chloe Smith</memberName> (Norwich North): To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what his planned timetable is to commence payment of compensation for firefighter pension arrears in accordance with the firefighter pension scheme immediate detriment framework of March 2023.	⁣<Transfer>[Transferred] </Transfer><UIN>(27005)</UIN></WQuestion> <Heading4>Questions for Answer on Thursday 23 May</Heading4> <Heading5>Questions for Written Answer</Heading5> <WQuestionRestart><memberName>Rachael Maskell</memberName> (York Central): To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps he is taking to (a) monitor and (b) manage risk across the public sector.	⁣<UIN>(27413)</UIN></WQuestionRestart> <WQuestion><memberName>Rachael Maskell</memberName> (York Central): To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will establish a representative panel consisting of (a) victims and (b) victims' families to scruitnise the contaminated blood compensation scheme.	⁣<UIN>(27414)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Rachael Maskell</memberName> (York Central): To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps he is taking to ensure public accountability for decision making in government.	⁣<UIN>(27415)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Rachael Maskell</memberName> (York Central): To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps the Government has taken to (a) understand the potential risk of and (b) prevent future health system failures similar to those that led to the infected blood scandal.	⁣<UIN>(27416)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Steve McCabe</memberName> (Birmingham, Selly Oak): To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 19 March 2024 to Question 18033 on Civil Servants: Veterans, if he will make an estimate of the number of veterans from minority ethnic backgrounds that were employed through the Great Place to Work for Veterans scheme in the last 12 months.	⁣<UIN>(27241)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Steve McCabe</memberName> (Birmingham, Selly Oak): To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 1 March 2024 to Question 15550 on Civil Servants: Veterans, if he will make an estimate of the number of veterans that were employed through the Great Place to Work for Veterans initiative in the West Midlands in the last 12 months.	⁣<UIN>(27242)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Dr Matthew Offord</memberName> (Hendon): To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that every family who lost a relative from infected blood is compensated.	⁣<UIN>(27337)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Dr Matthew Offord</memberName> (Hendon): To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether it is his policy to ensure that interim payments are made to those who have been affected by infected blood.	⁣<UIN>(27338)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Caroline Ansell</memberName> (Eastbourne): To ask the Member for South West Bedfordshire, representing the Church Commissioners, whether the Church of England has had discussions with the Clewer Initiative on tackling modern slavery in the last 12 months.	⁣<UIN>(27522)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Caroline Ansell</memberName> (Eastbourne): To ask the Member for South West Bedfordshire, representing the Church Commissioners, whether the Church of England has had discussions with the Clewer Initiative on the impact of its funding on its work; and whether the Church is taking steps to support the Clewer Initiative.	⁣<UIN>(27523)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Caroline Ansell</memberName> (Eastbourne): To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, whether she has made an assessment of the potential merits of increasing Government (a) financial and (b) other support for people looking to open new nurseries.	⁣<UIN>(27478)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Deidre Brock</memberName> (Edinburgh North and Leith): To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, if she will make an estimate of the total annual cost to UK businesses of completing customs declarations on trade across the EU-GB border, in each year since the UK left the EU.	⁣<UIN>(27404)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Fabian Hamilton</memberName> (Leeds North East): To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, whether she plans to implement tariffs on vehicles produced in China.	⁣<UIN>(27286)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Sir John Hayes</memberName> (South Holland and The Deepings): To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what the cost to the public purse of staff diversity networks in her Department was in each of the last five years.	⁣<UIN>(27268)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Sir John Hayes</memberName> (South Holland and The Deepings): To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, whether Ministers in her Department have met representatives of Black Lives Matter UK in the last five years.	⁣<UIN>(27269)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Mrs Pauline Latham</memberName> (Mid Derbyshire): To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what steps she is taking to strengthen the UK supply chain in the production of lithium-ion batteries.	⁣<UIN>(27339)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Mrs Pauline Latham</memberName> (Mid Derbyshire): To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what steps she is taking to encourage cathode active material producers to the UK.	⁣<UIN>(27340)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Mrs Pauline Latham</memberName> (Mid Derbyshire): To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what steps she is taking to encourage rare earth magnet producers to the UK.	⁣<UIN>(27341)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Mrs Pauline Latham</memberName> (Mid Derbyshire): To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of the UK’s domestic critical mineral capacity.	⁣<UIN>(27342)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Mrs Pauline Latham</memberName> (Mid Derbyshire): To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, which nations she has pursued critical mineral agreements with.	⁣<UIN>(27343)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Dr Matthew Offord</memberName> (Hendon): To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, how many times the Prime Minister’s Trade Envoy for Sri Lanka has visited Sri Lanka in the last 12 months.	⁣<UIN>(27333)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Dr Matthew Offord</memberName> (Hendon): To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what areas of the economy the Prime Minister’s Trade Envoy for Sri Lanka has promoted during his tenure.	⁣<UIN>(27334)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Dr Matthew Offord</memberName> (Hendon): To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what estimate her Department has made of the trade generated by the Prime Minister’s Trade Envoy for Sri Lanka since his appointment.	⁣<UIN>(27335)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Sir John Hayes</memberName> (South Holland and The Deepings): To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what her Department's policy is on Ministerial clearance of contracts relating to external equality, diversity and inclusion providers.	⁣<UIN>(27262)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Stephen Morgan</memberName> (Portsmouth South): To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether her Department plans to take steps to monitor secondary ticketing practices.	⁣<UIN>(27500)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Stephen Morgan</memberName> (Portsmouth South): To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether she plans to respond to the APPG on Music report entitled Artificial Intelligence and the Music Industry- Master or Servant, published on 1 May 2024.	⁣<UIN>(27502)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Stephanie Peacock</memberName> (Barnsley East): To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if she will make an assessment of the effectiveness of research, prevention and treatment commissioning when the statutory gambling levy is in place; and if she will make it her policy to publish (a) that assessment and (b) recommendations to improve the system.	⁣<UIN>(27555)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Stephanie Peacock</memberName> (Barnsley East): To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to the article by the Gambling Commission entitled Evaluating the impact of the Gambling Act Review, published on 19 March 2024, what the framework developed by the National Centre for Social Research for process and impact evaluations of the review of the Gambling Act 2005 will include.	⁣<UIN>(27556)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Feryal Clark</memberName> (Enfield North): To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many schools have reinforced autoclaved aerated concrete (RAAC) in Enfield North constituency.	⁣<UIN>(27447)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Feryal Clark</memberName> (Enfield North): To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what her planned timetable is for completing reinforced autoclaved aerated concrete (RAAC) remedial works in schools in Enfield North constituency.	⁣<UIN>(27448)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Feryal Clark</memberName> (Enfield North): To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to support schools with reinforced autoclaved aerated concrete (RAAC) in Enfield North constituency.	⁣<UIN>(27449)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Sir David Evennett</memberName> (Bexleyheath and Crayford): To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to help support children with special educational needs in the London Borough of Bexley.	⁣<UIN>(27291)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Wera Hobhouse</memberName> (Bath): To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what information her Department holds on the number of (a) students that studied texts by female authors and (b) female authors included in exam board syllabi for GCSE English Literature.	⁣<UIN>(27540)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Julian Knight</memberName> (Solihull): To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many staff have left the Office for Students in each year since its creation.	⁣<UIN>(27385)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Julian Knight</memberName> (Solihull): To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many staff have left the Office of the Children's Commissioner in each year since 2015.	⁣<UIN>(27386)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Julian Knight</memberName> (Solihull): To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many staff have left Social Work England in each year since its creation.	⁣<UIN>(27387)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Julian Knight</memberName> (Solihull): To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many staff have left the Student Loans Company in each year since 2015.	⁣<UIN>(27388)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Julian Knight</memberName> (Solihull): To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many staff have left the School Teachers' Review Body in each year since 2015.	⁣<UIN>(27389)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Julian Knight</memberName> (Solihull): To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many staff have left the Child Safeguarding Practice Review Panel in each year since its creation.	⁣<UIN>(27390)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Julian Knight</memberName> (Solihull): To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many staff have left the Independent Review Mechanism in each year since its creation.	⁣<UIN>(27391)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Julian Knight</memberName> (Solihull): To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many staff have left the Office of the Schools Adjudicator in each year since its creation.	⁣<UIN>(27392)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Rachael Maskell</memberName> (York Central): To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what guidance her Department provides to schools on engaging with parents of children of (a) primary and (b) secondary school age in the event that there is persistent absence or school refusal.	⁣<UIN>(27417)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Rachael Maskell</memberName> (York Central): To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether she has made a comparative assessment of the impact of (a) integrating SEND children in mainstream schools and (b) sending SEND children to specialised schools on the (i) educational outcomes and (ii) general wellbeing of those children.	⁣<UIN>(27418)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Rachael Maskell</memberName> (York Central): To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether her Department takes steps to monitor levels of parental engagement in schools.	⁣<UIN>(27419)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Rachael Maskell</memberName> (York Central): To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will make an assessment of the Swedish model of providing mother tongue lessons to children of new communities as they migrate into mainstream classes.	⁣<UIN>(27420)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Jim Shannon</memberName> (Strangford): To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment she has made of the adequacy of student accommodation.	⁣<UIN>(27365)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Feryal Clark</memberName> (Enfield North): To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what recent assessment she has made of the adequacy of the professional skills of certified installers for the microgeneration certification scheme under the Domestic Renewable Heat Incentive.	⁣<UIN>(27432)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Feryal Clark</memberName> (Enfield North): To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what support is available for people (a) during and (b) after installation of heat pumps through the microgeneration certification scheme under the Domestic Renewable Heat Incentive in cases in which the installers are no longer able to (i) complete installation and (ii) provide post-installation support.	⁣<UIN>(27433)</UIN></WQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Virginia Crosbie</memberName> (Ynys Môn): To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, whether she has taken steps with the Chancellor of the Exchequer to increase the offshore wind capacity delivered in the Contracts for Difference Allocation Round 6 compared to Allocation Round 5.	⁣<Transfer>[Transferred] </Transfer><UIN>(27162)</UIN></NQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi</memberName> (Slough): To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, whether her Department (a) is taking and (b) plans to take steps to encourage the use of balcony solar in urban environments.	⁣<UIN>(27526)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi</memberName> (Slough): To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what assessment her Department has made of the potential effectiveness of vehicle-to-grid technology.	⁣<UIN>(27527)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi</memberName> (Slough): To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what progress her Department has made on the installation of large-scale battery storage facilities across the UK.	⁣<UIN>(27528)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Wera Hobhouse</memberName> (Bath): To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what estimate she has made of the number of full-time permanent staff required for Great British Nuclear to fulfill its remit; how many and what proportion of that number has been recruited as of 21 May 2024; and what estimate she has made of the date by which Great British Nuclear will be fully staffed by permanent employees.	⁣<UIN>(27481)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Julian Knight</memberName> (Solihull): To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, how many staff have left Ofgem in each year since 2015.	⁣<UIN>(27393)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Julian Knight</memberName> (Solihull): To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, how many staff have left the Civil Nuclear Police Authority in each year since 2015.	⁣<UIN>(27394)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Julian Knight</memberName> (Solihull): To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, how many staff have left the Coal Authority in each year since 2015.	⁣<UIN>(27395)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Julian Knight</memberName> (Solihull): To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, how many staff have left the Committee on Climate Change in each year since its creation.	⁣<UIN>(27396)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Julian Knight</memberName> (Solihull): To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, how many staff have left Great British Nuclear in each year since its creation.	⁣<UIN>(27397)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Julian Knight</memberName> (Solihull): To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, how many staff have left the North Sea Transition Authority staff in each year since its creation.	⁣<UIN>(27398)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Julian Knight</memberName> (Solihull): To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, how many staff have left the Nuclear Decommissioning Authority in each year since 2015.	⁣<UIN>(27399)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Julian Knight</memberName> (Solihull): To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, how many staff have left Salix Finance Ltd in each year since 2015.	⁣<UIN>(27400)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Julian Knight</memberName> (Solihull): To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, how many staff have left the UK Atomic Energy Authority in each year since 2015.	⁣<UIN>(27401)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Julian Knight</memberName> (Solihull): To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, how many staff have left the Committee on Fuel Poverty in each year since its creation.	⁣<UIN>(27402)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Julian Knight</memberName> (Solihull): To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, how many staff have left the Committee on Radioactive Waste Management in each year since its creation.	⁣<UIN>(27403)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Rachel Maclean</memberName> (Redditch): To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, when she plans to publish a strategic roadmap for solar.	⁣<UIN>(27533)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Angus Brendan MacNeil</memberName> (Na h-Eileanan an Iar): To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what assessment her Department has made of the potential impact of shared ground loops on the decarbonisation of domestic heating; and if she will take steps to improve the design of heat network (a) zoning and (b) regulation to support these heat networks.	⁣<UIN>(27308)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Tim Farron</memberName> (Westmorland and Lonsdale): To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the Answer of 22 June 2023 to Question 188226 on Water Companies, how many (a) cautions, (b) prosecutions and (c) legal instruments the Drinking Water Inspectorate brought against water companies in each year since 2021 by water company.	⁣<UIN>(27313)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Tim Farron</memberName> (Westmorland and Lonsdale): To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 17 May 2024 to Question 25464, whether her Department has plans in place to move from a rapid response to a management phase for the Asian hornet, in the context of their growing presence in the UK.	⁣<UIN>(27314)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Sir John Hayes</memberName> (South Holland and The Deepings): To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent steps he has taken to help tackle waste crime in rural areas.	⁣<UIN>(27267)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Stephen Morgan</memberName> (Portsmouth South): To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will undertake an environmental impact assessment of Southern Water’s decision to respond to increased rainfall by improving surface water drainage.	⁣<UIN>(27503)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Stephen Morgan</memberName> (Portsmouth South): To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will undertake an environmental impact assessment of Southern Waters policy on sewage discharges into (a) Langstone Harbour and (b) the Solent.	⁣<UIN>(27504)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Andrew Rosindell</memberName> (Romford): To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will take steps to bring forward legislative proposals to restrict the planting of monopodial bamboo.	⁣<UIN>(27300)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Andrew Selous</memberName> (South West Bedfordshire): To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to SB6 of the Countryside Stewardship Higher Tier (Rhododendron Control), how many agreements have been reached to date; how many hectares are covered by those agreements; and how many hectares has rhododendron successfully been removed from.	⁣<UIN>(27301)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Andrew Selous</memberName> (South West Bedfordshire): To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the SB6 Countryside Stewardship Higher Tier grant for rhododendron control.	⁣<UIN>(27302)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Jim Shannon</memberName> (Strangford): To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much funding has been allocated to each of the devolved institutions to help tackle flooding in the last 12 months.	⁣<UIN>(27366)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Mike Amesbury</memberName> (Weaver Vale): To ask the Secretary of State for Levelling Up, Housing and Communities, whether he plans to continue funding for the Rough Sleeping Initiative after 2025.	⁣<UIN>(27496)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Mike Amesbury</memberName> (Weaver Vale): To ask the Secretary of State for Levelling Up, Housing and Communities, if he will make an assessment of the potential impact of extending the move-on period from 28 to 56 days for refugees leaving asylum support on homelessness.	⁣<UIN>(27509)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Mike Amesbury</memberName> (Weaver Vale): To ask the Secretary of State for Levelling Up, Housing and Communities, whether he is taking steps with Cabinet colleagues to work across Departments on supporting people with multiple complex needs who are homeless; and what steps he is taking to support such people out of homelessness.	⁣<UIN>(27513)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Louise Haigh</memberName> (Sheffield, Heeley): To ask the Secretary of State for Levelling Up, Housing and Communities, when he will publish the outcome of his Department's consultation entitled Private parking code of practice: call for evidence, which closed on 8 October 2023.	⁣<UIN>(27425)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Louise Haigh</memberName> (Sheffield, Heeley): To ask the Secretary of State for Levelling Up, Housing and Communities, what steps he is taking with representatives of the private parking industry to regulate parking fines.	⁣<UIN>(27426)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Louise Haigh</memberName> (Sheffield, Heeley): To ask the Secretary of State for Levelling Up, Housing and Communities, when he plans to publish the private parking code of practice.	⁣<UIN>(27427)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Damien Moore</memberName> (Southport): To ask the Secretary of State for Levelling Up, Housing and Communities, what guidance his Department has issued to local authorities on the construction of homes on (a) flood plains and (b) arable farmland.	⁣<UIN>(27548)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Wendy Morton</memberName> (Aldridge-Brownhills): To ask the Secretary of State for Levelling Up, Housing and Communities, when his Department will respond to its consultation entitled Modern leasehold: restricting ground rent for existing leases, published on 6 December 2023.	⁣<UIN>(27374)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Wendy Morton</memberName> (Aldridge-Brownhills): To ask the Secretary of State for Levelling Up, Housing and Communities, what steps he is taking to help improve the take-up of commonhold as an alternative to leasehold ownership.	⁣<UIN>(27375)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Wendy Morton</memberName> (Aldridge-Brownhills): To ask the Secretary of State for Levelling Up, Housing and Communities, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of extending the ban on new leasehold houses to flats.	⁣<UIN>(27376)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Charlotte Nichols</memberName> (Warrington North): To ask the Secretary of State for Levelling Up, Housing and Communities, whether he plans to create an independent regulator for parking charge notices.	⁣<UIN>(27510)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Jim Shannon</memberName> (Strangford): To ask the Secretary of State for Levelling Up, Housing and Communities, what recent discussions he has had with the Northern Ireland Communities Minister on the sustainability of social housing in Northern Ireland.	⁣<UIN>(27368)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Mr Virendra Sharma</memberName> (Ealing, Southall): To ask the Secretary of State for Levelling Up, Housing and Communities, what recent discussions he has had with (a) HM Treasure and (b) the Prime Minister's Office on the local government funding settlement.	⁣<UIN>(27321)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Mr Virendra Sharma</memberName> (Ealing, Southall): To ask the Secretary of State for Levelling Up, Housing and Communities, what assessment he has made of the budgetary capacity of local authorities to deliver pay awards in line with inflation.	⁣<UIN>(27322)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Mr Virendra Sharma</memberName> (Ealing, Southall): To ask the Secretary of State for Levelling Up, Housing and Communities, whether his Department has made an assessment of the adequacy of local services outsourced by local authorities.	⁣<UIN>(27323)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Mr Virendra Sharma</memberName> (Ealing, Southall): To ask the Secretary of State for Levelling Up, Housing and Communities, what assessment his Department has made of the potential impact of local authority funding changes on hospital discharge times to social care.	⁣<UIN>(27324)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Cat Smith</memberName> (Lancaster and Fleetwood): To ask the Secretary of State for Levelling Up, Housing and Communities, pursuant to the Answer of 20 May 2024 to Question 25652 on Local Government: Elections, if he will survey returning officers on the number of completed postal vote packs that arrived with the returning officer after the close of polls on 2 May 2024.	⁣<UIN>(27406)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Sir Peter Bottomley</memberName> (Worthing West): To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what steps her Department is taking to help support scientists to transition to animal-free, human-specific technologies through (a) practical support, (b) the provision of training and (c) other means.	⁣<UIN>(27237)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Sir Peter Bottomley</memberName> (Worthing West): To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of hosting a global summit on human-specific technologies for scientists and policymakers to discuss the transition to these methodologies.	⁣<UIN>(27238)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Dean Russell</memberName> (Watford): To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of amending the Data Protection and Digital Information Bill to extend the list of cookie exemptions to include (a) advertising performance and (b) audience measurement cookies.	⁣<UIN>(27464)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Daisy Cooper</memberName> (St Albans): To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 1 May 2024 to Question 23803 on Aviation: South East, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the progress made by Heathrow Airport in meeting the Future Airspace Strategy Implementation South change deadlines.	⁣<UIN>(27542)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi</memberName> (Slough): To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the number of electric vehicles with vehicle-to-grid technology that will be on the road in (a) Slough, (b) London and (c) the UK by 2030.	⁣<UIN>(27530)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Ben Everitt</memberName> (Milton Keynes North): To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what enforcement action can the DVLA take against untaxed vehicles parked on roads for business purposes; and what resources are available for this action in Milton Keynes.	⁣<UIN>(27547)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Nick Fletcher</memberName> (Don Valley): To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to help ensure that cycle lanes are not a danger to (a) visually impaired and (b) blind pedestrians.	⁣<UIN>(27534)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Mary Kelly Foy</memberName> (City of Durham): To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what criteria his Department used to assess applications to the Safer Roads Fund.	⁣<UIN>(27475)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Sir John Hayes</memberName> (South Holland and The Deepings): To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the cost to the public purse was of staff diversity networks in his Department in each of the last five years.	⁣<UIN>(27263)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Grahame Morris</memberName> (Easington): To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether Network Rail requires its contractors and suppliers to limit the use of zero hours contracts.	⁣<UIN>(27330)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Mike Amesbury</memberName> (Weaver Vale): To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make an assessment of the potential impact of taper rates for (a) housing benefit and (b) Universal Credit housing elements on people in temporary accommodation.	⁣<UIN>(27512)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Caroline Ansell</memberName> (Eastbourne): To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make an assessment of the potential impact of changes to the State Pension age for women born in the 1950s on those women in Eastbourne constituency.	⁣<UIN>(27476)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Caroline Ansell</memberName> (Eastbourne): To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of universal credit claimants are parents of a child with special educational needs in (a) the UK and (b) Eastbourne constituency.	⁣<UIN>(27520)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Caroline Ansell</memberName> (Eastbourne): To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of parents of children with special educational needs have returned to work due to the provision of Universal Credit in (a) Eastbourne constituency and (b) East Sussex over the most recent 12 months for which data is available.	⁣<UIN>(27521)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Caroline Ansell</memberName> (Eastbourne): To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Parliamentary and Health Service Ombudsman's report entitled Women’s State Pension age: our findings on injustice and associated issues, published on 21 March 2024, what estimate the Government has made of the potential cost of providing compensation to eligible women.	⁣<UIN>(27529)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Anna Firth</memberName> (Southend West): To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make an assessment of the potential impact of changes to the State Pension age on women born in the 1950s in Southend West constituency.	⁣<UIN>(27518)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Anna Firth</memberName> (Southend West): To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Parliamentary and Health Service Ombudsman's report into women’s State Pension age changes, published on 21 March 2024, what recent discussions he has had with the Leader of the House on making parliamentary time available for a debate on financial redress by 23 July 2024.	⁣<UIN>(27519)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Vicky Foxcroft</memberName> (Lewisham, Deptford): To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department is taking to help ensure that adequate support is in place for jobseekers with (a) health conditions and (b) disabilities in the period between the end of referrals to the Work and Health Programme in Autumn 2024 and the start of Universal Support in 2025.	⁣<UIN>(27550)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Sir John Hayes</memberName> (South Holland and The Deepings): To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the cost to the public purse was of staff diversity networks in his Department in each of the last five years.	⁣<UIN>(27264)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Alison McGovern</memberName> (Wirral South): To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much was spent on (a) dedicated work coaches, (b) support elements separate to the work coaches and (c) youth hubs through his Department's Youth Offer in (i) 2021, (ii) 2022 and (c) 2023.	⁣<UIN>(27352)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Alison McGovern</memberName> (Wirral South): To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many places were (a) available and (b) taken up for the Youth Offer in (i) 2021, (ii) 2022, (iii) 2023 and (iv) 2024 as of 21 May.	⁣<UIN>(27353)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Alison McGovern</memberName> (Wirral South): To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many work coaches were employed to support young people in (a) 2021, (b) 2022 and (c) 2023.	⁣<UIN>(27354)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Alison McGovern</memberName> (Wirral South): To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many full-time equivalent work coaches were working specifically to support young people as of 21 May 2024.	⁣<UIN>(27355)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Alison McGovern</memberName> (Wirral South): To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many Youth Hubs there were in 2021.	⁣<UIN>(27356)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Alison McGovern</memberName> (Wirral South): To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many Youth Hubs there were in 2022.	⁣<UIN>(27357)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Alison McGovern</memberName> (Wirral South): To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many Youth Hubs there were in 2023.	⁣<UIN>(27358)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Alison McGovern</memberName> (Wirral South): To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many Youth Hubs there are as of 21 May 2024.	⁣<UIN>(27359)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Alison McGovern</memberName> (Wirral South): To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many (a) face-to-face, (b) remote and (c) paper-based Personal Independence Payment assessments resulted in claims being (i) awarded, (ii) disallowed and (iii) withdrawn in each financial year since 2019-20.	⁣<UIN>(27360)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Alison McGovern</memberName> (Wirral South): To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people entered employment through the people and skills strand of the European Social Fund in each year since its inception until its end.	⁣<UIN>(27361)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Alison McGovern</memberName> (Wirral South): To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average waiting time was for an initial assessment for people on the Access to Work Scheme in the last five years.	⁣<UIN>(27362)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Alison McGovern</memberName> (Wirral South): To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant the Answer of 24 April 2024 to Question 22551 on Universal Credit: Employment, what her planned timetable is for the (a) conclusion and (b) publication of the evaluation of the Additional Jobcentre Support pilot.	⁣<UIN>(27363)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Stephen Morgan</memberName> (Portsmouth South): To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Parliamentary and Health Services Ombudsman report into the changes to Women’s State Pension Age, published on 21 March 2024, if he will bring forward a response to that report before 23 July 2024.	⁣<UIN>(27497)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Stephen Morgan</memberName> (Portsmouth South): To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Parliamentary and Health Services Ombudsman report into the changes to Women’s State Pension Age, published on 21 March 2024, if he will apologise to the women impacted by the changes to state pension age in that report.	⁣<UIN>(27498)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Stephen Morgan</memberName> (Portsmouth South): To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what his Department's policy is on communicating future increases to the State Pension age to the public.	⁣<UIN>(27499)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Jim Shannon</memberName> (Strangford): To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether his Department has made an estimate of the number of women born in the 1950s who have been impacted by State Pension age changes.	⁣<UIN>(27370)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Feryal Clark</memberName> (Enfield North): To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment she has made of the potential implications for her policies of the Care Quality Commission's inspection report on North Middlesex University Hospital NHS Trust, published on 28 March 2024.	⁣<UIN>(27436)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Feryal Clark</memberName> (Enfield North): To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans her Department has to improve the Care Quality Commission rating of North Middlesex University Hospital.	⁣<UIN>(27437)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Feryal Clark</memberName> (Enfield North): To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions her Department has had with North Middlesex University Hospital on their Care Quality Commission report, published on 28 March 2024.	⁣<UIN>(27438)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Feryal Clark</memberName> (Enfield North): To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how her Department plans to support North Middlesex University Hospital on the areas of the improvement listed in their Care Quality Commission report, published on 28 March 2024.	⁣<UIN>(27439)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Feryal Clark</memberName> (Enfield North): To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of GP provision in Enfield North constituency.	⁣<UIN>(27440)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Feryal Clark</memberName> (Enfield North): To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many full-time equivalent GPs are working in Enfield North constituency as of 21 May 2024.	⁣<UIN>(27441)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Feryal Clark</memberName> (Enfield North): To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps her Department is taking to help grow the GP workforce in Enfield North constituency.	⁣<UIN>(27442)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Feryal Clark</memberName> (Enfield North): To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if she will make an assessment of the adequacy of the GP-to-patient ratio in Enfield North constituency.	⁣<UIN>(27443)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Feryal Clark</memberName> (Enfield North): To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps her Department is taking to support the recruitment and retention of GPs in Enfield North constituency.	⁣<UIN>(27444)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Feryal Clark</memberName> (Enfield North): To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what proportion of GP surgeries are rated as good by the Care Quality Commission in Enfield North constituency.	⁣<UIN>(27445)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Feryal Clark</memberName> (Enfield North): To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether she plans to provide additional services in GP surgeries in Enfield North constituency.	⁣<UIN>(27446)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Fabian Hamilton</memberName> (Leeds North East): To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 15 May 2024 to Question 25226, on Hospices: Children, when she plans that consideration of the future of the NHS Children's Hospice Grant beyond 2024/25 will be concluded.	⁣<UIN>(27289)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Fabian Hamilton</memberName> (Leeds North East): To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer on 15 May 2024 to Question 25226 on Hospices: Children, what factors she plans to take into account when considering the future of the NHS Children's Hospice Grant beyond 2024-25.	⁣<UIN>(27290)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Rebecca Long Bailey</memberName> (Salford and Eccles): To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of providing targeted support for (a) infant and (b) parental mental health while a family is experiencing homelessness.	⁣<UIN>(27384)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Rachael Maskell</memberName> (York Central): To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if she will take steps to ensure that (a) clinical and (b) other data held by (i) the NHS and (ii) her Department is used to help identify poor clinical practice in the NHS; and if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of using (A) AI and (B) machine learning to identify such concerns.	⁣<UIN>(27412)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Rachael Maskell</memberName> (York Central): To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if she will undertake a study on trends in alcohol use among young people.	⁣<UIN>(27421)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Rachael Maskell</memberName> (York Central): To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment she has made of the (a) availability and (b) trends in the use of nicotine pouches in the last 12 months.	⁣<UIN>(27422)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Rachael Maskell</memberName> (York Central): To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if she will make an assessment of trends in the level of non-tobacco nicotine product usage in the last five years.	⁣<UIN>(27423)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Rachael Maskell</memberName> (York Central): To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if she will take legislative steps to end the marketing of all nicotine products.	⁣<UIN>(27424)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Steve McCabe</memberName> (Birmingham, Selly Oak): To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of increasing the level of mental health support provided to veterans who have addictions.	⁣<UIN>(27248)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Steve McCabe</memberName> (Birmingham, Selly Oak): To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many veterans were treated by the NHS for bipolar disorder in (a) 2018-19, (b) 2021-22 and (c) 2022-23.	⁣<UIN>(27249)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Steve McCabe</memberName> (Birmingham, Selly Oak): To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if she will make an estimate of the number of veterans that were treated by the NHS for psychosis and schizophrenia in (a) 2018-19, (b) 2021-22 and (c) 2022-23.	⁣<UIN>(27250)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Steve McCabe</memberName> (Birmingham, Selly Oak): To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if she will make an estimate of the number of veterans that were treated by the NHS for generalised anxiety disorder in (a) 2018-19, (b) 2021-22 and (c) 2022-23.	⁣<UIN>(27251)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Steve McCabe</memberName> (Birmingham, Selly Oak): To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if she will make an estimate of the number of veterans that were treated by the NHS for addiction in (a) 2018-19, (b) 2021-22 and (c) 2022-23.	⁣<UIN>(27252)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Steve McCabe</memberName> (Birmingham, Selly Oak): To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if she will make an estimate of the number of veterans that were treated by the NHS for PTSD in (a) 2018-19, (b) 2021-22 and (c) 2022-23.	⁣<UIN>(27253)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Steve McCabe</memberName> (Birmingham, Selly Oak): To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if she will make an estimate of the number of veterans that were treated by the NHS for depression in (a) 2018-19, (b) 2021-22 and (c) 2022-23.	⁣<UIN>(27254)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Sarah Owen</memberName> (Luton North): To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what data her Department holds on the proportion of funding from central Government for adult social care that has been spent on supporting people of working age with such needs in each of the last three years.	⁣<UIN>(27514)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Sarah Owen</memberName> (Luton North): To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment her department has made of the potential merits of a compulsory national register of care workers.	⁣<UIN>(27515)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Sarah Owen</memberName> (Luton North): To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether she is taking steps to encourage the standardisation of social care commissioning by local authorities.	⁣<UIN>(27516)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Sarah Owen</memberName> (Luton North): To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of access to adult social care services by people of working age.	⁣<UIN>(27517)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Will Quince</memberName> (Colchester): To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether officials in her Department have had discussions with NHS England on the potential merits of (a) renewing the national maternity safety ambition beyond 2025 and (b) extending that ambition to include reducing inequalities.	⁣<UIN>(27405)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Jim Shannon</memberName> (Strangford): To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment she has made of the adequacy of the availability of treatment for Endometriosis.	⁣<UIN>(27367)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Jim Shannon</memberName> (Strangford): To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if she will make an estimate of the number of people that have been (a) diagnosed with and (b) treated for bladder cancer in the last 12 months.	⁣<UIN>(27369)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Liz Twist</memberName> (Blaydon): To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that hospitals follow NICE guidelines on (a) suicide and (b) self-harm risk assessment (i) tools and (ii) scales.	⁣<UIN>(27544)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Sir Chris Bryant</memberName> (Rhondda): To ask the Deputy Foreign Secretary, how many Ministers attended the Great Futures conference in Riyadh, Saudi Arabia, on 14 and 15 May 2024.	⁣<UIN>(27298)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Sir Chris Bryant</memberName> (Rhondda): To ask the Deputy Foreign Secretary, which human rights issues Ministers raised with their Saudi counterparts during the Great Futures conference in Riyadh, Saudi Arabia, on 14 and 15 May 2024.	⁣<UIN>(27299)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Neil Coyle</memberName> (Bermondsey and Old Southwark): To ask the Deputy Foreign Secretary, whether he has made representations to his counterpart in the United Arab Emirates on that country's role (a) with the Rapid Support Forces and (b) in Sudan.	⁣<UIN>(27380)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Neil Coyle</memberName> (Bermondsey and Old Southwark): To ask the Deputy Foreign Secretary, what assessment he has made of the (a) role and (b) impact of (i) the Wagner Group and (ii) other Russian funded mercenary forces in Africa.	⁣<UIN>(27381)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Preet Kaur Gill</memberName> (Birmingham, Edgbaston): To ask the Deputy Foreign Secretary, what assessment he has made of the potential (a) implications for his policies of the recent insurgent attacks around (i) Macomia, (ii) Missufine and (iii) Cajerene in Mozambique and (b) impact of those attacks on the (A) displacement and (B) casualties of civilians.	⁣<UIN>(27486)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Fabian Hamilton</memberName> (Leeds North East): To ask the Deputy Foreign Secretary, what assessment he has made of the potential implications for his policies of the recent arrest of three men charged with aiding the Hong Kong Intelligence Service.	⁣<UIN>(27285)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Fabian Hamilton</memberName> (Leeds North East): To ask the Deputy Foreign Secretary, whether he has made an assessment of the implications for his policies of the news release entitled Myanmar: Military Forcibly Recruiting Rohingya, published by Human Rights Watch on 9 April 2024.	⁣<UIN>(27287)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Fabian Hamilton</memberName> (Leeds North East): To ask the Deputy Foreign Secretary, whether he has made an assessment of the implications for his policies of the impact on Brazil’s GDP of floods in the Rio Grande do Sul region.	⁣<UIN>(27288)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Afzal Khan</memberName> (Manchester, Gorton): To ask the Deputy Foreign Secretary, how much aid he has given to organisations providing humanitarian assistance in Gaza since October 2023.	⁣<UIN>(27495)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Stephen Morgan</memberName> (Portsmouth South): To ask the Deputy Foreign Secretary, what steps he is taking to help protect women in El Fasher.	⁣<UIN>(27492)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Stephen Morgan</memberName> (Portsmouth South): To ask the Deputy Foreign Secretary, whether he has made changes to the planned distribution of aid in Sudan.	⁣<UIN>(27493)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Stephen Morgan</memberName> (Portsmouth South): To ask the Deputy Foreign Secretary, what steps he is taking as the penholder on Sudan at the UN Security Council to prevent the flow of arms to the Rapid Support Forces.	⁣<UIN>(27494)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Stephen Morgan</memberName> (Portsmouth South): To ask the Deputy Foreign Secretary, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of Government legal advice on his policies in the context of Israel’s proposed military operations in Rafah.	⁣<UIN>(27505)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Stephen Morgan</memberName> (Portsmouth South): To ask the Deputy Foreign Secretary, whether he has made changes to the planned distribution of aid in Gaza.	⁣<UIN>(27506)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Stephen Morgan</memberName> (Portsmouth South): To ask the Deputy Foreign Secretary, what recent assessment he has made of the impact of Israel’s political strategy on Gaza.	⁣<UIN>(27507)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Stephen Morgan</memberName> (Portsmouth South): To ask the Deputy Foreign Secretary, whether he is taking steps to investigate reports of Israeli air strikes on refugee camps in Gaza.	⁣<UIN>(27508)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Lisa Nandy</memberName> (Wigan): To ask the Deputy Foreign Secretary, what steps his Department is taking to improve the transparency of aid.	⁣<UIN>(27346)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Lisa Nandy</memberName> (Wigan): To ask the Deputy Foreign Secretary, what steps his Department is taking to improve the transparency of aid provided by arms-length bodies.	⁣<UIN>(27347)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Lisa Nandy</memberName> (Wigan): To ask the Deputy Foreign Secretary, with reference to paragraph 4.27 of the report by the Independent Commission for Aid Impact entitled ICAI follow-up review of 2022-23 reports, published on 16 May 2024, if he will take steps to issue guidance on police reform and restricting the use of official development assistance funding for civilian policing tasks.	⁣<UIN>(27348)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Lisa Nandy</memberName> (Wigan): To ask the Deputy Foreign Secretary, what steps he is taking with regional partners to facilitate aid access to all parts of Sudan.	⁣<UIN>(27349)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Lisa Nandy</memberName> (Wigan): To ask the Deputy Foreign Secretary, what recent discussions he has had with his Israeli counterpart on ensuring safe passage of aid convoys through (a) Israel and (b) Israeli-controlled territory in Gaza.	⁣<UIN>(27350)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Lisa Nandy</memberName> (Wigan): To ask the Deputy Foreign Secretary, what recent discussions he has had with his Zimbabwean counterpart on the (a) economic and (b) humanitarian situation in that country.	⁣<UIN>(27351)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Dr Matthew Offord</memberName> (Hendon): To ask the Deputy Foreign Secretary, if he will make representations to his counterpart in Iran on stopping the execution of Arvin Nathaniel Ghahremani.	⁣<UIN>(27332)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Dr Matthew Offord</memberName> (Hendon): To ask the Deputy Foreign Secretary, what assessment his Department has made of the effectiveness of the Sri Lankan reconciliation process.	⁣<UIN>(27336)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi</memberName> (Slough): To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps his Department takes to ensure the police's use of powers at protests is compliant with human rights standards.	⁣<UIN>(27524)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Nick Fletcher</memberName> (Don Valley): To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that student visas are not used solely to gain residence in the UK.	⁣<UIN>(27539)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Louise Haigh</memberName> (Sheffield, Heeley): To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many identified victims of modern slavery in Sheffield were referred using the National Referral Mechanism in (a) 2023 and (b) 2024 to date.	⁣<UIN>(27428)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Louise Haigh</memberName> (Sheffield, Heeley): To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many victims of modern slavery were identified in south Yorkshire in (a) 2023 and (b) 2024 as of 21 May 2024.	⁣<UIN>(27429)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Louise Haigh</memberName> (Sheffield, Heeley): To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many modern slavery survivors in Sheffield had a positive conclusive grounds decision using the National Referral Mechanism in 2023.	⁣<UIN>(27430)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Louise Haigh</memberName> (Sheffield, Heeley): To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many survivors of modern slavery were identified in Sheffield in 2023, broken down by quarter.	⁣<UIN>(27431)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Louise Haigh</memberName> (Sheffield, Heeley): To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much funding his Department allocated to modern slavery first responder organisations in Sheffield in financial year 2023-24.	⁣<UIN>(27479)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Louise Haigh</memberName> (Sheffield, Heeley): To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps his Department is taking to (a) identify and (b) tackle modern slavery in Sheffield.	⁣<UIN>(27480)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Louise Haigh</memberName> (Sheffield, Heeley): To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps his Department takes to monitor modern slavery in Sheffield.	⁣<UIN>(27482)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Louise Haigh</memberName> (Sheffield, Heeley): To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people were investigated by the police on suspicion of involvement with modern slavery in 2023.	⁣<UIN>(27483)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Louise Haigh</memberName> (Sheffield, Heeley): To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many victims of (a) human trafficking, (b) labour exploitation, (c) sexual exploitation, (d) criminal exploitation and (e) domestic servitude were identified in Sheffield in (i) 2022 and (ii) 2023.	⁣<UIN>(27484)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Louise Haigh</memberName> (Sheffield, Heeley): To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much funding is provided to projects supporting victims of modern slavery in (a) Sheffield and (b) the rest of South Yorkshire.	⁣<UIN>(27485)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Louise Haigh</memberName> (Sheffield, Heeley): To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much funding has been allocated to Sheffield City Council to help support victims of modern slavery in the financial year 2023-24.	⁣<UIN>(27487)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Louise Haigh</memberName> (Sheffield, Heeley): To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, for what reason the Gangmasters and Labour Abuse Authority do not hold modern slavery data for Sheffield.	⁣<UIN>(27488)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Louise Haigh</memberName> (Sheffield, Heeley): To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many duty to notify referrals were made to his Department by the local authority in Sheffield in financial year 2023-24.	⁣<UIN>(27489)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Caroline Lucas</memberName> (Brighton, Pavilion): To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Point of Order by the hon. Member for Brighton, Pavilion of 21 May 2024 and the report entitled Protecting our Democracy from Coercion, HC 775, published on 21 May 2024, if he will amend page 1 of that report to include the registered interests of the UK Government’s independent adviser on political violence and disruption.	⁣<UIN>(27326)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Damien Moore</memberName> (Southport): To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps his Department is taking to support victims of (a) domestic abuse and (b) coercive control post-separation.	⁣<UIN>(27545)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Damien Moore</memberName> (Southport): To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will make an assessment of the potential impact of trends in the number of police officers operating visibly in communities on the number of drug-related offences recorded in the last five years.	⁣<UIN>(27546)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Wendy Morton</memberName> (Aldridge-Brownhills): To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what progress his Department has made on the surrender and compensation scheme for Zombie-style knives and machetes.	⁣<UIN>(27377)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Stephanie Peacock</memberName> (Barnsley East): To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will make an assessment of the impact of gambling-related (a) fraud and (b) other acquisitive crimes on the finances of the victims of those crimes.	⁣<UIN>(27553)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Stephanie Peacock</memberName> (Barnsley East): To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what information his Department holds on the amount of money that was returned to victims of gambling-related crimes (a) by the gambling industry, (b) through a proceeding under the Proceeds of Crime Act 2002 and (c) by any other means in the 2023-24 financial year.	⁣<UIN>(27554)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi</memberName> (Slough): To ask the hon. Member for Broxbourne, representing the House of Commons Commission, what steps the Commission is taking to ensure that security personnel employed at constituency surgeries by agencies contracted by parliamentary security are paid (a) at least the minimum wage and (b) travel expenses.	⁣<UIN>(27535)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi</memberName> (Slough): To ask the hon. Member for Broxbourne, representing the House of Commons Commission, if he will make an assessment of the adequacy of the terms and conditions of employment relating to (a) travel expenses and (b) other matters for security guards employed for hon. Members' constituency surgeries.	⁣<UIN>(27536)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi</memberName> (Slough): To ask the hon. Member for Broxbourne, representing the House of Commons Commission, how many contracted security personnel employed for constituency offices are paid below the minimum wage when travel time is included.	⁣<UIN>(27537)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Sir John Hayes</memberName> (South Holland and The Deepings): To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the cost to the public purse was of staff diversity networks in his Department in each of the last five years.	⁣<UIN>(27265)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>John Healey</memberName> (Wentworth and Dearne): To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the new Multi-Role Support Ships will be operated by the (a) Royal Navy and (b) Royal Fleet Auxiliary.	⁣<UIN>(27274)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>John Healey</memberName> (Wentworth and Dearne): To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when HMS Bulwark will next deploy.	⁣<UIN>(27276)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>John Healey</memberName> (Wentworth and Dearne): To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the out of service date is for RFA Argus.	⁣<UIN>(27277)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>John Healey</memberName> (Wentworth and Dearne): To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the out of service date is for the Royal Fleet Auxiliary’s Bay-class ships.	⁣<UIN>(27278)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>John Healey</memberName> (Wentworth and Dearne): To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to his Department's press release entitled New Golden Age of shipbuilding as new UK-built warships boost Navy building programme to up to 28 ships and submarines, published on 14 May 2024, whether the new Multi Role Support Ships will be procured via the integrated procurement model.	⁣<UIN>(27280)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>John Healey</memberName> (Wentworth and Dearne): To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to his Department's press release entitled New Golden Age of shipbuilding as new UK-built warships boost Navy building programme to up to 28 ships and submarines, published on 14 May 2024, what his expected timetable is to launch the competition for the first Multi Role Support Ship.	⁣<UIN>(27281)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>John Healey</memberName> (Wentworth and Dearne): To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to his Department's press release entitled New Golden Age of shipbuilding as new UK-built warships boost Navy building programme to up to 28 ships and submarines, published on 14 May 2024, what the expected in-service date will be for the first Multi Role Support Ship.	⁣<UIN>(27282)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>John Healey</memberName> (Wentworth and Dearne): To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to his Department's press release entitled New Golden Age of shipbuilding as new UK-built warships boost Navy building programme to up to 28 ships and submarines, published on 14 May 2024, where will the new Multi Role Support Ships be built.	⁣<UIN>(27283)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>John Healey</memberName> (Wentworth and Dearne): To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to his Department's press release entitled New Golden Age of shipbuilding as new UK-built warships boost Navy building programme to up to 28 ships and submarines, published on 14 May 2024, for how many of the new multi-role support ships has funding been allocated by his Department.	⁣<UIN>(27284)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Daniel Kawczynski</memberName> (Shrewsbury and Atcham): To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many people are being accommodated at Nesscliffe Training Camp.	⁣<UIN>(27310)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Daniel Kawczynski</memberName> (Shrewsbury and Atcham): To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will take steps to reduce the number of people being accommodated at Nesscliffe Training Camp.	⁣<UIN>(27311)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Steve McCabe</memberName> (Birmingham, Selly Oak): To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department plans to increase the (a) number and (b) frequency of the military training exercises conducted with NATO allies at army garrisons in the next twelve months.	⁣<UIN>(27255)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Steve McCabe</memberName> (Birmingham, Selly Oak): To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department plans to increase the (a) number and (b) frequency of the military training exercises conducted with non-NATO allies at army garrisons in the next twelve months.	⁣<UIN>(27256)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Steve McCabe</memberName> (Birmingham, Selly Oak): To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what progress he has made on implementation of the recommendations of the LGBT Veterans Independent Review.	⁣<UIN>(27257)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Luke Pollard</memberName> (Plymouth, Sutton and Devonport): To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department receives a payment for each export order of Type (a) 26 and (b) 31 frigate.	⁣<UIN>(27451)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Luke Pollard</memberName> (Plymouth, Sutton and Devonport): To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much his Department has received in payments for the export of the Type (a) 26 and (b) 31 frigate design since the project began.	⁣<UIN>(27452)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Luke Pollard</memberName> (Plymouth, Sutton and Devonport): To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much his Department has spent on improving service accommodation at Duchess of Kent Barracks since April 2022.	⁣<UIN>(27455)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Luke Pollard</memberName> (Plymouth, Sutton and Devonport): To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much his Department has spent on improving service accommodation at Browning Barracks since April 2022.	⁣<UIN>(27456)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Luke Pollard</memberName> (Plymouth, Sutton and Devonport): To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much his Department has spent on improving service accommodation at Thornhill Barracks since April 2022.	⁣<UIN>(27457)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Luke Pollard</memberName> (Plymouth, Sutton and Devonport): To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much his Department has spent on improving service accommodation at Provost Barracks since April 2022.	⁣<UIN>(27458)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Luke Pollard</memberName> (Plymouth, Sutton and Devonport): To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much his Department has spent on improving service accommodation at Ordnance Barracks since April 2022.	⁣<UIN>(27459)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Luke Pollard</memberName> (Plymouth, Sutton and Devonport): To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much his Department has spent on improving service accommodation at Mons Barracks since April 2022.	⁣<UIN>(27460)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Luke Pollard</memberName> (Plymouth, Sutton and Devonport): To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much his Department has spent on improving service accommodation at Lille Barracks since April 2022.	⁣<UIN>(27461)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Luke Pollard</memberName> (Plymouth, Sutton and Devonport): To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much his Department has spent on improving service accommodation at Hammersley Barracks since April 2022.	⁣<UIN>(27462)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Luke Pollard</memberName> (Plymouth, Sutton and Devonport): To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much his Department has spent on improving service accommodation at Gibraltar Barracks since April 2022.	⁣<UIN>(27463)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Luke Pollard</memberName> (Plymouth, Sutton and Devonport): To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many callouts have been made to McCullen Barracks for maintenance issues relating to (a) roofing, (b) loss of heating and hot water, (c) electrics, (d) pest control and (e) damp and mould since April 2022.	⁣<UIN>(27467)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Luke Pollard</memberName> (Plymouth, Sutton and Devonport): To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many callouts have been made to Sir John Moor Barracks for maintenance issues relating to (a) roofing, (b) loss of heating and hot water, (c) electrics, (d) pest control and (e) damp and mould since April 2022.	⁣<UIN>(27468)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Luke Pollard</memberName> (Plymouth, Sutton and Devonport): To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many callouts have been made to Baker Barracks for maintenance issues relating to (a) roofing, (b) loss of heating and hot water, (c) electrics, (d) pest control and (e) damp and mould since April 2022.	⁣<UIN>(27469)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Luke Pollard</memberName> (Plymouth, Sutton and Devonport): To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many callouts have been made to RAF Odiham for maintenance issues relating to (a) roofing, (b) loss of heating and hot water, (c) electrics, (d) pest control and (e) damp and mould since April 2022.	⁣<UIN>(27470)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Luke Pollard</memberName> (Plymouth, Sutton and Devonport): To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many callouts have been made to RAF Wyton for maintenance issues relating to (a) roofing, (b) loss of heating and hot water, (c) electrics, (d) pest control and (e) damp and mould since April 2022.	⁣<UIN>(27471)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Luke Pollard</memberName> (Plymouth, Sutton and Devonport): To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many callouts have been made to RAF Alconbury for maintenance issues relating to (a) roofing, (b) loss of heating and hot water, (c) electrics, (d) pest control and (e) damp and mould since April 2022.	⁣<UIN>(27472)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Luke Pollard</memberName> (Plymouth, Sutton and Devonport): To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many callouts have been made to Lympstone Commando Training Centre for maintenance issues relating to (a) roofing, (b) loss of heating and hot water, (c) electrics, (d) pest control and (e) damp and mould since April 2022.	⁣<UIN>(27473)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Luke Pollard</memberName> (Plymouth, Sutton and Devonport): To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many callouts have been made to RM Instow for maintenance issues relating to (a) roofing, (b) loss of heating and hot water, (c) electrics, (d) pest control and (e) damp and mould since April 2022.	⁣<UIN>(27474)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Luke Pollard</memberName> (Plymouth, Sutton and Devonport): To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many callouts have been made to RM Chivenor for maintenance issues relating to (a) roofing, (b) loss of heating and hot water, (c) electrics, (d) pest control and (e) damp and mould since April 2022.	⁣<UIN>(27541)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Sir John Hayes</memberName> (South Holland and The Deepings): To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have been convicted for breaching covid-19 restrictions since January 2022.	⁣<UIN>(27266)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Steve McCabe</memberName> (Birmingham, Selly Oak): To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department is taking to support veterans who are released from prison.	⁣<UIN>(27258)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Steve McCabe</memberName> (Birmingham, Selly Oak): To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether prison staff undergo veteran awareness training.	⁣<UIN>(27259)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Steve McCabe</memberName> (Birmingham, Selly Oak): To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether jurors undergo veteran awareness training.	⁣<UIN>(27260)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Steve McCabe</memberName> (Birmingham, Selly Oak): To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what support is provided to veterans with mental health conditions in prison.	⁣<UIN>(27261)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Stephanie Peacock</memberName> (Barnsley East): To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what resources his Department is providing for the (a) assessment, (b) referral and (c) provision of support for (i) offenders and (i) victims who are affected by harmful gambling.	⁣<UIN>(27552)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Stephen Hammond</memberName> (Wimbledon): To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of the Financial Conduct Authority's (FCA) proposals to publicly announce the names of firms and/or individuals at the commencement of enforcement investigations on the (a) commercial value of firms, (b) career prospects of individuals who are named and (c) overall competitiveness of the UK’s (i) financial and related professional services industries and (ii) wider economy; and if he will make an assessment of the compatibility of that proposal with the FCA’s secondary objective to consider international competitiveness and economic growth.	⁣<UIN>(27312)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Neil O'Brien</memberName> (Harborough): To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, for what reasons the discount rate used to calculate the Resource Accounting and Budgeting charge on student loans is different to the rate used for general policy appraisal.	⁣<UIN>(27501)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Sammy Wilson</memberName> (East Antrim): To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many families have taken up tax free childcare allowances in Northern Ireland in each of the last five years.	⁣<UIN>(27315)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Sammy Wilson</memberName> (East Antrim): To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many and what proportion of families eligible for tax free credits have not taken up their entitlement for tax free childcare in each of the last 5 years.	⁣<UIN>(27316)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Sammy Wilson</memberName> (East Antrim): To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to help ensure that parents who are eligible for tax free childcare in Northern Ireland access that support.	⁣<UIN>(27317)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Caroline Ansell</memberName> (Eastbourne): To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, whether she has had discussions with the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions on the Parliamentary and Health Service Ombudsman's report into women's State Pension age changes, published on 21 March 2024.	⁣<UIN>(27477)</UIN></WQuestion> <FullLineAfter/> <Heading4>Questions for Answer on Monday 3 June</Heading4> <Heading5>Questions for Written Answer</Heading5> <NQuestionRestart><memberName>Florence Eshalomi</memberName> (Vauxhall): To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what his planned timetable is to respond to his Department's consultation entitled Supporting Our Veterans.	⁣<UIN>(27538)</UIN></NQuestionRestart> <NQuestion><memberName>Dame Diana Johnson</memberName> (Kingston upon Hull North): To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether the Government plans to accept all recommendations of the second interim report of the Infected Blood Inquiry.	⁣<UIN>(27305)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Dame Diana Johnson</memberName> (Kingston upon Hull North): To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether the Infected Blood Compensation Authority will be directly accountable to Parliament.	⁣<UIN>(27306)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Dame Diana Johnson</memberName> (Kingston upon Hull North): To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of establishing a board akin to the Horizon Compensation Advisory Board to advise Ministers on compensation for people infected and affected by contaminated blood.	⁣<UIN>(27307)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Steve McCabe</memberName> (Birmingham, Selly Oak): To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 15 April 2024 to Question 19773 on Veterans: Cost of Living, what is the source of funding for Op PROSPER.	⁣<UIN>(27243)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Steve McCabe</memberName> (Birmingham, Selly Oak): To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the annual budget was for the Office for Veterans Affairs in (a) 2023-24 and (b) 2024-25.	⁣<UIN>(27244)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Colum Eastwood</memberName> (Foyle): To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, if she will make an assessment of the implications for her policies on arms export licenses to Israel of the decision of the Chief Prosecutor of the International Criminal Court to issue arrest warrants for the Prime Minister and Minister of Defence of Israel.	⁣<UIN>(27465)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Sarah Olney</memberName> (Richmond Park): To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, if she will make an estimate of the potential impact of increases to the salary threshold for skilled worker visas on the number of prospective job offers that were rescinded in 2024.	⁣<UIN>(27466)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Andy Slaughter</memberName> (Hammersmith): To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, whether she has had discussions with her Department’s Chief Scientific Adviser on arms exports.	⁣<UIN>(27304)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Mr Gregory Campbell</memberName> (East Londonderry): To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will have discussions with the Director of Free Speech and Academic Freedom in the Office for Students on recent trends in anti-Semitism in universities.	⁣<UIN>(27294)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Helen Hayes</memberName> (Dulwich and West Norwood): To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment her Department has undertaken into the adequacy of the level of childcare provision in each local authority area.	⁣<UIN>(27549)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Dr Alan Whitehead</memberName> (Southampton, Test): To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what information his Department holds on the number of trainees that received heat pump training as part of skills bootcamps; and which qualifications have been supported.	⁣<UIN>(27236)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Grahame Morris</memberName> (Easington): To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, if she will make it her policy to apply the £1.2bn investment fund to the mineworkers pension scheme.	⁣<UIN>(27327)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Liz Saville Roberts</memberName> (Dwyfor Meirionnydd): To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, with reference to the oral contribution of the Parliamentary Under Secretary of State, Department for Energy Security and Net Zero, in response to a question from the hon. Member for Dwyfor Meirionnydd on 21 May 2024, Official Report, which new regulations are intended to ensure that installations are carried out in the correct manner; and whether her Department has published guidance on the impact of those regulations on installers.	⁣<UIN>(27543)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Dr Rosena Allin-Khan</memberName> (Tooting): To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the annual mean of air quality recording for PM 10 Particulate at Tooting Broadway in each year since 2010.	⁣<UIN>(27490)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Dr Rosena Allin-Khan</memberName> (Tooting): To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the annual mean air quality recording of Nitrogen Dioxide was at Tooting Broadway in each year since 2010.	⁣<UIN>(27491)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Stella Creasy</memberName> (Walthamstow): To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 13 May 2024 to Question 24233 on Export Health Certificates: Languages, what guidance his Department has issued on the language into which importers must provide completed health certificates to the UK authorities.	⁣<UIN>(27364)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Preet Kaur Gill</memberName> (Birmingham, Edgbaston): To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to his Department's publication entitled UK Food Security Index 2024, published on 14 May 2024, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of including indices on the (a) affordability, (b) availability and (c) accessibility of food for (i) consumers and (ii) at household level in his Department's next publication of that index.	⁣<UIN>(27435)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Mr Virendra Sharma</memberName> (Ealing, Southall): To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what guidance his Department has given to water companies on setting technical standards for assets.	⁣<UIN>(27318)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Mr Virendra Sharma</memberName> (Ealing, Southall): To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how water companies (a) review and (b) update technical standards.	⁣<UIN>(27319)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Mr Virendra Sharma</memberName> (Ealing, Southall): To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of water companies’ engagement with the supply chain.	⁣<UIN>(27320)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Dr Alan Whitehead</memberName> (Southampton, Test): To ask the Secretary of State for Levelling Up, Housing and Communities, how many businesses are registered with competent person schemes to install (a) air and (b) ground source heat pumps.	⁣<UIN>(27233)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Dr Alan Whitehead</memberName> (Southampton, Test): To ask the Secretary of State for Levelling Up, Housing and Communities, how many heat pump installations were notified to competent person schemes in the most recent 12 month period for which data is available.	⁣<UIN>(27234)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Dr Alan Whitehead</memberName> (Southampton, Test): To ask the Secretary of State for Levelling Up, Housing and Communities, if he will make an estimate of the proportion of heat pump installations that were notified to competent person schemes in the last 12 months.	⁣<UIN>(27235)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Kenny MacAskill</memberName> (East Lothian): To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many and what proportion of hydrogen buses on UK-roads were manufactured (a) in the UK and (b) abroad.	⁣<UIN>(27557)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Helen Morgan</memberName> (North Shropshire): To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department plans to provide funding for the creation of the full business case for the reopening of the Oswestry to Gobowen railway line.	⁣<UIN>(27434)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Grahame Morris</memberName> (Easington): To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment Network Rail has made of the prevalence of the use of zero hours contracts within its supply chain.	⁣<UIN>(27329)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Stephen Kinnock</memberName> (Aberavon): To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many PIP applications disallowed at initial decision were later granted at (a) mandatory reconsideration stage, (b) appeal stage and (c) tribunal stage in the Aberavon constituency in each of the last five years.	⁣<UIN>(27378)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Sir David Davis</memberName> (Haltemprice and Howden): To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the average (a) number of staff and (b) length of service of staff was in the Countess of Chester hospital's neonatal unit in (i) 2013, (ii) 2014, (iii) 2015, (iv) 2016, (v) 2017 and (vi) 2018.	⁣<UIN>(27270)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Rachael Maskell</memberName> (York Central): To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment she has made of the potential implications for her policies of the final report of the Infected Blood Inquiry, published on 20 May 2024.	⁣<UIN>(27408)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Rachael Maskell</memberName> (York Central): To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps she is taking to consult the infected and affected survivors of infected blood to ensure that their concerns are addressed by her Department.	⁣<UIN>(27409)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Rachael Maskell</memberName> (York Central): To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps she is taking to encourage a culture of accountability in (a) her Department, (b) its agencies and (c) other relevant service providers.	⁣<UIN>(27410)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Rachael Maskell</memberName> (York Central): To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if she will take steps to ensure that senior NHS (a) managers and (b) other leaders in her Department are encouraged to raise concerns about clinical practice.	⁣<UIN>(27411)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Steve McCabe</memberName> (Birmingham, Selly Oak): To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the answer of 26 March 2024 to Question 19244 on Mental Health Services: Veterans, what proportion of the Better Care Fund was spent on veterans in 2022-23.	⁣<UIN>(27245)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Steve McCabe</memberName> (Birmingham, Selly Oak): To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the answer of 26 March 2024 to Question 19244 on Mental Health Services: Veterans, whether any of the social prescribing pilot sites are in garrison towns.	⁣<UIN>(27246)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Steve McCabe</memberName> (Birmingham, Selly Oak): To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 26 March 2024 to Question 19244 on Mental Health Services: Veterans, how many veterans are involved in the social prescribing pilot sites.	⁣<UIN>(27247)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Grahame Morris</memberName> (Easington): To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 20 May 2024 to Question 26406 on Dental Service: Easington, if she will make an assessment of the effectiveness of the North East and North Cumbria Integrated Care Board's local processes for identifying areas of need following the loss of NHS dental provision in the Easington constituency.	⁣<UIN>(27328)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Grahame Morris</memberName> (Easington): To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent discussions she has had with NHS England on the information provided to patients on the availability of NHS Dentist services.	⁣<UIN>(27331)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Abena Oppong-Asare</memberName> (Erith and Thamesmead): To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to page 18 of the report by the National Audit Office entitled Progress in improving mental health services in England, published on 9 February 2023, HC 1082, how much funding her Department has provided for each category of mental health service set out in figure three of that report in each financial year since 2013-14.	⁣<UIN>(27525)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Wes Streeting</memberName> (Ilford North): To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what was the spend by the NHS on agency doctors in each of the last five years.	⁣<UIN>(27450)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Wes Streeting</memberName> (Ilford North): To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much NHS in England has spent on agency staff in each of the last five years.	⁣<UIN>(27453)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Wes Streeting</memberName> (Ilford North): To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much the NHS has spent on non-disclosure agreements in each of the last five years.	⁣<UIN>(27454)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Mr Gregory Campbell</memberName> (East Londonderry): To ask the Deputy Foreign Secretary, if he will have urgent discussions with his Indian counterpart on (a) recent reported attacks on Christian (i) groups and (ii) individuals and (b) re-conversion ceremonies.	⁣<UIN>(27296)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Neil Coyle</memberName> (Bermondsey and Old Southwark): To ask the Deputy Foreign Secretary, whether he plans to impose sanctions on (a) the Rapid Support Forces in Sudan and (b) people who fund that group.	⁣<UIN>(27382)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Wayne David</memberName> (Caerphilly): To ask the Deputy Foreign Secretary, when he plans to respond to Question 26077 on Tawfik Ghanem, tabled by the hon. Member for Caerphilly on 14 May 2024.	⁣<UIN>(27293)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Seema Malhotra</memberName> (Feltham and Heston): To ask the Deputy Foreign Secretary, what recent discussions his Department has had with the Administrator of USAID on levels of (a) food and (b) fuel entering Gaza.	⁣<UIN>(27372)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Seema Malhotra</memberName> (Feltham and Heston): To ask the Deputy Foreign Secretary, whether he has had recent discussions with his Austrian counterpart on the decision of that country to reinstate funding to UNRWA.	⁣<UIN>(27373)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Anne McLaughlin</memberName> (Glasgow North East): To ask the Deputy Foreign Secretary, what steps he is taking to ensure that humanitarian aid reaches (a) the most vulnerable populations and (b) areas that are hard to access in Somalia.	⁣<UIN>(27407)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Andy Slaughter</memberName> (Hammersmith): To ask the Deputy Foreign Secretary, whether his Department has taken recent steps to help secure the release of Manahel al-Otaibi.	⁣<UIN>(27303)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Gareth Thomas</memberName> (Harrow West): To ask the Deputy Foreign Secretary, with reference to the Answer of 24 December 2018 to Question 203351 on British Nationals Abroad: Detainees, how many referrals have been made to the pro bono legal panel in each of the last 12 months.	⁣<UIN>(27239)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Mr Gregory Campbell</memberName> (East Londonderry): To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people who arrived in the UK by small boats in 2023 are (a) male and (b) female.	⁣<UIN>(27295)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Mr Gregory Campbell</memberName> (East Londonderry): To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the Defending Democracy Taskforce is taking steps to examine the (a) presence of and (b) influence exerted by the Confucius Institutes.	⁣<UIN>(27297)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Dan Jarvis</memberName> (Barnsley Central): To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 20 May to Question 26458 on Oppression, if he will publish his speech to the Hong Kong Symposium on 27 April 2024.	⁣<UIN>(27371)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Stephen Kinnock</memberName> (Aberavon): To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the press release entitled Prime Minister announces new funding to stop the boats, published on 20 May 2024, if he will publish the data that supports the statements that the Government has (a) dismantled 82 organised crime groups, (b) seized 352 boats and (c) prevent thousands of migrants from crossing the Channel.	⁣<UIN>(27379)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>John Healey</memberName> (Wentworth and Dearne): To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many water contamination incidents have occurred at Ministry of Defence barracks in each year since 2010.	⁣<UIN>(27271)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>John Healey</memberName> (Wentworth and Dearne): To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 20 May 2024 to Question 26344 on Air Force: Recruitment and with reference to the Answer of 25 July 2023 to Question 26344 on Air Force: Recruitment, for what reason he was (a) able to supply recruitment target data in 2023 and (b) not able to supply recruitment target data in 2024.	⁣<UIN>(27272)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>John Healey</memberName> (Wentworth and Dearne): To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 5 February 2024 to Question 11252 on Defence Equipment: Finance, when he plans to write to the hon. Member for Wentworth and Dearne.	⁣<UIN>(27273)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>John Healey</memberName> (Wentworth and Dearne): To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when HMS (a) Westminster and (b) Argyll will be formally retired.	⁣<UIN>(27275)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>John Healey</memberName> (Wentworth and Dearne): To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to his Department's press release entitled New Golden Age of shipbuilding as new UK-built warships boost Navy building programme to up to 28 ships and submarines, published on 14 May 2024, whether the new Multi Role Support Ships will be designated as warships.	⁣<UIN>(27279)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Karl Turner</memberName> (Kingston upon Hull East): To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent discussions he has had with maritime trade unions on the Royal Fleet Auxiliary industrial dispute over the 2023-24 pay settlement.	⁣<UIN>(27344)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Karl Turner</memberName> (Kingston upon Hull East): To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent discussions his Department has had with the Royal Fleet Auxiliary on leave ratios for merchant seafarers.	⁣<UIN>(27345)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Ruth Cadbury</memberName> (Brentford and Isleworth): To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prison officers working in the Long Term High Security Estate south have less than one year's experience.	⁣<UIN>(27383)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Colum Eastwood</memberName> (Foyle): To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, whether his Department has (a) received and (b) granted requests to provide communications data on journalists in Northern Ireland in the last five years.	⁣<Transfer>[Transferred] </Transfer><UIN>(27145)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Colum Eastwood</memberName> (Foyle): To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, whether his Department (a) received and (b) granted requests to provide communications data on lawyers in Northern Ireland in the last five years.	⁣<Transfer>[Transferred] </Transfer><UIN>(27146)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Colum Eastwood</memberName> (Foyle): To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, whether his Department has (a) received and (b) granted requests to provide communications data on Members of the Northern Ireland Assembly in the last five years.	⁣<Transfer>[Transferred] </Transfer><UIN>(27147)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Colum Eastwood</memberName> (Foyle): To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, whether his Department has had discussions with the Department of Justice in Northern Ireland on the alleged surveillance of journalists in Northern Ireland.	⁣<Transfer>[Transferred] </Transfer><UIN>(27148)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Richard Fuller</memberName> (North East Bedfordshire): To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much revenue has been raised as a result of steps his Department has taken to close the tax gap in each year since 2010.	⁣<UIN>(27325)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>James Murray</memberName> (Ealing North): To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many HMRC employees were (a) recruited exclusively using artificial intelligence and (b) in roles relating to the recruitment of new staff in each of the last five years.	⁣<UIN>(27511)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Anneliese Dodds</memberName> (Oxford East): To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, whether she plans to carry out another National LGBT Survey.	⁣<UIN>(27531)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Anneliese Dodds</memberName> (Oxford East): To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, with reference to the National LGBT survey, published in July 2018, what the resource cost of that survey was.	⁣<UIN>(27532)</UIN></NQuestion> <FullLineAfter/> <Heading4>Questions for Answer on Tuesday 4 June</Heading4> <Heading5>Questions for Written Answer</Heading5> <NQuestionRestart><memberName>Mr John Baron</memberName> (Basildon and Billericay): To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when he plans to respond to the correspondence of (a) 9 January, (b) 1 February, (c) 7 March and (d) 9 May 2024 from the hon. Member for Basildon and Billericay, case reference JB44530.	⁣<UIN>(27292)</UIN></NQuestionRestart> <NQuestion><memberName>Daniel Kawczynski</memberName> (Shrewsbury and Atcham): To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans his Department has for the use of Nesscliffe Training Camp.	⁣<UIN>(27309)</UIN></NQuestion> <FullLineAfter/> <Heading4>Questions for Answer on Wednesday 5 June</Heading4> <Heading5>Questions for Written Answer</Heading5> <NQuestionRestart><memberName>Marsha De Cordova</memberName> (Battersea): To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what visa schemes are available to Palestinians seeking to reunite with family in the UK.	⁣<UIN>(27551)</UIN></NQuestionRestart> <FullLineAfter/> <Heading4>Questions for Answer on Thursday 6 June</Heading4> <Heading5>Questions for Written Answer</Heading5> <NQuestionRestart><memberName>Jeremy Corbyn</memberName> (Islington North): To ask the Deputy Foreign Secretary, whether he has made representations to his Kenyan counterpart on rates of femicide in that country.	⁣<UIN>(27240)</UIN></NQuestionRestart> </root>