<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<root><Heading4>Questions for Answer on Wednesday 8 May</Heading4> <Heading5>Questions for Written Answer</Heading5> <WQuestionRestart><memberName>Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi</memberName> (Slough): To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if she will take steps to help support companies in the gaming industry that use artificial intelligence to innovate.	⁣<Transfer>[Transferred] </Transfer><UIN>(24796)</UIN></WQuestionRestart> <WQuestion><memberName>Kenny MacAskill</memberName> (East Lothian): To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of using (a) the (i) detritus and (ii) cut offs from timber products and (b) the waste from Whisky distilling in the manufacture of sustainable aviation fuel.	⁣<UIN>(25077)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Allan Dorans</memberName> (Ayr, Carrick and Cumnock): To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of ensuring that degrees awarded by the Open University are recognised as professional qualifications by the (a) Health and Care Professions Council and (b) British Psychological Society.	⁣<Transfer>[Transferred] </Transfer><UIN>(24830)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>John McNally</memberName> (Falkirk): To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what training he plans to provide to staff responsible for assisting with the work of the upper tribunal in relocating asylum seekers to Rwanda; who will provide that training; what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of that training; and whether he plans to issue a contract for the recruitment of those staff.	⁣<Transfer>[Transferred] </Transfer><UIN>(24780)</UIN></WQuestion> <FullLineAfter/> <Heading4>Questions for Answer on Thursday 9 May</Heading4> <Heading5>Questions for Written Answer</Heading5> <WQuestionRestart><memberName>Martin Docherty-Hughes</memberName> (West Dunbartonshire): To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of proposed reductions in the number of civil servants on the (a) capacity and (b) efficiency of the Civil Service.	⁣<UIN>(24927)</UIN></WQuestionRestart> <WQuestion><memberName>Jim Shannon</memberName> (Strangford): To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether he has made an assessment of the potential merits of taking steps to increase the number of civil servants working from the office.	⁣<UIN>(24916)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Andrew Bridgen</memberName> (North West Leicestershire): To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, if she will make an assessment of the potential impact of the EU Critical Raw Materials Act on levels of trade between Northern Ireland and the (a) rest of the UK and (b) EU.	⁣<UIN>(24922)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Sir Geoffrey Cox</memberName> (Torridge and West Devon): To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what discussions the Minister of State for Enterprise, Markets and Small Business has had with Post Office Ltd on the decision to reduce the remuneration period for subpostmasters with Hard to Place post offices; and what steps he is taking to ensure sufficient compensation and support for affected subpostmasters during the transition period.	⁣<UIN>(24869)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Colleen Fletcher</memberName> (Coventry North East): To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what steps she is taking to support job creation schemes in (a) Coventry North East constituency, (b) Coventry and (c) the West Midlands.	⁣<UIN>(24935)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Colleen Fletcher</memberName> (Coventry North East): To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what data her Department holds on the number of people in (a) the West Midlands, (b) Coventry and (c) Coventry North East constituency who have been employed in the automotive industry in each of the last three years.	⁣<UIN>(24938)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Colleen Fletcher</memberName> (Coventry North East): To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what estimate she has made of the number of small businesses in (a) Coventry North East constituency, (b) Coventry and (c) England that have closed in each of the last three years.	⁣<UIN>(24939)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Mark Menzies</memberName> (Fylde): To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what steps she is taking to support the UK nuclear industry to increase exports.	⁣<UIN>(24891)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Matt Rodda</memberName> (Reading East): To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, with reference to the guidance by the Central Digital and Data Office entitled Guidance on the Legacy IT Risk Assessment Framework, published on 29 September 2023, how many red-rated IT systems are used by her Department; and how many red-rated IT systems have been identified since 4 December 2023.	⁣<UIN>(25018)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Anneliese Dodds</memberName> (Oxford East): To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what progress her Department has made on developing updated guidance for schools on tackling sexual harassment.	⁣<UIN>(25022)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Colleen Fletcher</memberName> (Coventry North East): To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to tackle educational disadvantage in (a) Coventry North East constituency and (b) Coventry.	⁣<UIN>(24940)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Jonathan Gullis</memberName> (Stoke-on-Trent North): To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of using (a) the Duke of Edinburgh Award scheme and (b) other opportunities within further education colleges to help (i) people to develop skills for the workplace and (ii) deliver local skills improvement plans.	⁣<UIN>(25096)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Jonathan Gullis</memberName> (Stoke-on-Trent North): To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether her Department has made a recent assessment of the potential merits of supporting youth sector organisations to work with Local Enterprise Partnerships on the implementation of local skills improvement plans.	⁣<UIN>(25097)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Emma Hardy</memberName> (Kingston upon Hull West and Hessle): To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate her Department has made of the average length of time the Student Loans Company takes to refund people who have made an overpayment on their student loan.	⁣<UIN>(24995)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Emma Hardy</memberName> (Kingston upon Hull West and Hessle): To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what discussions she has had with HM Revenue and Customs on the timeframe for refunding student loan overpayment.	⁣<UIN>(24996)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Helen Hayes</memberName> (Dulwich and West Norwood): To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether she has made an assessment of the potential implications for her policies of the Royal National Institute of Blind People's research entitled Provision under pressure: Gaps in Educational Support for Children and Young People with Vision Impairment in England (2023), published in February 2024; and what steps her Department (a) is taking and (b) plans to take to ensure that children and young people with vision impairment have equitable access to education.	⁣<UIN>(24977)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Stephen Morgan</memberName> (Portsmouth South): To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to improve standards in (a) reading, (b) writing and (c) maths in Portsmouth schools.	⁣<UIN>(25007)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Stephen Morgan</memberName> (Portsmouth South): To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment she has made of the adequacy of SEND provision in schools in (a) Portsmouth and (b) England.	⁣<UIN>(25008)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Stephen Morgan</memberName> (Portsmouth South): To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to reduce waiting times for SEND services in schools.	⁣<UIN>(25009)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Matt Rodda</memberName> (Reading East): To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the guidance by the Central Digital and Data Office entitled Guidance on the Legacy IT Risk Assessment Framework, published on 29 September 2023, how many red-rated IT systems are used by her Department; and how many red-rated IT systems have been identified since 4 December 2023.	⁣<UIN>(25017)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Jim Shannon</memberName> (Strangford): To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of reforming university funding models to reduce dependence on the income of international students.	⁣<UIN>(24915)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Rushanara Ali</memberName> (Bethnal Green and Bow): To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, when her Department plans to submit its next nationally determined contribution to the UN Framework Convention on Climate Change; and if she will make it her policy that the next nationally determined contribution will set out how the UK will adhere to the 1.5 degrees Celsius warming limit.	⁣<UIN>(24923)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Deidre Brock</memberName> (Edinburgh North and Leith): To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what steps she (a) has taken and (b) plans to take with the devolved Administrations to improve coordination of efforts towards achieving the UK's international (i) climate and (ii) biodiversity obligations.	⁣<UIN>(24949)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Colleen Fletcher</memberName> (Coventry North East): To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what estimate her Department has made of the average amount spent on energy bills per household in (a) Coventry North East constituency, (b) Coventry, (c) the West Midlands and (d) England in each of the last five years.	⁣<UIN>(24937)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Selaine Saxby</memberName> (North Devon): To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, how many energy efficiency measures have been installed by parliamentary constituency between 2010 and 2024.	⁣<UIN>(25102)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Selaine Saxby</memberName> (North Devon): To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, how many households received the Warm Home Discount by parliamentary constituency since its creation.	⁣<UIN>(25103)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Selaine Saxby</memberName> (North Devon): To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, how much has been spent through the Warm Home Discount scheme by parliamentary constituency since its creation.	⁣<UIN>(25104)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Selaine Saxby</memberName> (North Devon): To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, how many households received support through the Energy Price Guarantee; and what the total amount of support received was by parliamentary constituency.	⁣<UIN>(25105)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Selaine Saxby</memberName> (North Devon): To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, how many businesses received support through the Energy Bills Discount Scheme; and what the total amount of support received was, by parliamentary constituency.	⁣<UIN>(25106)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Selaine Saxby</memberName> (North Devon): To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, how many businesses received support through the Energy Bill Relief Scheme; and what the total amount of support received was, by parliamentary constituency.	⁣<UIN>(25107)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Selaine Saxby</memberName> (North Devon): To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, how much has been spent through the Social Housing Decarbonisation Fund; and how many measures have been installed as a result of that expenditure, by parliamentary constituency.	⁣<UIN>(25108)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Selaine Saxby</memberName> (North Devon): To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, how much has been spent through the Public Sector Decarbonisation Scheme; and how many measures have been installed as a result of that expenditure, by parliamentary constituency.	⁣<UIN>(25109)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Selaine Saxby</memberName> (North Devon): To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, how much has been spent through the Green Homes Grant; and how many measures have been installed as a result of that expenditure, by parliamentary constituency.	⁣<UIN>(25110)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Selaine Saxby</memberName> (North Devon): To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, how much has been spent through the Local Authority Delivery Scheme; and how many measures have been installed as a result of that expenditure, by parliamentary constituency.	⁣<UIN>(25111)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Selaine Saxby</memberName> (North Devon): To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, how much has been spent through the Boiler Upgrade Scheme; and how many measures have been installed as a result of that expenditure, by parliamentary constituency.	⁣<UIN>(25112)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Selaine Saxby</memberName> (North Devon): To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, whether she has made an assessment of trends in the level of UK exports in low carbon and renewable sectors since 2015.	⁣<UIN>(25113)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Selaine Saxby</memberName> (North Devon): To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, whether she has made an estimate of the value of UK exports in low carbon and renewables sectors since 2015.	⁣<UIN>(25114)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Selaine Saxby</memberName> (North Devon): To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, whether she made an assessment of trends in the level of exports from the offshore wind sector since 2015 and; whether she has made an estimate of their total value.	⁣<UIN>(25115)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Sir Paul Beresford</memberName> (Mole Valley): To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what guidance his Department has issued on how the new regulations on hedge cutting apply to commercial hedgelaying.	⁣<UIN>(24845)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi</memberName> (Slough): To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when he plans to publish the National Action Plan for the Sustainable Use of Pesticides.	⁣<UIN>(24991)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi</memberName> (Slough): To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to support farmers to adopt (a) integrated pest management and (b) other alternative pest management approaches.	⁣<UIN>(24992)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi</memberName> (Slough): To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the potential impact of permitted pesticides on pollinator populations in England.	⁣<UIN>(24993)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi</memberName> (Slough): To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to (a) monitor and (b) ensure compliance with pesticide regulations.	⁣<UIN>(24994)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Tim Farron</memberName> (Westmorland and Lonsdale): To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many hectares of trees have been planted in each year since 2015.	⁣<UIN>(24876)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Tim Farron</memberName> (Westmorland and Lonsdale): To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much his Department has spent on tree planting in each year since 2015.	⁣<UIN>(24877)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Tim Farron</memberName> (Westmorland and Lonsdale): To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many inspections of shellfish waters his Department has conducted in each year since 2015.	⁣<UIN>(24878)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Jo Gideon</memberName> (Stoke-on-Trent Central): To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to page 15 of the report by Bite Back entitled Fuel us don't fool us, published in 2024, what steps he is taking to prevent the food industry from targeting children; and whether he has made an assessment of the potential merits of requiring manufacturers to remove (a) child-appealing features and (b) misleading health claims from unhealthy products.	⁣<UIN>(25098)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Matt Hancock</memberName> (West Suffolk): To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when his Department plans to announce the long-term funding solution for internal drainage boards.	⁣<UIN>(24896)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Ruth Jones</memberName> (Newport West): To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he is taking steps to (a) support the development of recycling (i) infrastructure and (ii) technologies and (b) help enable increased recovery of (A) critical minerals and (B) other materials.	⁣<UIN>(25065)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Ruth Jones</memberName> (Newport West): To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he is taking steps to improve (a) data collection, (b) mapping and (c) tracking of (i) critical minerals and (ii) other material streams in (A) electrical and (B) electronic equipment.	⁣<UIN>(25066)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Ruth Jones</memberName> (Newport West): To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will take steps to support the (a) re-use, (b) repair and (c) re-manufacturing of electronic waste products according to the waste hierarchy; and if he will make an assessment of the effectiveness of recycling infrastructure in supporting the management of e-waste.	⁣<UIN>(25067)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Ruth Jones</memberName> (Newport West): To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent estimate he has made of the scale of illegal hunting with dogs in (a) England and (b) Wales.	⁣<UIN>(25068)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Ruth Jones</memberName> (Newport West): To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential impact on rural communities in (a) Wales and (b) England of anti-social behaviour associated with hunting with dogs.	⁣<UIN>(25069)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Ruth Jones</memberName> (Newport West): To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with the Minister for the Environment in the Northern Ireland Executive.	⁣<UIN>(25070)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Ruth Jones</memberName> (Newport West): To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what progress he has made on implementing the recommendations included in the United Nations Office of Drugs and Crime report entitled Wildlife and Forest Crime Analytic Toolkit Report, published in 2021.	⁣<UIN>(25071)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Damien Moore</memberName> (Southport): To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what financial support is available to farmers impacted by flooding who are not eligible for support under the Farming Recovery Fund.	⁣<UIN>(25023)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Matt Rodda</memberName> (Reading East): To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the guidance by the Central Digital and Data Office entitled Guidance on the Legacy IT Risk Assessment Framework, published on 29 September 2023, how many red-rated IT systems are used by his Department; and how many red-rated IT systems have been identified since 4 December 2023.	⁣<UIN>(25015)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Alexander Stafford</memberName> (Rother Valley): To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking with Cabinet colleagues to help support the mental health of people working in the companion animal welfare sector.	⁣<UIN>(25116)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Alexander Stafford</memberName> (Rother Valley): To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to raise awareness of legal changes requiring the microchipping of cats by 10 June 2024.	⁣<UIN>(25117)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Colleen Fletcher</memberName> (Coventry North East): To ask the Secretary of State for Levelling Up, Housing and Communities, what steps his Department is taking to support first-time home buyers in (a) Coventry North East constituency and (b) Coventry.	⁣<UIN>(24941)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Colleen Fletcher</memberName> (Coventry North East): To ask the Secretary of State for Levelling Up, Housing and Communities, what assessment he has made of the level of home ownership in (a) Coventry North East constituency and (b) Coventry in each of the last three years.	⁣<UIN>(24942)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Stephen McPartland</memberName> (Stevenage): To ask the Secretary of State for Levelling Up, Housing and Communities, whether he plans to introduce a cap on service charges.	⁣<UIN>(24906)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Stephen McPartland</memberName> (Stevenage): To ask the Secretary of State for Levelling Up, Housing and Communities, what support is available for tenants in dispute with local authorities on damp and mould issues.	⁣<UIN>(24907)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Stephen McPartland</memberName> (Stevenage): To ask the Secretary of State for Levelling Up, Housing and Communities, what steps he is taking to help leaseholders in properties which are of no value due to remediation costs on service charges.	⁣<UIN>(24908)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Stephen Morgan</memberName> (Portsmouth South): To ask the Secretary of State for Levelling Up, Housing and Communities, if he will take steps to issue mandatory guidance to local authorities to ensure that all public washrooms include at least one male incontinence bin.	⁣<UIN>(25006)</UIN></WQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Alyn Smith</memberName> (Stirling): To ask the Secretary of State for Levelling Up, Housing and Communities, what discussions he has had with Cabinet colleagues on the adequacy of funding arrangements for Freeports.	⁣<Transfer>[Transferred] </Transfer><UIN>(24826)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Alyn Smith</memberName> (Stirling): To ask the Secretary of State for Levelling Up, Housing and Communities, what assessment he has made of the return of investment from Freeports for (a) the UK economy, (b) the Scottish economy and (c) shareholders and private investors.	⁣<Transfer>[Transferred] </Transfer><UIN>(24827)</UIN></NQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Dr Thérèse Coffey</memberName> (Suffolk Coastal): To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what proportion of households in Suffolk Coastal constituency had access to broadband speeds of over (a) 10 mbps and (b) 30mbps in (i) 2010 and (ii) the most recent period for which data is available.	⁣<UIN>(24909)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Anneliese Dodds</memberName> (Oxford East): To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, whether she plans to bring forward a code of practice regarding violence against women and girls online.	⁣<UIN>(25021)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Colleen Fletcher</memberName> (Coventry North East): To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much funding his Department has provided for transport projects in (a) the West Midlands and (b) Coventry in each of the last three years.	⁣<UIN>(24933)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Fabian Hamilton</memberName> (Leeds North East): To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of changes to vehicle tax for electric and low emissions vehicles from 1 April 2025 on the number of purchases of those vehicles.	⁣<UIN>(24858)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Fabian Hamilton</memberName> (Leeds North East): To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department (a) is taking and (b) plans to take steps to increase the provision of fast chargers for electric vehicles.	⁣<UIN>(24859)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Fabian Hamilton</memberName> (Leeds North East): To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department plans to take to help sustainable aviation fuel producers meet levels of demand from airlines.	⁣<UIN>(24860)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Navendu Mishra</memberName> (Stockport): To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of the number of electric vehicle charging points in Stockport constituency.	⁣<UIN>(25092)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Ashley Dalton</memberName> (West Lancashire): To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many child maintenance cases were moved from collect and pay to direct pay in (a) 2022 and (b) 2023.	⁣<UIN>(25127)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Ashley Dalton</memberName> (West Lancashire): To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many child maintenance cases were moved from collect and pay to direct pay where the child maintenance service was aware of domestic abuse in (a) 2022 and (b) 2023.	⁣<UIN>(25128)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Ashley Dalton</memberName> (West Lancashire): To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what his planned timetable is for laying secondary legislation to implement the Child Support Collection (Domestic Abuse) Act 2023.	⁣<UIN>(25129)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Marsha De Cordova</memberName> (Battersea): To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to recommendation 90(a) of the UN Committee on the Rights of Persons with Disabilities' Report on follow-up to the inquiry concerning the United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland, advance unedited version published on 22 March 2024, whether he is taking steps with Cabinet colleagues to (a) consult (i) disabled people and (ii) representative organisations on the national disability strategy and (b) otherwise involve those stakeholders with the strategy.	⁣<UIN>(25033)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Marsha De Cordova</memberName> (Battersea): To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of people receiving the personal independence payment are in paid employment.	⁣<UIN>(25034)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Marsha De Cordova</memberName> (Battersea): To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, for what reason the address to which to submit pre-action correspondence to his Department changed from DWP Legal Advisers to the Treasury Solicitor in January 2024.	⁣<UIN>(25035)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Marsha De Cordova</memberName> (Battersea): To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department has taken to communicate to benefits advisers the change of address to which to submit pre-action correspondence relating to his Department.	⁣<UIN>(25036)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Marsha De Cordova</memberName> (Battersea): To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many pieces of pre-action correspondence relating to his Department have been (a) received by the Treasury Solicitor and (b) responded to since 1 January 2024.	⁣<UIN>(25037)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Marsha De Cordova</memberName> (Battersea): To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average time is between pre-action correspondence relating to his Department being (a) received by the Treasury Solicitor and (b) responded to in the latest period for which data is available.	⁣<UIN>(25038)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Marsha De Cordova</memberName> (Battersea): To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department is taking to help ensure accurate understanding among (a) claimants and (b) benefits advisers of Personal Independence Payment in relation to being a benefit linked with the extra costs of disability not employment status.	⁣<UIN>(25039)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Marsha De Cordova</memberName> (Battersea): To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of PIP to cover the extra costs incurred by people with a disability.	⁣<UIN>(25040)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Vicky Foxcroft</memberName> (Lewisham, Deptford): To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people were waiting for a decision on their PIP application on 1 April 2024.	⁣<UIN>(24962)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Vicky Foxcroft</memberName> (Lewisham, Deptford): To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people were waiting for a decision on their PIP application on 1 March 2024.	⁣<UIN>(24963)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Vicky Foxcroft</memberName> (Lewisham, Deptford): To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people were waiting for a decision on their PIP application on 1 January 2024.	⁣<UIN>(24964)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Vicky Foxcroft</memberName> (Lewisham, Deptford): To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department took to engage with (a) disabled people and (b) disabled people's organisations when developing the Work Well programme.	⁣<UIN>(24965)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Vicky Foxcroft</memberName> (Lewisham, Deptford): To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what criteria his Department used to select the pilot areas for the WorkWell programme.	⁣<UIN>(24966)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Vicky Foxcroft</memberName> (Lewisham, Deptford): To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how his Department plans to measure the effectiveness of the WorkWell programme pilots.	⁣<UIN>(24967)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Vicky Foxcroft</memberName> (Lewisham, Deptford): To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what progress his Department has made on the roll out of the Back to Work Plan.	⁣<UIN>(24968)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Vicky Foxcroft</memberName> (Lewisham, Deptford): To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what progress his Department has made on the Health Transformation Programme.	⁣<UIN>(24969)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Vicky Foxcroft</memberName> (Lewisham, Deptford): To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of Personal Independence Payment claimants are in a form of paid employment.	⁣<UIN>(24970)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Vicky Foxcroft</memberName> (Lewisham, Deptford): To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of people in the Universal Credit (Limited Capability for Work) group are in a form of paid employment.	⁣<UIN>(24971)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Vicky Foxcroft</memberName> (Lewisham, Deptford): To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many Universal Credit claimants in the limited capability for work and work related activity group are in some form of paid employment as of May 2024.	⁣<UIN>(24972)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Vicky Foxcroft</memberName> (Lewisham, Deptford): To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in receipt of Attendance Allowance are in paid employment.	⁣<UIN>(24973)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Vicky Foxcroft</memberName> (Lewisham, Deptford): To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in receipt of Carer's Allowance are in paid employment.	⁣<UIN>(24974)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Caroline Lucas</memberName> (Brighton, Pavilion): To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of unpaid carers receiving Carer’s Allowance are caring for someone who receives Personal Independence Payment.	⁣<UIN>(24888)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Caroline Lucas</memberName> (Brighton, Pavilion): To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many unpaid carers receiving Carer’s Allowance are in receipt of Personal Independence Payment.	⁣<UIN>(24889)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Caroline Lucas</memberName> (Brighton, Pavilion): To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment his Department has made of the impact of his proposed changes to the Personal Independence Payment on unpaid carers and their eligibility to receive Carer’s Allowance.	⁣<UIN>(24890)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Alison McGovern</memberName> (Wirral South): To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether he plans to update the baseline year for absolute poverty.	⁣<UIN>(24903)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Charlotte Nichols</memberName> (Warrington North): To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make it his policy to allow beneficiaries to claim two years of a deceased person's state pension contributions in the event that they die before state pension age.	⁣<UIN>(25084)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Chloe Smith</memberName> (Norwich North): To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the impact of proposed changes to Personal Independence Payment on people living with (a) cancer and (b) the long-term side effects of cancer treatment.	⁣<UIN>(24886)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Marsha De Cordova</memberName> (Battersea): To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of collecting data on waiting times for accessing vision rehabilitation support.	⁣<UIN>(25025)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Marsha De Cordova</memberName> (Battersea): To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if she will make it her policy to collect data on waiting times for accessing vision rehabilitation support.	⁣<UIN>(25026)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Marsha De Cordova</memberName> (Battersea): To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether she has made an assessment of the potential merits of requiring each integrated care system to establish alert systems for general practice.	⁣<UIN>(25041)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Marsha De Cordova</memberName> (Battersea): To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether she has made an assessment of the potential merits of increasing the share of NHS funding for general practice.	⁣<UIN>(25042)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Marsha De Cordova</memberName> (Battersea): To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps her Department is taking to help grow the GP workforce.	⁣<UIN>(25043)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Marsha De Cordova</memberName> (Battersea): To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether she has had discussions with the Secretary of State for the Home Department on the potential merits of introducing a guaranteed permanent residence for international medical graduates qualifying as GPs.	⁣<UIN>(25044)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Colleen Fletcher</memberName> (Coventry North East): To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the take-up rate was for breast cancer screening in (a) Coventry, (b) the West Midlands and (c) England in each of the last two years.	⁣<UIN>(24934)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Colleen Fletcher</memberName> (Coventry North East): To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment she has made of trends in childhood obesity levels in (a) Coventry North East constituency, (b) Coventry, (c) the West Midlands and (d) England in each of the last three years.	⁣<UIN>(24936)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Peter Gibson</memberName> (Darlington): To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment she has made of the levels of Gonorrhea recorded; and what steps she is taking to reduce it.	⁣<UIN>(25072)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Peter Gibson</memberName> (Darlington): To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment she has made of the current levels of syphilis recorded; and what steps she is taking to tackle it.	⁣<UIN>(25073)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Claire Hanna</memberName> (Belfast South): To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment she has given to the potential merits of increasing the level of funding for research into (a) pancreatic cancer and (b) other cancers with lower survival rates.	⁣<UIN>(25101)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Sir John Hayes</memberName> (South Holland and The Deepings): To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether her Department is taking steps to assess the level of regional variation in the detection of lung cancer.	⁣<UIN>(24852)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Navendu Mishra</memberName> (Stockport): To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps her Department is taking to help improve specialist services for patients diagnosed with myalgic encephalomyelitis.	⁣<UIN>(25093)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Damien Moore</memberName> (Southport): To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information her Department holds on the number of people who (a) were under the age of 18 and (b) from Southport constituency who attended (i) Alder Hey Children's Hospital Trust and (ii) Ormskirk District General Hospital Children's Accident and Emergency Departments in each year from 2002-2023.	⁣<UIN>(25024)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Stephen Morgan</memberName> (Portsmouth South): To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether she is taking steps to raise public awareness (a) on the need for male continence bins and (b) to reduce the stigma associated with those who use them.	⁣<UIN>(25005)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Charlotte Nichols</memberName> (Warrington North): To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if she will make it her policy to abolish hospital car parking fees.	⁣<UIN>(25083)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Jim Shannon</memberName> (Strangford): To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps her Department is taking to improve waiting times for treatment for osteoporosis patients.	⁣<UIN>(24912)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Jim Shannon</memberName> (Strangford): To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if she will make an estimate of when single-step scaffold insertion will be available on the NHS for people with torn cartilage injuries.	⁣<UIN>(24913)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Jim Shannon</memberName> (Strangford): To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps her Department is taking to improve diagnosis of anaemia in women.	⁣<UIN>(24914)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Jim Shannon</memberName> (Strangford): To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps she is taking to reduce A&amp;E waiting times.	⁣<UIN>(24918)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Cat Smith</memberName> (Lancaster and Fleetwood): To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps she is taking to improve research into acute myeloid leukaemia.	⁣<UIN>(24951)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Royston Smith</memberName> (Southampton, Itchen): To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the average cost was of prescribing puberty blockers to each patient on the NHS in the latest period for which data is available.	⁣<UIN>(24961)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Liz Twist</memberName> (Blaydon): To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many staff were employed in the Office for Health Improvement and Disparities in public mental health national roles in (a) 2021, (b) 2022, (c) 2023 and (d) 2024.	⁣<UIN>(24988)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Liz Twist</memberName> (Blaydon): To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much funding has been allocated to (a) The Prevention Concordat for Better Mental Health and (b) Every Mind Matters in each year since their inception.	⁣<UIN>(24989)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>George Galloway</memberName> (Rochdale): To ask the Deputy Foreign Secretary, what the cost to the public purse has been of the UK's (a) participation in Operation Prosperity Guardian and (b) military air strikes on Yemen.	⁣<UIN>(24864)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Patrick Grady</memberName> (Glasgow North): To ask the Deputy Foreign Secretary, whether he has had discussions with the Government of (a) Germany and (b) France on the refusal of entry to their country of Dr Ghassan Abu Sittah, Rector of Glasgow University; and if he will make an assessment of the implications for his policies of such refusals.	⁣<UIN>(24950)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Fabian Hamilton</memberName> (Leeds North East): To ask the Deputy Foreign Secretary, what steps his Department plans to take to investigate the recent MoD security breach.	⁣<UIN>(24855)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Fabian Hamilton</memberName> (Leeds North East): To ask the Deputy Foreign Secretary, whether he plans to take steps to support the Brazilian state of Rio Grande do Sul following recent floods in that area.	⁣<UIN>(24856)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Fabian Hamilton</memberName> (Leeds North East): To ask the Deputy Foreign Secretary, what steps his Department is taking to support people facing food insecurity due to El Niño in (a) Colombia, (b) Ecuador, (c) Peru and (d) Bolivia.	⁣<UIN>(24862)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Fabian Hamilton</memberName> (Leeds North East): To ask the Deputy Foreign Secretary, whether his Department plans to take steps with (a) NGOs and (b) charities to tackle deficiencies in water (i) quality and (ii) access in South American countries due to El Niño.	⁣<UIN>(24863)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Claire Hanna</memberName> (Belfast South): To ask the Deputy Foreign Secretary, how many (a) clean water and (b) sanitation projects his Department has funded through official development assistance since 2021.	⁣<UIN>(25099)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Claire Hanna</memberName> (Belfast South): To ask the Deputy Foreign Secretary, if he will make an assessment of the adequacy of progress made towards achieving the UN Sustainable Development Goals by 2030.	⁣<UIN>(25100)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Stephen Morgan</memberName> (Portsmouth South): To ask the Deputy Foreign Secretary, whether he plans to make representations to his Israeli counterpart against the military operation in Rafah.	⁣<UIN>(24999)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Stephen Morgan</memberName> (Portsmouth South): To ask the Deputy Foreign Secretary, what steps he is taking to help ensure Israel takes steps to protect civilians and humanitarian aid workers in Rafah.	⁣<UIN>(25000)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Stephen Morgan</memberName> (Portsmouth South): To ask the Deputy Foreign Secretary, if he will make diplomatic representations to his Israeli counterparts to ensure the Rafah crossing remains open and the flow of aid continues.	⁣<UIN>(25001)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Stephen Morgan</memberName> (Portsmouth South): To ask the Deputy Foreign Secretary, what diplomatic steps he is taking to support international partners with ceasefire discussions between Israel and Hamas.	⁣<UIN>(25002)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Stephen Morgan</memberName> (Portsmouth South): To ask the Deputy Foreign Secretary, what diplomatic steps he is taking to support the freedom of the press reporting on the Israel Hamas war in Gaza.	⁣<UIN>(25003)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Stephen Morgan</memberName> (Portsmouth South): To ask the Deputy Foreign Secretary, what steps he is taking to help ensure there is a continued supply of fuel into Gaza, in the context of Israel’s closure of both the Rafah and Kerem Shalom crossings.	⁣<UIN>(25004)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Lisa Nandy</memberName> (Wigan): To ask the Deputy Foreign Secretary, whether he has had recent discussions with his (a) international partners and (b) non-governmental organisations on potential food shortages in East Africa; and if he will make an assessment of the implications for his policies of these potential food shortages.	⁣<UIN>(24897)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Lisa Nandy</memberName> (Wigan): To ask the Deputy Foreign Secretary, pursuant to the Answer of 2 May 2024 to Question 23469 on Afghanistan: Non-governmental Organisations, when a Minister from his Department last met representatives of non-governmental organisations working in Afghanistan.	⁣<UIN>(24898)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Lisa Nandy</memberName> (Wigan): To ask the Deputy Foreign Secretary, what steps his Department is taking to support multi-lateral institutions in promoting good governance in the global south.	⁣<UIN>(24899)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Lisa Nandy</memberName> (Wigan): To ask the Deputy Foreign Secretary, what recent steps his Department has taken to help support (a) governance reform and (b) humanitarian delivery in Lebanon.	⁣<UIN>(24900)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Lisa Nandy</memberName> (Wigan): To ask the Deputy Foreign Secretary, what steps he is taking to help ensure female Afghan students can (a) apply for and (b) study through Chevening scholarships.	⁣<UIN>(24901)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Lisa Nandy</memberName> (Wigan): To ask the Deputy Foreign Secretary, whether he has had preliminary discussions with (a) NGOs, (b) partner nations and (iii) the UN on future reconstruction of Gaza's education system.	⁣<UIN>(24902)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Matt Rodda</memberName> (Reading East): To ask the Deputy Foreign Secretary, with reference to the guidance by the Central Digital and Data Office entitled Guidance on the Legacy IT Risk Assessment Framework, published on 29 September 2023, how many red-rated IT systems are used by his Department; and how many red-rated IT systems have been identified since 4 December 2023.	⁣<UIN>(25016)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Jim Shannon</memberName> (Strangford): To ask the Deputy Foreign Secretary, if his Department will make an assessment of the implications for his policies of the religious dimension of the recent attacks against Christians by (a) jihadist groups and (b) Fulani militants in (i) Northern Nigeria and (ii) the Middle Belt.	⁣<UIN>(24919)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Catherine West</memberName> (Hornsey and Wood Green): To ask the Deputy Foreign Secretary, whether he has made an assessment of the potential impact of the Australian national defence strategy on the UK's cooperation with (a) Australia (b) other partners in the Indo-Pacific.	⁣<UIN>(24981)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Catherine West</memberName> (Hornsey and Wood Green): To ask the Deputy Foreign Secretary, whether he is taking steps with Cabinet colleagues to (a) assess instances of and (b) help tackle transnational repression.	⁣<UIN>(24982)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Catherine West</memberName> (Hornsey and Wood Green): To ask the Deputy Foreign Secretary, whether he has had recent discussions with his international partners on transnational repression.	⁣<UIN>(24983)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Catherine West</memberName> (Hornsey and Wood Green): To ask the Deputy Foreign Secretary, what estimate he has made of the number of journalists detained in China; and what steps he is taking to support media freedom in that country.	⁣<UIN>(24984)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Andrew Bridgen</memberName> (North West Leicestershire): To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many asylum seekers have been returned to the UK from Ireland since 2016.	⁣<UIN>(24920)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Andrew Bridgen</memberName> (North West Leicestershire): To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many requests have been made by the Irish government for the UK to accept an asylum seeker since 2016.	⁣<UIN>(24921)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Deidre Brock</memberName> (Edinburgh North and Leith): To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the video entitled The first individuals set to be removed to Rwanda, posted on X by his Department on 1 May 2024, who produced the video; and how much the video cost to produce.	⁣<UIN>(24948)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Anneliese Dodds</memberName> (Oxford East): To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to (a) evaluate and (b) review the violence against women and girls strategy.	⁣<UIN>(25020)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Tim Farron</memberName> (Westmorland and Lonsdale): To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people have worked under the poultry Seasonal Worker visa scheme in each year since 2021.	⁣<UIN>(24879)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Tim Farron</memberName> (Westmorland and Lonsdale): To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many and what proportion of applicants have secured a Seasonal Worker visa in each year since 2019.	⁣<UIN>(24880)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Sir John Hayes</memberName> (South Holland and The Deepings): To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many asylum seekers awaiting decisions has his Department been unable to locate or contact since January 2022.	⁣<UIN>(24851)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Mark Menzies</memberName> (Fylde): To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of Operation Centurion on anti-social behaviour in Lancashire.	⁣<UIN>(24893)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Navendu Mishra</memberName> (Stockport): To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people has his Department identified for deportation to Rwanda in a) Stockport and b) Greater Manchester.	⁣<UIN>(25094)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Navendu Mishra</memberName> (Stockport): To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will undertake a review of maternity leave entitlement for Police Officers; and update police regulations to reflect the outcome of that review.	⁣<UIN>(25095)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Jim Shannon</memberName> (Strangford): To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps he is taking to protect retailers from shoplifting.	⁣<UIN>(24917)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Martin Docherty-Hughes</memberName> (West Dunbartonshire): To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of deploying armed forces personnel to help facilitate the medical evacuation of civilians in Gaza.	⁣<UIN>(24928)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Martin Docherty-Hughes</memberName> (West Dunbartonshire): To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to ensure that any evidence of war crimes being committed in Gaza witnessed by UK armed forces surveillance is (a) documented and (b) investigated.	⁣<UIN>(24929)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Martin Docherty-Hughes</memberName> (West Dunbartonshire): To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to increase representation of women in veteran support services.	⁣<UIN>(24930)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Martin Docherty-Hughes</memberName> (West Dunbartonshire): To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to (a) reduce and (b) prevent sexual harassment and assault of women serving in the armed forces.	⁣<UIN>(24931)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Martin Docherty-Hughes</memberName> (West Dunbartonshire): To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to ensure that Armed Forces Compensation payments are processed before applicants die.	⁣<UIN>(24932)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Fabian Hamilton</memberName> (Leeds North East): To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the potential implications for his policies of Russia's threat of a military response following the UK's provision of long-range missiles to Ukraine.	⁣<UIN>(24857)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Fabian Hamilton</memberName> (Leeds North East): To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the BGI Group (a) has or (b) has ever had contracts with his Department.	⁣<UIN>(24861)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Daniel Kawczynski</memberName> (Shrewsbury and Atcham): To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the War Widows Recognition Payment Scheme.	⁣<UIN>(24871)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Daniel Kawczynski</memberName> (Shrewsbury and Atcham): To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many applications have been (a) made to, (b) approved by and (c) paid by the War Widows Recognition Payment Scheme.	⁣<UIN>(24872)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Daniel Kawczynski</memberName> (Shrewsbury and Atcham): To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the (a) shortest, (b) average and (c) longest time taken is between application to and a payment under the War Widows Recognition Payment Scheme.	⁣<UIN>(24873)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Daniel Kawczynski</memberName> (Shrewsbury and Atcham): To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many applications have been made to the War Widows Recognition Payment Scheme in each month since it was announced.	⁣<UIN>(24874)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Daniel Kawczynski</memberName> (Shrewsbury and Atcham): To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many staff in his Department work on the War Widows Recognition Payment Scheme.	⁣<UIN>(24875)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Helen Morgan</memberName> (North Shropshire): To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he made of the adequacy of the standard of service accommodation before setting the Defence Infrastructure Organisation budget for 2024-25.	⁣<UIN>(25126)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Luke Pollard</memberName> (Plymouth, Sutton and Devonport): To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many callouts have been made to DMS Whittington for maintenance issues relating to (a) roofing, (b) loss of heating and hot water, (c) electrics, (d) pest control and (e) damp and mould since April 2022.	⁣<UIN>(25045)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Luke Pollard</memberName> (Plymouth, Sutton and Devonport): To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many callouts have been made to Chetwynd Barracks for maintenance issues relating to (a) roofing, (b) loss of heating and hot water, (c) electrics, (d) pest control and (e) damp and mould since April 2022.	⁣<UIN>(25046)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Luke Pollard</memberName> (Plymouth, Sutton and Devonport): To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many callouts have been made to Prince William of Gloucester Barracks for maintenance issues relating to (a) roofing, (b) loss of heating and hot water, (c) electrics, (d) pest control and (e) damp and mould since April 2022.	⁣<UIN>(25047)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Luke Pollard</memberName> (Plymouth, Sutton and Devonport): To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many callouts have been made to Parsons Barracks for maintenance issues relating to (a) roofing, (b) loss of heating and hot water, (c) electrics, (d) pest control and (e) damp and mould since April 2022.	⁣<UIN>(25048)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Luke Pollard</memberName> (Plymouth, Sutton and Devonport): To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many callouts have been made to Venning Barracks for maintenance issues relating to (a) roofing, (b) loss of heating and hot water, (c) electrics, (d) pest control and (e) damp and mould since April 2022.	⁣<UIN>(25049)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Luke Pollard</memberName> (Plymouth, Sutton and Devonport): To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many service personnel are based at DMS Whittington.	⁣<UIN>(25050)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Luke Pollard</memberName> (Plymouth, Sutton and Devonport): To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many service personnel are based at Chetwynd Barracks.	⁣<UIN>(25051)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Luke Pollard</memberName> (Plymouth, Sutton and Devonport): To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many service personnel are based at Prince William of Gloucester Barracks.	⁣<UIN>(25052)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Luke Pollard</memberName> (Plymouth, Sutton and Devonport): To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many service personnel are based at Parsons Barracks.	⁣<UIN>(25053)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Luke Pollard</memberName> (Plymouth, Sutton and Devonport): To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many service personnel are based at Venning Barracks.	⁣<UIN>(25054)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Luke Pollard</memberName> (Plymouth, Sutton and Devonport): To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much his Department has spent on improving service accommodation at DMS Whittington since April 2022.	⁣<UIN>(25055)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Luke Pollard</memberName> (Plymouth, Sutton and Devonport): To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much his Department has spent on improving service accommodation at Chetwynd Barracks since April 2022.	⁣<UIN>(25056)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Luke Pollard</memberName> (Plymouth, Sutton and Devonport): To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much his Department has spent on improving service accommodation at Prince William of Gloucester Barracks since April 2022.	⁣<UIN>(25057)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Luke Pollard</memberName> (Plymouth, Sutton and Devonport): To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much his Department has spent on improving service accommodation at Parsons Barracks since April 2022.	⁣<UIN>(25058)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Luke Pollard</memberName> (Plymouth, Sutton and Devonport): To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much his department has spent on improving service accommodation at Venning Barracks since April 2022.	⁣<UIN>(25059)</UIN></WQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Alex Cunningham</memberName> (Stockton North): To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what discussions he has had with the Courts and Tribunals Judiciary on its decision to make second and subsequent bail applications remote by default.	⁣<UIN>(24910)</UIN></NQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Marsha De Cordova</memberName> (Battersea): To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to recommendation 90(c) of the UN Committee on the Rights of Persons with Disabilities' Report on follow-up to the inquiry concerning the United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland, advance unedited version published on 22 March 2024, if he will take steps to ensure that protections for disabled people under hate crime laws are nationally consistent.	⁣<UIN>(25032)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Matt Rodda</memberName> (Reading East): To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the guidance by the Central Digital and Data Office entitled Guidance on the Legacy IT Risk Assessment Framework, published on 29 September 2023, how many red-rated IT systems are used by his Department; and how many red-rated IT systems have been identified since 4 December 2023.	⁣<UIN>(25013)</UIN></WQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Wendy Chamberlain</memberName> (North East Fife): To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the average waiting time was for processing a new application for Child Benefit in the latest period for which data is available.	⁣<Transfer>[Transferred] </Transfer><UIN>(24831)</UIN></NQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Adam Holloway</memberName> (Gravesham): To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many referrals have been received by HMRC from trading standards since the commencement of the Tobacco Products (Traceability and Security Features) Regulations 2023; and how many penalties have been issued following such referrals.	⁣<UIN>(24870)</UIN></WQuestion> <WQuestion><memberName>Mark Menzies</memberName> (Fylde): To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of banking hubs in helping to ensure access to banking facilities in rural communities.	⁣<UIN>(24892)</UIN></WQuestion> <FullLineAfter/> <Heading4>Questions for Answer on Friday 10 May</Heading4> <Heading5>Questions for Written Answer</Heading5> <NQuestionRestart><memberName>Gen Kitchen</memberName> (Wellingborough): To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if she will provide additional funding for the provision of out-of-hours GP appointments in (a) Wellingborough constituency and (b) Northamptonshire.	⁣<UIN>(25130)</UIN></NQuestionRestart> <FullLineAfter/> <Heading4>Questions for Answer on Monday 13 May</Heading4> <Heading5>Questions for Written Answer</Heading5> <NQuestionRestart><memberName>Matt Rodda</memberName> (Reading East): To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the guidance by the Central Digital and Data Office entitled Guidance on the Legacy IT Risk Assessment Framework, published on 29 September 2023, how many red-rated IT systems are used by his Department; and how many red-rated IT systems have been identified since 4 December 2023.	⁣<UIN>(25014)</UIN></NQuestionRestart> <NQuestion><memberName>Conor McGinn</memberName> (St Helens North): To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what steps she is taking to help increase business investment in (a) St Helens North constituency and (b) the North West.	⁣<UIN>(24957)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Navendu Mishra</memberName> (Stockport): To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 18 April to Question 20456 on Special Educational Needs: Stockport Metropolitan Borough Counci, what estimate her Department has made of the number of local authorities that are not delivering their education, health and care function as a result of constraints upon the general fund.	⁣<UIN>(25087)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Sir Stephen Timms</memberName> (East Ham): To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans she has to uprate the income threshold for eligibility for free school meals.	⁣<UIN>(24850)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Sir Chris Bryant</memberName> (Rhondda): To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what was the total number of cut flower imports between 2010 and 2020.	⁣<UIN>(24866)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Sir Chris Bryant</memberName> (Rhondda): To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many (a) gypsophila, (b) solidago, (c) orchids, (d) dianthus and (e) chrysanthemum consignments were imported from the EU between 2020 and 2023.	⁣<UIN>(24867)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Sir Chris Bryant</memberName> (Rhondda): To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many recorded incidents of disease were connected to imports from the EU of (a) gypsophila, (b) solidago, (c) orchids, (d) dianthus and (e) chrysanthemum between 2020 and 2023.	⁣<UIN>(24868)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Wendy Chamberlain</memberName> (North East Fife): To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when he plans to lay the Windsor Framework (Non-Commercial Movement of Pet Animals) Regulations before Parliament.	⁣<UIN>(25076)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Stella Creasy</memberName> (Walthamstow): To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many and what proportion of consignments containing high-risk goods which were required to pay the Common User Charge entering the UK from the EU were subject to a physical inspection under the Border Target Operating Model between 30 April and 5 May 2024.	⁣<UIN>(24904)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Stella Creasy</memberName> (Walthamstow): To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many and what proportion of consignments containing only medium or low-risk goods which were required to pay the Common User Charge entering the UK from the EU were subject to a physical inspection under the Border Target Operating Model between 30 April and 5 May 2024.	⁣<UIN>(24905)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Darren Jones</memberName> (Bristol North West): To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of extending the deadline for neutering dogs whose owners wish to withdraw a certificate of exemption.	⁣<UIN>(24990)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Colleen Fletcher</memberName> (Coventry North East): To ask the Secretary of State for Levelling Up, Housing and Communities, whether his Department plans to take steps to reduce health inequalities through housing in (a) Coventry North East constituency, (b) Coventry, (c) the West Midlands and (d) England.	⁣<UIN>(24943)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Colleen Fletcher</memberName> (Coventry North East): To ask the Secretary of State for Levelling Up, Housing and Communities, what recent estimate he has made of the number of empty residential properties in (a) Coventry North East constituency, (b) Coventry, (c) the West Midlands and (d) England; and what steps his Department is taking to ensure empty residential properties do not fall into disrepair.	⁣<UIN>(24944)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Peter Kyle</memberName> (Hove): To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, pursuant to the Answer of 22 April 2024 to Question 22348 on Public Expenditure, what his planned timetable is for publishing the response to David Willetts’ report.	⁣<UIN>(24975)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Navendu Mishra</memberName> (Stockport): To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of Avanti West Coast’s management of Euston railway station.	⁣<UIN>(25091)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Stephen Morgan</memberName> (Portsmouth South): To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what progress his Department has made on HS2 tunnelling between Old Oak Common and Euston Station.	⁣<UIN>(24997)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Stephen Morgan</memberName> (Portsmouth South): To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what financing mechanisms he plans to use to help deliver the HS2 station at London Euston.	⁣<UIN>(24998)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Colleen Fletcher</memberName> (Coventry North East): To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what support his Department provides to older jobseekers in (a) Coventry North East constituency, (b) Coventry, (c) the West Midlands and (d) England who are looking to (i) reskill or (ii) change careers.	⁣<UIN>(24945)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Matt Rodda</memberName> (Reading East): To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the guidance by the Central Digital and Data Office entitled Guidance on the Legacy IT Risk Assessment Framework, published on 29 September 2023, a) how many red-rated IT systems are used by his Department; and how many red-rated IT systems have been identified since 4 December 2023.	⁣<UIN>(25012)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Sir Stephen Timms</memberName> (East Ham): To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of people who claimed Carer's Allowance were caring for someone in receipt of a Personal Independence Payment in the past 12 months.	⁣<UIN>(24846)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Sir Stephen Timms</memberName> (East Ham): To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of people who claimed Carer's Allowance also claimed a Personal Independence Payment in the past 12 months.	⁣<UIN>(24847)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Sir Stephen Timms</memberName> (East Ham): To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of his Department's proposed changes to Personal Independence Payments on unpaid carers.	⁣<UIN>(24848)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Dr Philippa Whitford</memberName> (Central Ayrshire): To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether additional funding is available to local authorities to provide services to assist people with Universal Credit claims where those services are not available through Citizens Advice.	⁣<UIN>(24946)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Conor McGinn</memberName> (St Helens North): To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether her Department has made an assessment of the potential impact of pharmacy closures on the quality of primary care in St Helens constituency since 2019.	⁣<UIN>(24958)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Navendu Mishra</memberName> (Stockport): To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 16 April 2024 to Question 20454 on Mental Health Services: Stockport, how the £4.7 billion of increased funding for mental health has been spent; and how much and what proportion of that funding has been spent by (a) local authority and (b) constituency area.	⁣<UIN>(25088)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Navendu Mishra</memberName> (Stockport): To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 2 April 2024 to Question 17003 on River Mersey: Water, when he expects the Environment Agency's national programmes report on its investigation into chemical failures and historic sources of chemicals across the Mersey catchment to be published.	⁣<UIN>(25089)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Navendu Mishra</memberName> (Stockport): To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if she will provide a timescale of when she expects (a) NHS England to conclude its commercial negotiations with Vertex Pharmaceuticals and (b) NICE to issue final guidance on NHS availability of Kaftrio for new patients.	⁣<UIN>(25090)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Mr Virendra Sharma</memberName> (Ealing, Southall): To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps she is taking to increase HPV vaccination uptake.	⁣<UIN>(24881)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Mr Virendra Sharma</memberName> (Ealing, Southall): To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if she will provide an update on the status of the recruitment process for the Chair of the MHRA.	⁣<UIN>(24882)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Mr Virendra Sharma</memberName> (Ealing, Southall): To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when she plans to announce the new Chair of the MHRA.	⁣<UIN>(24883)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Mr Virendra Sharma</memberName> (Ealing, Southall): To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what role the incoming Chair of the MHRA will have in the recruitment process for the new Chief Executive.	⁣<UIN>(24884)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Mr Virendra Sharma</memberName> (Ealing, Southall): To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if she will provide an update on the status of the recruitment process for the Chief Executive of the MHRA.	⁣<UIN>(24885)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Karin Smyth</memberName> (Bristol South): To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate she has made of the cost to (a) integrated care boards and (b) NHS England of commissioning specialised services in the financial year (i) 2022-23 and ( ii) 2023-24.	⁣<UIN>(24952)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Karin Smyth</memberName> (Bristol South): To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of the nine statutory joint committees formed between integrated care boards and NHS England regions on specialised commissioning.	⁣<UIN>(24953)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Karin Smyth</memberName> (Bristol South): To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what (a) training and (b) support on specialised services is provided for staff working in integrated care boards in the (i) East of England, (ii) Midlands and (iii) North West following full delegation of commissioning in 2024-25.	⁣<UIN>(24954)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Karin Smyth</memberName> (Bristol South): To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate she has made of the proportion of specialised services that met national standards in the (a) 2022-23 and (b) 2023-24 financial years.	⁣<UIN>(24955)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Karin Smyth</memberName> (Bristol South): To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment has she made of the adequacy of the progress towards full delegated commissioning for Integrated Care Boards by April 2025 in (a) the South West, (b) the South East, (c) London and (d) the North East.	⁣<UIN>(24956)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Nadia Whittome</memberName> (Nottingham East): To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of increasing funding to increase capacity in children and young people's gender services.	⁣<UIN>(25118)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Nadia Whittome</memberName> (Nottingham East): To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps she is taking to help support 17-year-olds on the waiting list for gender identity services who have had their appointments with adult services cancelled and are not eligible for young people’s services.	⁣<UIN>(25119)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Nadia Whittome</memberName> (Nottingham East): To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether additional funding will be provided to local Children and Adolescent Mental Health Services for ongoing support beyond initial assessment for young people who are currently on the waiting list for gender services.	⁣<UIN>(25120)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Nadia Whittome</memberName> (Nottingham East): To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether (a) children and young people and (b) adults whose care has moved to adult gender services will be able to opt out of research into those who attended the Gender Identity Development Services at Tavistock and Portman NHS Foundation Trust.	⁣<UIN>(25121)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Holly Lynch</memberName> (Halifax): To ask the Deputy Foreign Secretary, whether the Minister of State for the Indo-Pacific raised human rights concerns relating to the 2024 Safeguarding National Security Bill and the 2020 National Security Law while meeting the (a) Hong Kong Secretary for Financial Services and (b) Treasury Christopher Hui in Hong Kong.	⁣<UIN>(24959)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Holly Lynch</memberName> (Halifax): To ask the Deputy Foreign Secretary, if the Minister of State for the Indo-Pacific will declare the 2024 Safeguarding National Security Bill in Hong Kong to be a breach of the Sino-British Joint Declaration following its first application in the case of Ma Chun-man in March 2024.	⁣<UIN>(24960)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Matthew Pennycook</memberName> (Greenwich and Woolwich): To ask the Deputy Foreign Secretary, what recent steps his Department has taken to help ensure all parties comply with resolution 2728 (2024) adopted by the UN Security Council on 25 March 2024.	⁣<UIN>(24978)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Liz Saville Roberts</memberName> (Dwyfor Meirionnydd): To ask the Deputy Foreign Secretary, if he will make an assessment of the implications for his policies of the planned march into Gaza by Israeli settlers on 15 May 2024.	⁣<UIN>(24979)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Liz Saville Roberts</memberName> (Dwyfor Meirionnydd): To ask the Deputy Foreign Secretary, what discussions he has had with his Israeli counterparts on the planned march in Gaza by Israeli settlers on 15 May 2024; and if he will take diplomatic steps to help prevent the resettlement of Israeli settlers in Gaza.	⁣<UIN>(24980)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Sir Stephen Timms</memberName> (East Ham): To ask the Deputy Foreign Secretary, what recent discussions Ministers in his Department have had with their Egyptian counterparts on Alaa Abd El-Fattah.	⁣<UIN>(24849)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Wendy Chamberlain</memberName> (North East Fife): To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the (a) average and (b) longest waiting times were for processing applications for certificates of sponsorship for skilled workers in each month from November 2023 to April 2024.	⁣<UIN>(25074)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Wendy Chamberlain</memberName> (North East Fife): To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether he has made an assessment of the potential cost to businesses of the reforms to skilled worker visas.	⁣<UIN>(25075)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Sarah Green</memberName> (Chesham and Amersham): To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether he has discussions with Cabinet colleagues on the potential merits of banning flights by Iran Air to the UK.	⁣<UIN>(25122)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Kate Osborne</memberName> (Jarrow): To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many Rule 35(1) reports made by GPs working in Immigration Removal Centres setting out their concerns that continued detention of a person was likely to be injurious to their health were received by his Department from 1 January 2022 to 31 December 2023; how many such persons were released from detention as a result of such a report; and in how many cases was detention continued because his Department believed that the vulnerabilities identified by the medical practitioner were outweighed by immigration control factors.	⁣<UIN>(25082)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Matt Rodda</memberName> (Reading East): To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the guidance by the Central Digital and Data Office entitled Guidance on the Legacy IT Risk Assessment Framework, published on 29 September 2023, a) how many red-rated IT systems are used by his Department; and how many red-rated IT systems have been identified since 4 December 2023.	⁣<UIN>(25011)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Kenny MacAskill</memberName> (East Lothian): To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Royal Air Force operated planes have flown to Israel since 24 April 2024.	⁣<UIN>(25078)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Kenny MacAskill</memberName> (East Lothian): To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will publish details of the items that Royal Air Force operated planes landing in Israel since 7 October 2023 have carried on board.	⁣<UIN>(25079)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Kenny MacAskill</memberName> (East Lothian): To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many personnel from his Department have been transported to Israel on RAF operated planes since 7 October 2023.	⁣<UIN>(25080)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Helen Morgan</memberName> (North Shropshire): To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to improve the quality of service accommodation.	⁣<UIN>(25125)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Luke Pollard</memberName> (Plymouth, Sutton and Devonport): To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many single living accommodation bedspaces are there in Scotland.	⁣<UIN>(25060)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Luke Pollard</memberName> (Plymouth, Sutton and Devonport): To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many maintenance requests have been made at RAF Brize Norton for issues relating to (a) roofing, (b) loss of heating and hot water, (c) electrics, (d) pest control and (e) damp and mould since April 2022.	⁣<UIN>(25061)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Luke Pollard</memberName> (Plymouth, Sutton and Devonport): To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many service personnel are based at RAF Brize Norton as of May 2024.	⁣<UIN>(25062)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Luke Pollard</memberName> (Plymouth, Sutton and Devonport): To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much his Department has spent on improving service accommodation at RAF Brize Norton since April 2022.	⁣<UIN>(25063)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Luke Pollard</memberName> (Plymouth, Sutton and Devonport): To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 1 May 2024 to Question 23282 on Armed Forces: Housing, how many service personnel are based in Woolwich; and what estimate he has made of the number of personnel to be based there in each of the next five years.	⁣<UIN>(25064)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Matt Rodda</memberName> (Reading East): To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the guidance by the Central Digital and Data Office entitled Guidance on the Legacy IT Risk Assessment Framework, published on 29 September 2023, how many red-rated IT systems are used by his Department; and how many red-rated IT systems have been identified since 4 December 2023.	⁣<UIN>(25010)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Matt Rodda</memberName> (Reading East): To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department has made an assessment of the implications for his Department of the national security risks associated with IT infrastructure operated by (a) his Department's arm’s-length bodies and (b) private firms under contract to his Department.	⁣<UIN>(25019)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Kate Hollern</memberName> (Blackburn): To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people serving an imprisonment for a Public Protection sentence were held in secure hospitals at the start of the last 20 quarters.	⁣<UIN>(24924)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Kate Hollern</memberName> (Blackburn): To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people serving an Imprisonment for Public Protection sentence on licence in the community took their own life in each year since 2010.	⁣<UIN>(24925)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Kate Hollern</memberName> (Blackburn): To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people serving an Imprisonment for Public Protection sentence have been transferred from prison to secure hospitals on mental health grounds in each year since 2020.	⁣<UIN>(24926)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Hilary Benn</memberName> (Leeds Central): To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what steps his Department is taking to ensure mental health support is available to police veterans in relation to the Omagh Bombing Inquiry.	⁣<UIN>(24853)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Hilary Benn</memberName> (Leeds Central): To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what steps his Department is taking to ensure legal representation is made available to police veterans called to the Omagh Bombing Inquiry.	⁣<UIN>(24854)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Mr Kevan Jones</memberName> (North Durham): To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether funding has been allocated to Harland &amp; Wolff to run a ferry service between Penzance and the Isles of Scilly.	⁣<UIN>(24865)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Helen Morgan</memberName> (North Shropshire): To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the efficiency and effectiveness of the Financial Services Compensation Scheme in its assessment of mortgage mis-selling complaints.	⁣<UIN>(25123)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Helen Morgan</memberName> (North Shropshire): To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many and what proportion of appeals to the Financial Services Compensation Scheme have resulted in an over-turned decision.	⁣<UIN>(25124)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Caroline Nokes</memberName> (Romsey and Southampton North): To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he has had recent discussions with the (a) insurance sector, (b) Financial Conduct Authority, (c) Financial Ombudsman and (d) Equality and Human Rights Commission on the ability of people in the Gypsy, Roma and Traveller community to obtain (i) buildings and (ii) contents insurance.	⁣<UIN>(24894)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Caroline Nokes</memberName> (Romsey and Southampton North): To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps his Department is taking to help support people in the Gypsy, Roma and Traveller community to obtain (a) buildings and (b) contents insurance.	⁣<UIN>(24895)</UIN></NQuestion> <HalfLineAfter/> <Heading5>Oral Questions to the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions</Heading5> <OQuestionRestart><memberName>Helen Morgan</memberName> (North Shropshire): What assessment he has made of the adequacy of the average time taken to decide the outcome of Personal Independence Payment applications.	⁣<UIN>(902750)</UIN></OQuestionRestart> <OQuestion><memberName>Steve Double</memberName> (St Austell and Newquay): What steps he is taking to help fill job vacancies in St Austell and Newquay constituency.	⁣<UIN>(902751)</UIN></OQuestion> <OQuestion><memberName>Sarah Green</memberName> (Chesham and Amersham): What recent assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the Child Maintenance Service in securing funds from paying parents.	⁣<UIN>(902752)</UIN></OQuestion> <OQuestion><memberName>Mrs Sheryll Murray</memberName> (South East Cornwall): What steps his Department is taking to increase the support available in Jobcentres in South East Cornwall constituency.	⁣<UIN>(902753)</UIN></OQuestion> <OQuestion><memberName>James Morris</memberName> (Halesowen and Rowley Regis): What plans he has to increase levels of employment.	⁣<UIN>(902754)</UIN></OQuestion> <OQuestion><memberName>Neale Hanvey</memberName> (Kirkcaldy and Cowdenbeath): What recent assessment he has made of the potential merits of providing compensation to women born in the 1950s affected by changes to the State Pension age.	⁣<UIN>(902755)</UIN></OQuestion> <OQuestion><memberName>Dr James Davies</memberName> (Vale of Clwyd): What steps his Department is taking to support pensioners.	⁣<UIN>(902756)</UIN></OQuestion> <OQuestion><memberName>Paula Barker</memberName> (Liverpool, Wavertree): If he will make an estimate of the number of in-work Universal Credit claimants that have had payments stopped due to errors made by his Department in the last 12 months.	⁣<UIN>(902757)</UIN></OQuestion> <OQuestion><memberName>Christian Wakeford</memberName> (Bury South): What recent estimate he has made of the number of pensioners in poverty.	⁣<UIN>(902758)</UIN></OQuestion> <OQuestion><memberName>Andrew Jones</memberName> (Harrogate and Knaresborough): What steps his Department is taking to support disabled people into work.	⁣<UIN>(902759)</UIN></OQuestion> <OQuestion><memberName>Neil Coyle</memberName> (Bermondsey and Old Southwark): What steps his Department is taking to reduce waiting times for Access to Work assessments.	⁣<UIN>(902760)</UIN></OQuestion> <OQuestion><memberName>Gordon Henderson</memberName> (Sittingbourne and Sheppey): What steps he is taking to help fill job vacancies in Sittingbourne and Sheppey constituency.	⁣<UIN>(902761)</UIN></OQuestion> <OQuestion><memberName>Jill Mortimer</memberName> (Hartlepool): What steps his Department is taking to increase the support available in Jobcentres in Hartlepool.	⁣<UIN>(902762)</UIN></OQuestion> <OQuestion><memberName>Peter Aldous</memberName> (Waveney): What steps he is taking to reform the welfare system.	⁣<UIN>(902763)</UIN></OQuestion> <OQuestion><memberName>Peter Gibson</memberName> (Darlington): What steps his Department is taking to support people with autism into employment.	⁣<UIN>(902764)</UIN></OQuestion> <OQuestion><memberName>Craig Tracey</memberName> (North Warwickshire): What steps his Department is taking to help reduce unemployment.	⁣<UIN>(902765)</UIN></OQuestion> <OQuestion><memberName>Alexander Stafford</memberName> (Rother Valley): What steps his Department is taking to support pensioners.	⁣<UIN>(902766)</UIN></OQuestion> <OQuestion><memberName>Richard Burgon</memberName> (Leeds East): What steps his Department is taking to support pensioners with increases in the cost of living.	⁣<UIN>(902767)</UIN></OQuestion> <OQuestion><memberName>Deidre Brock</memberName> (Edinburgh North and Leith): What recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of support for pensioners with increases in the cost of living.	⁣<UIN>(902768)</UIN></OQuestion> <OQuestion><memberName>Graham Stuart</memberName> (Beverley and Holderness): What steps his Department is taking to reform the welfare system.	⁣<UIN>(902769)</UIN></OQuestion> <OQuestion><memberName>Dr Jamie Wallis</memberName> (Bridgend): What steps his Department is taking to help reduce unemployment.	⁣<UIN>(902770)</UIN></OQuestion> <OQuestion><memberName>Ian Blackford</memberName> (Ross, Skye and Lochaber): If he will have discussions with the Industrial Injuries Advisory Council on the potential merits of classifying people with football-related brain injuries as having industrial injuries.	⁣<UIN>(902771)</UIN></OQuestion> <OQuestion><memberName>Miss Sarah Dines</memberName> (Derbyshire Dales): What steps his Department is taking to support pensioners.	⁣<UIN>(902772)</UIN></OQuestion> <OQuestion><memberName>Marion Fellows</memberName> (Motherwell and Wishaw): If he will take steps to help tackle negative attitudes towards disabled benefit claimants.	⁣<UIN>(902773)</UIN></OQuestion> <OQuestion><memberName>Jeff Smith</memberName> (Manchester, Withington): What steps his Department is taking to reduce the number of people in destitution.	⁣<UIN>(902774)</UIN></OQuestion> <HalfLineAfter/> <Heading5>Topical Questions to the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions</Heading5> <TQuestionRestart><memberName>Chris Clarkson</memberName> (Heywood and Middleton): If he will make a statement on his departmental responsibilities.	⁣<UIN>(902775)</UIN></TQuestionRestart> <TQuestion><memberName>Sir Desmond Swayne</memberName> (New Forest West): 	⁣<UIN>(902776)</UIN></TQuestion> <TQuestion><memberName>Neale Hanvey</memberName> (Kirkcaldy and Cowdenbeath): 	⁣<UIN>(902777)</UIN></TQuestion> <TQuestion><memberName>Stephen Morgan</memberName> (Portsmouth South): 	⁣<UIN>(902778)</UIN></TQuestion> <TQuestion><memberName>Cat Smith</memberName> (Lancaster and Fleetwood): 	⁣<UIN>(902779)</UIN></TQuestion> <TQuestion><memberName>Luke Pollard</memberName> (Plymouth, Sutton and Devonport): 	⁣<UIN>(902780)</UIN></TQuestion> <TQuestion><memberName>Sir David Evennett</memberName> (Bexleyheath and Crayford): 	⁣<UIN>(902781)</UIN></TQuestion> <TQuestion><memberName>Jack Brereton</memberName> (Stoke-on-Trent South): 	⁣<UIN>(902782)</UIN></TQuestion> <TQuestion><memberName>Sarah Green</memberName> (Chesham and Amersham): 	⁣<UIN>(902783)</UIN></TQuestion> <TQuestion><memberName>Steve Tuckwell</memberName> (Uxbridge and South Ruislip): 	⁣<UIN>(902784)</UIN></TQuestion> <FullLineAfter/> <Heading4>Questions for Answer on Tuesday 14 May</Heading4> <Heading5>Questions for Written Answer</Heading5> <NQuestionRestart><memberName>Jamie Stone</memberName> (Caithness, Sutherland and Easter Ross): To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many water sports (a) training sessions, (b) activities and (c) events have been reported to her Department due to unsafe water quality in each year since 2020.	⁣<UIN>(24987)</UIN></NQuestionRestart> <NQuestion><memberName>Julie Elliott</memberName> (Sunderland Central): To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether reinforced autoclaved aerated concrete (RAAC) has been found on his Department's estate.	⁣<UIN>(24911)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Jamie Stone</memberName> (Caithness, Sutherland and Easter Ross): To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether his Department requested that water sports (a) training sessions, (b) activities and (c) events were (i) cancelled and (ii) postponed due to unsafe water quality in each year since 2020.	⁣<UIN>(24985)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Jamie Stone</memberName> (Caithness, Sutherland and Easter Ross): To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many water sports (a) training sessions, (b) activities and (c) events have been reported to his Department due to unsafe water quality in each year since 2020.	⁣<UIN>(24986)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Peter Kyle</memberName> (Hove): To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, pursuant to the Answer of 22 February 2024 on Government Departments: Artificial Intelligence, whether the detailed policy for the Algorithmic transparency recording standard has been agreed across all departments; and whether he has a planned timeline for compliance.	⁣<UIN>(24976)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Alicia Kearns</memberName> (Rutland and Melton): To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what his Department's planned timescale is for issuing guidance to local authorities on allocating funding for the Local Transport Fund.	⁣<UIN>(25085)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Marsha De Cordova</memberName> (Battersea): To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make an assessment of the implications for his policies of the advance unedited report from the United Nations Committee on the Rights of Persons with Disabilities entitled Report on follow-up to the inquiry concerning the United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland, published on 22 March 2024.	⁣<UIN>(25027)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Marsha De Cordova</memberName> (Battersea): To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether he plans to accept the recommendations of the advance unedited report from the United Nations Committee on the Rights of Persons with Disabilities entitled Report on follow-up to the inquiry concerning the United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland, published on 22 March 2024.	⁣<UIN>(25028)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Marsha De Cordova</memberName> (Battersea): To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the advance unedited report from the United Nations Committee on the Rights of Persons with Disabilities entitled Report on follow-up to the inquiry concerning the United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland, published on 22 March 2024, whether his Department is taking steps to ensure non-regression of the Convention on the Rights of Disabled People (a) principles and (b) standards.	⁣<UIN>(25029)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Marsha De Cordova</memberName> (Battersea): To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to ensure that disabled people receive adequate financial support through the benefit system; and with reference to the advance unedited report from the United Nations Committee on the Rights of Persons with Disabilities entitled Report on follow-up to the inquiry concerning the United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland, published on 22 March 2024, if he will take steps to implement human rights-based cumulative impact assessments of the potential impact of welfare reforms on disabled people.	⁣<UIN>(25030)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Marsha De Cordova</memberName> (Battersea): To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to recommendation 90(f) of the UN Committee on the Rights of Persons with Disabilities' Report on follow-up to the inquiry concerning the United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland, advance unedited version published on 22 March 2024, if he will (a) review the Universal Credit system and (b) take steps to (i) identify the additional costs of living with disabilities and (ii) ensure that the level of social security benefits take adequate account of such costs.	⁣<UIN>(25031)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Alicia Kearns</memberName> (Rutland and Melton): To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether Captogan has been found in the UK; and whether his Department is taking steps to prevent it becoming available.	⁣<UIN>(25086)</UIN></NQuestion> <NQuestion><memberName>Kate Osborne</memberName> (Jarrow): To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Government Response to the recommendation in paragraph 47 of the Report of the European Committee for the Prevention of Torture and Inhuman or Degrading Treatment or Punishment (CPT) on its visit to the United Kingdom from 27 March to 6 April 2023 (CPT/Inf (2024) 09) that a healthcare professional be present during all Assessment, Care in Detention and Teamwork (ACDT) interviews in Immigration Removal Centres (IRCs), if he will take steps to address resourcing constraints of healthcare staff in order to meet the needs of mentally vulnerable people in detention.	⁣<RInterest>[R] </RInterest><UIN>(25081)</UIN></NQuestion> <FullLineAfter/> <Heading4>Questions for Answer on Thursday 16 May</Heading4> <Heading5>Questions for Written Answer</Heading5> <NQuestionRestart><memberName>Dr Philippa Whitford</memberName> (Central Ayrshire): To ask the Deputy Foreign Secretary, pursuant to the Answer of 23 April 2024 to Question 22020 on Ghassan Abu Sittah, whether he has (a) received information on the reasons that Germany issued a Schengen Area wide travel ban on British-Palestinian national Dr. Abu Sittah and (b) held discussions with his (i) German and (ii) French counterpart on that matter.	⁣<UIN>(24947)</UIN></NQuestionRestart> </root>