<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ArrayOfQuestionBlock xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
  <QuestionBlock>
    <Date>2024-05-16</Date>
    <Description>Questions for Written Answer</Description>
    <Questions>
      <Question>
        <Member>Charlotte Nichols</Member>
        <Constituency>Warrington North</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if she will take steps to help ensure that ultra-processed foods are easily identifiable to consumers.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department of Health and Social Care</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>1</Number>
        <UIN>26286</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>true</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Andrew Rosindell</Member>
        <Constituency>Romford</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether his Department plans to take steps to help local authorities in Greater London tackle the illegal use of e-scooters.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Home Office</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>2</Number>
        <UIN>26086</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>true</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
    </Questions>
    <QuestionType>Written</QuestionType>
    <ContainsWithdrawnQuestions>false</ContainsWithdrawnQuestions>
  </QuestionBlock>
  <QuestionBlock>
    <Date>2024-05-17</Date>
    <Description>Questions for Written Answer</Description>
    <Questions>
      <Question>
        <Member>Mr Gregory Campbell</Member>
        <Constituency>East Londonderry</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will hold discussions with (a) the Chancellor of the Exchequer and (b) other Cabinet colleagues on duty-free shopping in Northern Ireland airports when travelling to and from destinations in the EU.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Cabinet Office</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>1</Number>
        <UIN>26080</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>NAMEDDAY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>true</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Emma Hardy</Member>
        <Constituency>Kingston upon Hull West and Hessle</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of the average contribution of international students to the economy in each of the last five years.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Education</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>2</Number>
        <UIN>26579</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>true</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Sir Bill Wiggin</Member>
        <Constituency>North Herefordshire</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the potential impact of the draft Agriculture (Delinked Payments) (Reductions) (England) Regulations 2024 on the incomes of farmers.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>3</Number>
        <UIN>26372</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>true</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Andrew Lewer</Member>
        <Constituency>Northampton South</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Levelling Up, Housing and Communities, pursuant to the Answer of 19 April 2024 to Question 21211 on Ground Rent, whether his Department plans to make contingencies for the payment of (a) compensation and (b) legal fees that could be required for loss of income as a result of a ground rent cap.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Levelling Up, Housing and Communities</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>4</Number>
        <UIN>26596</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>true</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Dan Jarvis</Member>
        <Constituency>Barnsley Central</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, if she will commission a report on the potential impact of AI on (a) democracy and (b) elections.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Science, Innovation and Technology</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>5</Number>
        <UIN>26168</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>NAMEDDAY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>true</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Charlotte Nichols</Member>
        <Constituency>Warrington North</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps the Government is taking to support women to stay in employment when managing menopausal symptoms.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Work and Pensions</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>6</Number>
        <UIN>26623</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>true</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
    </Questions>
    <QuestionType>Written</QuestionType>
    <ContainsWithdrawnQuestions>false</ContainsWithdrawnQuestions>
  </QuestionBlock>
  <QuestionBlock>
    <Date>2024-05-20</Date>
    <Description>Questions for Written Answer</Description>
    <Questions>
      <Question>
        <Member>Caroline Lucas</Member>
        <Constituency>Brighton, Pavilion</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Attorney General, pursuant to the Answer of 16 May 2024 to Question 25822 on War Crimes: Gaza and with reference to paragraph 2.13 of the Ministerial Code, updated on 22 December 2022, if she will hold discussions with the Prime Minister on the potential merits of using her authority to publish summaries of advice provided to him on alleged war crimes in Gaza since 1 April 2024.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Attorney General</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>1</Number>
        <UIN>26669</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Dawn Butler</Member>
        <Constituency>Brent Central</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the 10 pilot programs are that have been funded through the Incubator for AI.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Cabinet Office</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>2</Number>
        <UIN>26373</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>NAMEDDAY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>true</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Fleur Anderson</Member>
        <Constituency>Putney</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what recent steps her Department has taken to help support (a) pubs, (b) restaurants, (c) cafes and (d) other parts of the hospitality sector.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Business and Trade</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>3</Number>
        <UIN>26779</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Wendy Chamberlain</Member>
        <Constituency>North East Fife</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, whether she has made a recent assessment of the potential merits for (a) businesses and (b) workers of introducing paid carers leave.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Business and Trade</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>4</Number>
        <UIN>26761</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Alicia Kearns</Member>
        <Constituency>Rutland and Melton</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, whether she has made an assessment of the potential implications for her policies of the decision by the United States to impose a 50% tariff on Chinese made solar cells.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Business and Trade</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>5</Number>
        <UIN>26288</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>NAMEDDAY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>true</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Alicia Kearns</Member>
        <Constituency>Rutland and Melton</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of introducing a 50% tariff on Chinese-made solar cells in the context of US tariff policy.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Business and Trade</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>6</Number>
        <UIN>26289</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>NAMEDDAY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>true</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Mr Toby Perkins</Member>
        <Constituency>Chesterfield</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, whether she has made a recent assessment of the potential merits of introducing licensing for funeral directors.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Business and Trade</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>7</Number>
        <UIN>26670</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Deidre Brock</Member>
        <Constituency>Edinburgh North and Leith</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if her Department will make an assessment of the potential merits of (a) reducing and (b) abolishing VAT on (i) maintenance and (ii) energy-efficiency improvements on historic and cultural buildings.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Culture, Media and Sport</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>8</Number>
        <UIN>26695</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Deidre Brock</Member>
        <Constituency>Edinburgh North and Leith</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if she will provide additional financial support to help the creative sector meet (a) energy and (b) maintenance costs.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Culture, Media and Sport</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>9</Number>
        <UIN>26696</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Fleur Anderson</Member>
        <Constituency>Putney</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to help (a) improve the quality of and (b) increase the affordability of childcare in (i) Wandsworth and (ii) the UK.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Education</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>10</Number>
        <UIN>26772</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Taiwo Owatemi</Member>
        <Constituency>Coventry North West</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether the Statutory Guidance on Relationships Education, Relationships and Sex Education and Health Education will include (a) variations in sex characteristics and (b) intersex.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Education</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>11</Number>
        <UIN>26764</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Alex Sobel</Member>
        <Constituency>Leeds North West</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, whether her Department has made an assessment of the potential impact of the Ofgem Targeted Charging Review on the rollout of electric vehicle charge points.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Energy Security and Net Zero</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>12</Number>
        <UIN>26720</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Alex Sobel</Member>
        <Constituency>Leeds North West</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what steps her Department is taking to help increase the deployment of electric vehicle charge points in rural areas.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Energy Security and Net Zero</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>13</Number>
        <UIN>26721</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Alex Sobel</Member>
        <Constituency>Leeds North West</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, if she will make an assessment of the potential (a) merits of introducing a standing charge relief for electric vehicle charge point operators and (b) impact of such a relief on the deployment of electric vehicle charge points in rural areas.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Energy Security and Net Zero</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>14</Number>
        <UIN>26722</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Alex Sobel</Member>
        <Constituency>Leeds North West</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what recent discussions her Department has had with industry stakeholders on the proposed Energy Bill Relief Scheme final reconciliation date in May 2024.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Energy Security and Net Zero</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>15</Number>
        <UIN>26723</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Alex Sobel</Member>
        <Constituency>Leeds North West</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, if she will make an assessment of the potential impact of the proposed Energy Bill Relief Scheme final reconciliation date of May 2024 on the non-domestic energy sector in the (a) medium- and (b) long-term.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Energy Security and Net Zero</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>16</Number>
        <UIN>26724</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Alex Sobel</Member>
        <Constituency>Leeds North West</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, whether her Department has made an assessment of the potential merits of (a) including additional reconciliation windows until 2027 and (b) other alternative proposals to the proposed Energy Bill Relief Scheme final reconciliation date of May 2024.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Energy Security and Net Zero</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>17</Number>
        <UIN>26725</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Sir John Hayes</Member>
        <Constituency>South Holland and The Deepings</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many and what proportion of (a) cars and (b) other vehicles used by his Department were made in Britain.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>18</Number>
        <UIN>26642</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Gen Kitchen</Member>
        <Constituency>Wellingborough</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to encourage (a) farmers and (b) food producers use sustainable farming methods in Wellingborough constituency.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>19</Number>
        <UIN>26822</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Gen Kitchen</Member>
        <Constituency>Wellingborough</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what data his Department holds on the number of trees planted in Wellingborough constituency since 2010.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>20</Number>
        <UIN>26823</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Gen Kitchen</Member>
        <Constituency>Wellingborough</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to help prevent off-road vehicles used for recreational purposes from causing damage to (a) farmland and (b) the countryside in Wellingborough constituency.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>21</Number>
        <UIN>26824</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Damien Moore</Member>
        <Constituency>Southport</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to help support coastal habitats.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>22</Number>
        <UIN>26729</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Damien Moore</Member>
        <Constituency>Southport</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to help support cockle fishing communities (a) around the Southport Cockle Bed and (b) in other areas.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>23</Number>
        <UIN>26730</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Damien Moore</Member>
        <Constituency>Southport</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to support the sustainability of the cockle fisheries sector.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>24</Number>
        <UIN>26731</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Damien Moore</Member>
        <Constituency>Southport</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent steps his Department has taken to protect (a) rural and (b) coastal communities at risk of flooding; and what steps he plans to take.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>25</Number>
        <UIN>26732</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Charlotte Nichols</Member>
        <Constituency>Warrington North</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the press release entitled Record number of new bathing sites get the go ahead, published on 13 May 2024, whether the new wild swimming spots will be safe to swim in 365 days a year.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>26</Number>
        <UIN>26782</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Martin Vickers</Member>
        <Constituency>Cleethorpes</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 23 April 2024 to Question 21619, what his planned timetable is for (a) completing the Emission Factors for Domestic Solid Fuels Work Package 1 project and (b) assessing the implications for his policies of the outcomes from that project; and whether he plans to publish that assessment.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>27</Number>
        <UIN>26671</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Fleur Anderson</Member>
        <Constituency>Putney</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Levelling Up, Housing and Communities, what steps his Department is taking to help (a) reduce the number of children in temporary accommodation and (b) increase the number of children living in secure tenancies.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Levelling Up, Housing and Communities</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>28</Number>
        <UIN>26774</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Fleur Anderson</Member>
        <Constituency>Putney</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Levelling Up, Housing and Communities, what recent steps his Department has taken to (a) improve the quality of and (b) increase the number of outreach programmes for people facing street homelessness.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Levelling Up, Housing and Communities</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>29</Number>
        <UIN>26775</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Bob Blackman</Member>
        <Constituency>Harrow East</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Levelling Up, Housing and Communities, what steps his Department plans to take to implement the Supported Housing (Regulatory Oversight) Act 2023.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Levelling Up, Housing and Communities</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>30</Number>
        <UIN>26675</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Bob Blackman</Member>
        <Constituency>Harrow East</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Levelling Up, Housing and Communities, with reference to his Department's consultation entitled Competence and Conduct Standard for social housing, published on 6 February 2024, if he will take steps to extend the (a) competence and (b) mandatory qualification standards to residential property managers.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Levelling Up, Housing and Communities</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>31</Number>
        <UIN>26676</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi</Member>
        <Constituency>Slough</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Levelling Up, Housing and Communities, how much funding his Department has provided to Slough Borough Council for social housing projects in each of the last five years.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Levelling Up, Housing and Communities</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>32</Number>
        <UIN>26715</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Gen Kitchen</Member>
        <Constituency>Wellingborough</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Levelling Up, Housing and Communities, what steps his Department is undertaking to (a) protect and (b) enhance green spaces in Wellingborough constituency.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Levelling Up, Housing and Communities</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>33</Number>
        <UIN>26807</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Gen Kitchen</Member>
        <Constituency>Wellingborough</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Levelling Up, Housing and Communities, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the supply of adapted housing for (a) adults and (b) children with disabilities in Wellingborough constituency.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Levelling Up, Housing and Communities</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>34</Number>
        <UIN>26808</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Gen Kitchen</Member>
        <Constituency>Wellingborough</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Levelling Up, Housing and Communities, how many Help to Buy homeowners are waiting for a decision on a loan redemption application in (a) Wellingborough and (b) Northamptonshire.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Levelling Up, Housing and Communities</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>35</Number>
        <UIN>26809</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Gen Kitchen</Member>
        <Constituency>Wellingborough</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Levelling Up, Housing and Communities, what assessment his Department has made of trends in the levels of people living in overcrowded housing in Wellingborough constituency.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Levelling Up, Housing and Communities</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>36</Number>
        <UIN>26810</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Gen Kitchen</Member>
        <Constituency>Wellingborough</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Levelling Up, Housing and Communities, what assessment his Department has made of trends in the prevalence of damp and mould in social housing in (a) Wellingborough constituency and (b) Northamptonshire.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Levelling Up, Housing and Communities</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>37</Number>
        <UIN>26811</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Gen Kitchen</Member>
        <Constituency>Wellingborough</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Levelling Up, Housing and Communities, if he will make an estimate of the proportion of houses in Wellingborough constituency that have an energy performance certificate rating of (a) A, (b) B, (c) C, (d) D and (e) E .</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Levelling Up, Housing and Communities</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>38</Number>
        <UIN>26812</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Gen Kitchen</Member>
        <Constituency>Wellingborough</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Levelling Up, Housing and Communities, what support his Department provided to rough sleepers in Wellingborough constituency in Winter 2023-24; and what steps his Department plans to take for Winter 2024-25.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Levelling Up, Housing and Communities</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>39</Number>
        <UIN>26813</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Wendy Morton</Member>
        <Constituency>Aldridge-Brownhills</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Levelling Up, Housing and Communities, what data his Department holds on the number of leasehold homes that have been repossessed under forfeiture since 2010, by region.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Levelling Up, Housing and Communities</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>40</Number>
        <UIN>26686</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Fleur Anderson</Member>
        <Constituency>Putney</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what steps her Department is taking to help tackle digital exclusion.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Science, Innovation and Technology</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>41</Number>
        <UIN>26777</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Damien Moore</Member>
        <Constituency>Southport</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what steps her Department is taking to help reduce the use of animal testing in scientific research.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Science, Innovation and Technology</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>42</Number>
        <UIN>26728</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Nick Fletcher</Member>
        <Constituency>Don Valley</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he has made an assessment of the potential merits of altering the legislation to enable the Civil Aviation Authority to allow drones to be operated out of the line of sight by the (a) police and (b) armed forces.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Transport</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>43</Number>
        <UIN>26791</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Dame Andrea Jenkyns</Member>
        <Constituency>Morley and Outwood</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions he has had with Uber on (a) passenger safety and (b) private hire and taxi laws.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Transport</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>44</Number>
        <UIN>26521</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>NAMEDDAY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>true</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Chi Onwurah</Member>
        <Constituency>Newcastle upon Tyne Central</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to support innovation to make transport more accessible to deaf people.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Transport</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>45</Number>
        <UIN>26682</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Fleur Anderson</Member>
        <Constituency>Putney</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make an assessment of the reasons for trends in the level of the use of food banks in the last five years.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Work and Pensions</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>46</Number>
        <UIN>26778</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Wendy Chamberlain</Member>
        <Constituency>North East Fife</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether he has made a recent assessment of the potential impact of the level of paid carers leave on rates of economic activity.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Work and Pensions</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>47</Number>
        <UIN>26759</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Wendy Chamberlain</Member>
        <Constituency>North East Fife</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to ensure that people over the age of 50 receive adequate support through the Back to Work Plan.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Work and Pensions</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>48</Number>
        <UIN>26760</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Vicky Foxcroft</Member>
        <Constituency>Lewisham, Deptford</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 15 May 2024 to Question 24972 on Universal Credit: Employment, what the criteria are for classifying people as live fit note (pre-wca).</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Work and Pensions</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>49</Number>
        <UIN>26707</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Dean Russell</Member>
        <Constituency>Watford</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make it his policy to amend Universal Credit regulations to take into account the 53-week rent year for 2024.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Work and Pensions</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>50</Number>
        <UIN>26788</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Owen Thompson</Member>
        <Constituency>Midlothian</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether his Department publishes statistics on response times for cases that have been sent to tribunals.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Work and Pensions</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>51</Number>
        <UIN>26704</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Owen Thompson</Member>
        <Constituency>Midlothian</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average response time is for cases that have been sent to tribunal.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Work and Pensions</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>52</Number>
        <UIN>26705</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Owen Thompson</Member>
        <Constituency>Midlothian</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what is the longest wait for a case to be heard at tribunal once referred.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Work and Pensions</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>53</Number>
        <UIN>26706</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Fleur Anderson</Member>
        <Constituency>Putney</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps her Department is taking to help improve (a) research into treatments for and (b) (i) emotional and (ii) financial support for people living with pancreatic cancer.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department of Health and Social Care</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>54</Number>
        <UIN>26771</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Fleur Anderson</Member>
        <Constituency>Putney</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of offering breast cancer screening to women going through early menopause.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department of Health and Social Care</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>55</Number>
        <UIN>26776</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Sir Philip Davies</Member>
        <Constituency>Shipley</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many responses were received to her Department's consultation entitled The disclosure of industry payments to the healthcare sector, which closed on 16 October 2023; and what her planned timetable is to respond to that consultation.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department of Health and Social Care</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>56</Number>
        <UIN>26667</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Carolyn Harris</Member>
        <Constituency>Swansea East</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many patients were referred to the Fracture Liaison Service with fragility fractures in each of the last five years; and what proportion of those patients were women over the age of 50.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department of Health and Social Care</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>57</Number>
        <UIN>26702</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Carolyn Harris</Member>
        <Constituency>Swansea East</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many and what proportion of the women over the age of 50 that were referred to the Fracture Liaison Service with fragility fractures were (a) taking hormone replacement therapy (HRT) prior to their first fragility fracture and (b) prescribed HRT as part of their treatment after their first fragility fracture in each of the last five years.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department of Health and Social Care</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>58</Number>
        <UIN>26703</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Caroline Lucas</Member>
        <Constituency>Brighton, Pavilion</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 20 February 2023 to Question 142657 on Mental Health Services: Children and Young People, what progress has been made on work to (a) establish the feasibility and associated risks of introducing new mental health waiting time standards for (i) adult's and (ii) children and young people’s community-based mental health services and (b) support the development of a baseline position for waiting times.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department of Health and Social Care</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>59</Number>
        <UIN>26668</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Alex Sobel</Member>
        <Constituency>Leeds North West</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps her Department have taken to reduce the time taken from initial presentation of symptoms to diagnosis of bipolar disorder.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department of Health and Social Care</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>60</Number>
        <UIN>26719</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Rushanara Ali</Member>
        <Constituency>Bethnal Green and Bow</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Deputy Foreign Secretary, if he will make an assessment of the adequacy of the UK's compliance with the UN Human Rights Council resolution on the Situation of human rights in Myanmar of 4 April 2024, A/HRC/55/L.17, in the context of the involvement of UK-based companies in supply chains delivering jet fuel to Myanmar that could be used by the military in that country.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>61</Number>
        <UIN>26684</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>John Healey</Member>
        <Constituency>Wentworth and Dearne</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Deputy Foreign Secretary, whether he has had discussions with his counterparts in (a) the US and (b) France on the war in Sudan since the start of that conflict.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>62</Number>
        <UIN>26657</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>John Healey</Member>
        <Constituency>Wentworth and Dearne</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Deputy Foreign Secretary, how many (a) people and (b) entities connected to the Rapid Support Forces in Sudan have been sanctioned by the UK Government.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>63</Number>
        <UIN>26658</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>John Healey</Member>
        <Constituency>Wentworth and Dearne</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Deputy Foreign Secretary, what estimate his Department has made of the number of civilians killed in Sudan since the start of the civil war in that country.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>64</Number>
        <UIN>26659</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Michael Fabricant</Member>
        <Constituency>Lichfield</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will make it his policy to maintain routes to enable international students to (a) study and (b) make an economic contribution to the UK.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Home Office</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>65</Number>
        <UIN>26639</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Damien Moore</Member>
        <Constituency>Southport</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what progress his Department has made on ending the use of seaside hotels for housing asylum seekers.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Home Office</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>66</Number>
        <UIN>26726</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Alison Thewliss</Member>
        <Constituency>Glasgow Central</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of people who have been served with notices of intent for removal to Rwanda are (a) women and (b) unaccompanied children.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Home Office</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>67</Number>
        <UIN>26697</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Alison Thewliss</Member>
        <Constituency>Glasgow Central</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many unaccompanied children are recorded as missing from asylum hotels as of 16 May 2024.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Home Office</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>68</Number>
        <UIN>26698</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Catherine West</Member>
        <Constituency>Hornsey and Wood Green</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether he has had recent discussions with representatives of the mobile phone industry on using technology to prevent stolen phones from being re-used.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Home Office</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>69</Number>
        <UIN>26708</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>John Healey</Member>
        <Constituency>Wentworth and Dearne</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much funding his Department has (a) allocated to and (b) spent on the DragonFire programme.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Ministry of Defence</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>70</Number>
        <UIN>26644</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>John Healey</Member>
        <Constituency>Wentworth and Dearne</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many DragonFire systems are planned to enter service in the Royal Navy in (a) 2027, (b) 2028, (c) 2029 and (d) 2030.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Ministry of Defence</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>71</Number>
        <UIN>26645</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>John Healey</Member>
        <Constituency>Wentworth and Dearne</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to his speech at the First Sea Lord’s Sea Power conference on 14 May 2024, what the planned timetable is for the multi-role support ships reaching (a) initial and (b) full operating capability.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Ministry of Defence</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>72</Number>
        <UIN>26647</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>John Healey</Member>
        <Constituency>Wentworth and Dearne</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Answer of 16 December 2021 to Question 91847 on Navy: Shipping, what the whole life costs are for this programme.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Ministry of Defence</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>73</Number>
        <UIN>26651</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>John Healey</Member>
        <Constituency>Wentworth and Dearne</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many shipbuilding contracts have been awarded to industry since the National Shipbuilding Strategy Refresh was published.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Ministry of Defence</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>74</Number>
        <UIN>26652</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>John Healey</Member>
        <Constituency>Wentworth and Dearne</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many officials in his Department work on the Sudan desk as of 16 May 2024.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Ministry of Defence</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>75</Number>
        <UIN>26653</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>John Healey</Member>
        <Constituency>Wentworth and Dearne</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, where the UK defence attaché for Sudan is based.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Ministry of Defence</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>76</Number>
        <UIN>26654</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>John Healey</Member>
        <Constituency>Wentworth and Dearne</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many meetings Ministers in his Department have had with the Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office on the civil war in Sudan.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Ministry of Defence</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>77</Number>
        <UIN>26655</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>John Healey</Member>
        <Constituency>Wentworth and Dearne</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether he has had discussions with his counterparts in (a) the US and (b) France on the war in Sudan since the start of that conflict.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Ministry of Defence</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>78</Number>
        <UIN>26656</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>John Healey</Member>
        <Constituency>Wentworth and Dearne</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether officials in his Department are supporting the work of the Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office to de-escalate the civil war in Sudan.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Ministry of Defence</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>79</Number>
        <UIN>26660</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>John Healey</Member>
        <Constituency>Wentworth and Dearne</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department has a joint working group on Sudan with the Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Ministry of Defence</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>80</Number>
        <UIN>26661</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Damien Moore</Member>
        <Constituency>Southport</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to increase value for money in procurement.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Ministry of Defence</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>81</Number>
        <UIN>26735</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Damien Moore</Member>
        <Constituency>Southport</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of procuring (CTOL) F-35A aircraft.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Ministry of Defence</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>82</Number>
        <UIN>26736</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Luke Pollard</Member>
        <Constituency>Plymouth, Sutton and Devonport</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many service personnel are based at Royal Military Academy Sandhurst as of May 2024.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Ministry of Defence</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>83</Number>
        <UIN>26742</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Luke Pollard</Member>
        <Constituency>Plymouth, Sutton and Devonport</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many service personnel are based at Normandy Barracks as of May 2024.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Ministry of Defence</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>84</Number>
        <UIN>26743</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Luke Pollard</Member>
        <Constituency>Plymouth, Sutton and Devonport</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many service personnel are based at New Normandy Barracks as of May 2024.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Ministry of Defence</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>85</Number>
        <UIN>26744</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Luke Pollard</Member>
        <Constituency>Plymouth, Sutton and Devonport</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many service personnel are based at Saint Omer Barracks as of May 2024.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Ministry of Defence</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>86</Number>
        <UIN>26745</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Luke Pollard</Member>
        <Constituency>Plymouth, Sutton and Devonport</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many service personnel are based at Duchess of Kent Barracks as of May 2024.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Ministry of Defence</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>87</Number>
        <UIN>26746</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Luke Pollard</Member>
        <Constituency>Plymouth, Sutton and Devonport</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many service personnel are based at Browning Barracks as of May 2024.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Ministry of Defence</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>88</Number>
        <UIN>26747</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Luke Pollard</Member>
        <Constituency>Plymouth, Sutton and Devonport</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many service personnel are based at Thornhill Barracks as of May 2024.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Ministry of Defence</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>89</Number>
        <UIN>26748</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Luke Pollard</Member>
        <Constituency>Plymouth, Sutton and Devonport</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many service personnel are based at Provost Barracks as of May 2024.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Ministry of Defence</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>90</Number>
        <UIN>26749</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Luke Pollard</Member>
        <Constituency>Plymouth, Sutton and Devonport</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many service personnel are based at Ordnance Barracks as of May 2024.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Ministry of Defence</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>91</Number>
        <UIN>26750</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Luke Pollard</Member>
        <Constituency>Plymouth, Sutton and Devonport</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many service personnel are based at Mons Barracks as of May 2024.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Ministry of Defence</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>92</Number>
        <UIN>26751</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Luke Pollard</Member>
        <Constituency>Plymouth, Sutton and Devonport</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many service personnel are based at Lille Barracks as of May 2024.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Ministry of Defence</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>93</Number>
        <UIN>26752</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Luke Pollard</Member>
        <Constituency>Plymouth, Sutton and Devonport</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many service personnel are based at Hammersley Barracks as of May 2024.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Ministry of Defence</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>94</Number>
        <UIN>26753</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Luke Pollard</Member>
        <Constituency>Plymouth, Sutton and Devonport</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many service personnel are based at Gibraltar Barracks as of May 2024.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Ministry of Defence</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>95</Number>
        <UIN>26754</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Luke Pollard</Member>
        <Constituency>Plymouth, Sutton and Devonport</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many service personnel are based at Denison Barracks as of May 2024.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Ministry of Defence</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>96</Number>
        <UIN>26755</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Luke Pollard</Member>
        <Constituency>Plymouth, Sutton and Devonport</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many service personnel are based at Combermere Barracks as of May 2024.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Ministry of Defence</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>97</Number>
        <UIN>26756</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Fleur Anderson</Member>
        <Constituency>Putney</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent steps his Department has taken to improve the (a) practical and (b) emotional support provided to (i) families and (ii) other witnesses attending the Coroners’ Courts.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Ministry of Justice</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>98</Number>
        <UIN>26765</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Fleur Anderson</Member>
        <Constituency>Putney</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent assessment his Department has made of the effectiveness of the (a) practical and (b) emotional support provided to (i) families and (ii) other witnesses attending the Coroners’ Courts.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Ministry of Justice</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>99</Number>
        <UIN>26766</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Fleur Anderson</Member>
        <Constituency>Putney</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether his Department has had recent discussions with the Coroners Courts Support Service on taking steps to improve the (a) practical and (b) emotional support provided to (i) families and (ii) other witnesses attending the Coroners’ Courts.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Ministry of Justice</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>100</Number>
        <UIN>26767</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Fleur Anderson</Member>
        <Constituency>Putney</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent steps his Department has taken to help tackle delays at Coroners’ Courts.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Ministry of Justice</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>101</Number>
        <UIN>26768</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi</Member>
        <Constituency>Slough</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether she has made a recent assessment of the adequacy of legal aid provision for immigration cases.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Ministry of Justice</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>102</Number>
        <UIN>26716</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi</Member>
        <Constituency>Slough</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prison officers have been investigated for drug smuggling in the last five years.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Ministry of Justice</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>103</Number>
        <UIN>26717</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi</Member>
        <Constituency>Slough</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of funding for criminal defence solicitors.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Ministry of Justice</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>104</Number>
        <UIN>26718</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi</Member>
        <Constituency>Slough</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what data his Department holds on the number of criminal legal aid firms that have ceased operations in each of the last 15 years.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Ministry of Justice</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>105</Number>
        <UIN>26825</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Rachel Hopkins</Member>
        <Constituency>Luton South</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many requests were completed by frontline HM Prison and Probation Service staff for prisoners to be exempted from the End of Custody Supervised Licence scheme in each month since October 2023; and how many and what proportion of these requests were granted by senior HM Prison and Probation Service managers.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Ministry of Justice</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>106</Number>
        <UIN>26798</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Rachel Hopkins</Member>
        <Constituency>Luton South</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many qualified probation officers were in post at the end of March in each year since 2020.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Ministry of Justice</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>107</Number>
        <UIN>26799</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Rachel Hopkins</Member>
        <Constituency>Luton South</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent assessment he has made of the impact of the Target Operating Model on Divisional Sex Offender Units.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Ministry of Justice</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>108</Number>
        <UIN>26800</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Sir John Hayes</Member>
        <Constituency>South Holland and The Deepings</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how many and what proportion of (a) cars and (b) other vehicles used by his Department were made in Britain.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Scotland Office</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>109</Number>
        <UIN>26641</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Fleur Anderson</Member>
        <Constituency>Putney</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many (a) promoters and (b) operators of schemes subject to the loan charge have been prosecuted.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Treasury</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>110</Number>
        <UIN>26769</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Fleur Anderson</Member>
        <Constituency>Putney</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make an estimate of the number of people who will need to sell their home to pay the loan charge.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Treasury</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>111</Number>
        <UIN>26770</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Fleur Anderson</Member>
        <Constituency>Putney</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what fiscal steps his Department is taking to help support people on lower incomes.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Treasury</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>112</Number>
        <UIN>26773</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Gen Kitchen</Member>
        <Constituency>Wellingborough</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what data his Department holds on the number of people in Wellingborough constituency who (a) paid national insurance contributions and (b) earned below £25,000 per year in financial year 2022-23.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Treasury</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>113</Number>
        <UIN>26814</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Gen Kitchen</Member>
        <Constituency>Wellingborough</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many high street businesses in (a) Wellingborough constituency, (b) Northamptonshire and (c) England have closed in each of the last five years; and what plans he has for business rates in the next five years.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Treasury</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>114</Number>
        <UIN>26815</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Gen Kitchen</Member>
        <Constituency>Wellingborough</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make an assessment of the potential impact of bank closures on access to (a) cash and (b) in-person services in Wellingborough constituency.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Treasury</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>115</Number>
        <UIN>26816</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Gen Kitchen</Member>
        <Constituency>Wellingborough</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make an estimate of the number of bank branches that have closed in (a) Wellingborough constituency and (b) Northamptonshire in each year since 2010.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Treasury</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>116</Number>
        <UIN>26817</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Gen Kitchen</Member>
        <Constituency>Wellingborough</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to help support people on lower incomes in Wellingborough constituency.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Treasury</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>117</Number>
        <UIN>26818</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Gen Kitchen</Member>
        <Constituency>Wellingborough</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will take steps to help ensure free access to cash (a) withdrawal and (b) deposit facilities in Wellingborough constituency.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Treasury</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>118</Number>
        <UIN>26819</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Gen Kitchen</Member>
        <Constituency>Wellingborough</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make an assessment of the potential impact of trends in mortgage interest rates on household disposable income in (a) Wellingborough constituency, (b) Northamptonshire and (c) England.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Treasury</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>119</Number>
        <UIN>26820</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Gen Kitchen</Member>
        <Constituency>Wellingborough</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make an assessment of the potential impact of increases in the cost of living on trends in the number of (a) businesses at risk of insolvency and (b) people in debt in Wellingborough constituency; and what fiscal steps he is taking to support these (i) businesses and (ii) people.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Treasury</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>120</Number>
        <UIN>26821</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Damien Moore</Member>
        <Constituency>Southport</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what fiscal steps he is taking to support coastal communities with tourism industries in summer 2024.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Treasury</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>121</Number>
        <UIN>26733</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Damien Moore</Member>
        <Constituency>Southport</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what fiscal steps he is taking to support golf (a) courses and (b) clubs in Southport.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Treasury</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>122</Number>
        <UIN>26734</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Sir John Hayes</Member>
        <Constituency>South Holland and The Deepings</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how many and what proportion of (a) cars and (b) other vehicles used by his Department were made in Britain.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Wales Office</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>123</Number>
        <UIN>26640</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Damien Moore</Member>
        <Constituency>Southport</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what steps her Department is taking to help promote community cohesion in (a) towns and (b) cities.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Women and Equalities</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>124</Number>
        <UIN>26727</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>ORDINARY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
    </Questions>
    <QuestionType>Written</QuestionType>
    <ContainsWithdrawnQuestions>false</ContainsWithdrawnQuestions>
  </QuestionBlock>
  <QuestionBlock>
    <Date>2024-05-21</Date>
    <Description>Questions for Written Answer</Description>
    <Questions>
      <Question>
        <Member>Miss Sarah Dines</Member>
        <Constituency>Derbyshire Dales</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Attorney General, with reference to the Answer of 20 January 2023 to Question 125287 on Rape: Prosecutions, how many (a) completed prosecutions and (b) convictions there were for sexual offences in each quarter from the start of January 2005 to the end of September 2015.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Attorney General</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>1</Number>
        <UIN>26789</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>NAMEDDAY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Miss Sarah Dines</Member>
        <Constituency>Derbyshire Dales</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Attorney General, with reference to the Answer of 20 January 2023 to Question 125287 on Rape: Prosecutions, how many (a) completed prosecutions and (b) convictions there were for rape in each quarter from the start of January 2005 to the end of September 2015.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Attorney General</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>2</Number>
        <UIN>26790</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>NAMEDDAY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Kenny MacAskill</Member>
        <Constituency>East Lothian</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 15 May 2024 to Question 25364 on Bahrain: Official Visits, whether any (a) Departments, (b) agencies and (c) public bodies were responsible for (i) arranging, (ii) coordinating and (iii) advising the meeting between Prince Salman bin Hamad Al Khalifa and HM the King on 3 May 2024.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Cabinet Office</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>3</Number>
        <UIN>26763</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>NAMEDDAY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Fabian Hamilton</Member>
        <Constituency>Leeds North East</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will have discussions with the Secretary of State for Levelling Up, Housing and Communities on making funding available to Leeds City Council to ensure the continuation of Little Owls nursery provision.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Education</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>4</Number>
        <UIN>26664</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>NAMEDDAY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Seema Malhotra</Member>
        <Constituency>Feltham and Heston</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many funded enrolments there were on each of the courses for 16 to 19 year olds that will have funding withdrawn after 1 August 2024 in each financial year since 2021-22.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Education</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>5</Number>
        <UIN>26685</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>NAMEDDAY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Chi Onwurah</Member>
        <Constituency>Newcastle upon Tyne Central</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of trends in the level of funding for schools in (a) Newcastle upon Tyne Central constituency, (b) Newcastle upon Tyne and (c) the North East since 2010.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Education</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>6</Number>
        <UIN>26683</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>NAMEDDAY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Alistair Strathern</Member>
        <Constituency>Mid Bedfordshire</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what progress her Department has made on the implementation of the National Kinship Care Strategy.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Education</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>7</Number>
        <UIN>26804</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>NAMEDDAY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Alistair Strathern</Member>
        <Constituency>Mid Bedfordshire</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what progress her Department has made on the implementation of the financial allowance pathfinder.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Education</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>8</Number>
        <UIN>26805</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>NAMEDDAY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Alistair Strathern</Member>
        <Constituency>Mid Bedfordshire</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when she plans to announce the eight local authorities selected for the financial allowance pathfinder.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Education</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>9</Number>
        <UIN>26806</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>NAMEDDAY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Dave Doogan</Member>
        <Constituency>Angus</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what her planned timetable is for announcing the final revised budget for contracts for difference allocation round six.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Energy Security and Net Zero</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>10</Number>
        <UIN>26758</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>NAMEDDAY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Grahame Morris</Member>
        <Constituency>Easington</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, how much revenue the Exchequer has received from the British Coal Staff Superannuation Fund since 1994.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Energy Security and Net Zero</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>11</Number>
        <UIN>26672</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>NAMEDDAY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Grahame Morris</Member>
        <Constituency>Easington</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, how many former employees were recipients of the British Coal Staff Superannuation Scheme in (a) Easington constituency and (b) the UK in May 2024.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Energy Security and Net Zero</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>12</Number>
        <UIN>26673</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>NAMEDDAY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Grahame Morris</Member>
        <Constituency>Easington</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, pursuant to the Answer of 14 November 2023 to Question 1095 on Mineworkers' Pension Scheme, if she will take steps to calculate how many of the 23,974 spouse/dependant pensioners in the Mineworkers’ Pension Scheme reside in (a) Easington constituency and (b) the North East.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Energy Security and Net Zero</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>13</Number>
        <UIN>26674</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>NAMEDDAY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Helen Morgan</Member>
        <Constituency>North Shropshire</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Levelling Up, Housing and Communities, what assessment his Department has made of the potential impact of social rented properties which do not include floor coverings in all habitable rooms on the health of tenants.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Levelling Up, Housing and Communities</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>14</Number>
        <UIN>26801</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>NAMEDDAY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Helen Morgan</Member>
        <Constituency>North Shropshire</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Levelling Up, Housing and Communities, whether he has had discussions with (a) housing associations and (b) local authorities on the full provision of flooring social housing.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Levelling Up, Housing and Communities</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>15</Number>
        <UIN>26802</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>NAMEDDAY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Simon Lightwood</Member>
        <Constituency>Wakefield</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 18 April 2024 to Question 21868 on Buses: Carbon Emissions, how many and what proportion of the buses allocated funding under the Zero Emission Bus Regional Areas scheme 1 (a) are on the road in each local transport authority and (b) (i) have been and (ii) will be manufactured in the UK.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Transport</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>16</Number>
        <UIN>26803</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>NAMEDDAY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Chi Onwurah</Member>
        <Constituency>Newcastle upon Tyne Central</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment he has made of the (a) standard of wifi services provided by train operators, (b) trends in the standards of that service over the last three years and (c) effectiveness of incentives for train operators to provide high quality wifi services.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Transport</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>17</Number>
        <UIN>26680</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>NAMEDDAY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Chi Onwurah</Member>
        <Constituency>Newcastle upon Tyne Central</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to table 6 of his Department’s publication entitled Child Maintenance Service statistics: data to December 2023, published on 26 March 2024, how much child maintenance had not been paid and needed to be collected through Collect and Pay in (a) each nation, (b) each region and (c) Newcastle Central constituency as of 31 December 2023.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Work and Pensions</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>18</Number>
        <UIN>26681</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>NAMEDDAY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Derek Thomas</Member>
        <Constituency>St Ives</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department is taking to publicise the online system for (a) checking the completeness of National Insurance records and (b) paying voluntary National Insurance contributions.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Work and Pensions</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>19</Number>
        <UIN>26709</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>NAMEDDAY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Fabian Hamilton</Member>
        <Constituency>Leeds North East</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether her Department (a) has and (b) plans to provide funding for new treatments for ME or chronic fatigue syndrome.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department of Health and Social Care</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>20</Number>
        <UIN>26662</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>NAMEDDAY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Fabian Hamilton</Member>
        <Constituency>Leeds North East</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if she will make an assessment of the adequacy of NHS provision of specialist ME or chronic fatigue syndrome services; and if she will take steps to increase the number of clinicians who specialise in ME or chronic fatigue syndrome.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department of Health and Social Care</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>21</Number>
        <UIN>26663</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>NAMEDDAY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Karin Smyth</Member>
        <Constituency>Bristol South</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many and what proportion of (a) CT and (b) MRI scanners have been in operation for longer than 10 years.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department of Health and Social Care</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>22</Number>
        <UIN>26699</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>NAMEDDAY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Karin Smyth</Member>
        <Constituency>Bristol South</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many IT failures there have been at NHS trusts in each of the last five years.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department of Health and Social Care</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>23</Number>
        <UIN>26700</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>NAMEDDAY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Karin Smyth</Member>
        <Constituency>Bristol South</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many IT failures there have been at NHS trusts that affected clinical service delivery in each of the last five years.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department of Health and Social Care</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>24</Number>
        <UIN>26701</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>NAMEDDAY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Neil Coyle</Member>
        <Constituency>Bermondsey and Old Southwark</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Deputy Foreign Secretary, what steps he has taken to tackle the People’s Republic of China’s security and intelligence network operating in the UK in response to the arrest of three alleged spies.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>25</Number>
        <UIN>26687</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>NAMEDDAY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Neil Coyle</Member>
        <Constituency>Bermondsey and Old Southwark</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Deputy Foreign Secretary, what steps his Department is taking to ensure compliance with sanctions against Russia by (a) JCB and (b) other companies.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>26</Number>
        <UIN>26688</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>NAMEDDAY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Kenny MacAskill</Member>
        <Constituency>East Lothian</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Deputy Foreign Secretary, pursuant to the Answer of 14 May 2024 to Question 24574 on Bahrain: Political Prisoners, if he will list the individual human rights cases discussed with Bahrain Foreign Minister Al Zayani on 22 April 2024.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>27</Number>
        <UIN>26762</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>NAMEDDAY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Michael Fabricant</Member>
        <Constituency>Lichfield</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of the potential implications for his policies of the report by the Migration Advisory Committee entitled Rapid review of the graduate route, published in May 2024; and whether he plans to implement each of the recommendations in full.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Home Office</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>28</Number>
        <UIN>26638</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>NAMEDDAY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Sarah Olney</Member>
        <Constituency>Richmond Park</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to page 64 of the Migration Advisory Committee's report entitled, Rapid Review of the Graduate Route, published on 14 May 2024, if she will take steps to implement the recommendation on establishing a mandatory registration system for international recruitment agents and subagents.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Home Office</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>29</Number>
        <UIN>26711</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>NAMEDDAY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Sarah Olney</Member>
        <Constituency>Richmond Park</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to page 64 of the Migration Advisory Committee's report entitled, Rapid Review of the Graduate Route, published on 14 May 2024, if she will take steps to implement the recommendation on requiring universities to publish data on (a) their spend on recruitment agents and (b) the number of international students recruited through such agents.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Home Office</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>30</Number>
        <UIN>26712</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>NAMEDDAY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Nadia Whittome</Member>
        <Constituency>Nottingham East</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will implement a visa scheme to enable Palestinian children to receive critical medical treatment in the UK.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Home Office</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>31</Number>
        <UIN>26792</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>NAMEDDAY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>John Healey</Member>
        <Constituency>Wentworth and Dearne</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much he plans to allocate to spending on defence R&amp;D in each year to 2030.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Ministry of Defence</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>32</Number>
        <UIN>26643</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>NAMEDDAY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>John Healey</Member>
        <Constituency>Wentworth and Dearne</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to his speech at the First Sea Lord’s Sea Power conference on 14 May 2024, how much funding his Department has allocated for the construction of six new multi-role support ships.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Ministry of Defence</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>33</Number>
        <UIN>26646</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>NAMEDDAY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>John Healey</Member>
        <Constituency>Wentworth and Dearne</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to his speech at the First Sea Lord’s Sea Power conference on 14 May 2024, what the planned in-service date is for the multi-role support ships.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Ministry of Defence</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>34</Number>
        <UIN>26648</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>NAMEDDAY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>John Healey</Member>
        <Constituency>Wentworth and Dearne</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what is the average salary was for service staff at each Royal Fleet Auxilliary rank in each year since 2010.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Ministry of Defence</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>35</Number>
        <UIN>26649</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>NAMEDDAY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>John Healey</Member>
        <Constituency>Wentworth and Dearne</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Answer of 16 December 2021 to Question 91847 on Navy: Shipping, whether that contract has now been awarded.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Ministry of Defence</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>36</Number>
        <UIN>26650</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>NAMEDDAY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Luke Pollard</Member>
        <Constituency>Plymouth, Sutton and Devonport</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much his Department has spent on improving service accommodation at Aldershot Garrison since April 2022.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Ministry of Defence</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>37</Number>
        <UIN>26737</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>NAMEDDAY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Luke Pollard</Member>
        <Constituency>Plymouth, Sutton and Devonport</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many service personnel are based at Aldershot Garrison as of May 2024.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Ministry of Defence</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>38</Number>
        <UIN>26738</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>NAMEDDAY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Luke Pollard</Member>
        <Constituency>Plymouth, Sutton and Devonport</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many callouts have been made to Aldershot Garrison for maintenance issues relating to (a) roofing, (b) loss of heating and hot water, (c) electrics, (d) pest control and (e) damp and mould since April 2022.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Ministry of Defence</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>39</Number>
        <UIN>26739</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>NAMEDDAY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Luke Pollard</Member>
        <Constituency>Plymouth, Sutton and Devonport</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many callouts have been made to Royal Military Academy Sandhurst for maintenance issues relating to (a) roofing, (b) loss of heating and hot water, (c) electrics, (d) pest control and (e) damp and mould since April 2022.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Ministry of Defence</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>40</Number>
        <UIN>26740</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>NAMEDDAY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Luke Pollard</Member>
        <Constituency>Plymouth, Sutton and Devonport</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much his Department has spent on improving service accommodation at Royal Military Academy Sandhurst since April 2022.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Ministry of Defence</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>41</Number>
        <UIN>26741</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>NAMEDDAY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Dr Rosena Allin-Khan</Member>
        <Constituency>Tooting</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what information his Department holds on the secondment of police officers to cover shifts in Wandsworth Prison in the last 30 days.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Ministry of Justice</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>42</Number>
        <UIN>26710</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>NAMEDDAY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Ruth Cadbury</Member>
        <Constituency>Brentford and Isleworth</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many appearances in magistrates courts were delayed on (a) 15 and (b) 16 May 2024 as part of Operation Early Dawn.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Ministry of Justice</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>43</Number>
        <UIN>26690</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>NAMEDDAY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Ruth Cadbury</Member>
        <Constituency>Brentford and Isleworth</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether he has made an assessment of the potential risk to public safety of Operation Early Dawn.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Ministry of Justice</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>44</Number>
        <UIN>26691</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>NAMEDDAY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Ruth Cadbury</Member>
        <Constituency>Brentford and Isleworth</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether his Department consulted representatives of (a) magistrates and (b) solicitors before implementing Operation Early Dawn.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Ministry of Justice</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>45</Number>
        <UIN>26692</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>NAMEDDAY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Ruth Cadbury</Member>
        <Constituency>Brentford and Isleworth</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether beds of prisoners who have been released on temporary licence are counted as available for the purposes of determining capacity.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Ministry of Justice</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>46</Number>
        <UIN>26693</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>NAMEDDAY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Ruth Cadbury</Member>
        <Constituency>Brentford and Isleworth</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many vacancies there are in the probation service by region.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Ministry of Justice</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>47</Number>
        <UIN>26694</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>NAMEDDAY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Dave Doogan</Member>
        <Constituency>Angus</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make an assessment of the effectiveness of steps taken by (a) his Department and (b) the Department for Energy Security and Net Zero on ensuring that the Contracts for Difference Allocation Round 6 delivers more offshore wind capacity than Allocation Round 5.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Treasury</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>48</Number>
        <UIN>26757</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>NAMEDDAY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>James Murray</Member>
        <Constituency>Ealing North</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many incidents of tax fraud involving (a) the VAT484 form and (b) other paper forms HMRC has recorded in each of last five financial years; and what the (i) total and (ii) average value of those incidents is.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Treasury</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>49</Number>
        <UIN>26780</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>NAMEDDAY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>James Murray</Member>
        <Constituency>Ealing North</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, on what date (a) he and (b) HMRC first became aware of fraud involving the VAT484 form; and what steps he is taking to tackle such fraud.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Treasury</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>50</Number>
        <UIN>26781</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>NAMEDDAY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
    </Questions>
    <QuestionType>Written</QuestionType>
    <ContainsWithdrawnQuestions>false</ContainsWithdrawnQuestions>
  </QuestionBlock>
  <QuestionBlock>
    <Date>2024-05-22</Date>
    <Description>Questions for Written Answer</Description>
    <Questions>
      <Question>
        <Member>Alison McGovern</Member>
        <Constituency>Wirral South</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to his Department's statistics entitled Fraud and error in the benefit system, Financial Year Ending (FYE) 2024, published on 16 May 2024, how much of the £7.4 billion overpayment due to fraud is due to serious and organised crime.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Work and Pensions</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>1</Number>
        <UIN>26677</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>NAMEDDAY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Alison McGovern</Member>
        <Constituency>Wirral South</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what definition his Department uses for serious and organised crime.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Work and Pensions</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>2</Number>
        <UIN>26678</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>NAMEDDAY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Liz Twist</Member>
        <Constituency>Blaydon</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to table 3 of his Department's publication entitled Completing the move to Universal Credit: Statistics related to the move of households claiming Tax Credits and DWP Benefits to Universal Credit: data to end of March 2024, published on 14 May 2024, if he will break down this data by (a) each nation, (b) each region and (c) each local authority area in the North East.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Work and Pensions</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>3</Number>
        <UIN>26713</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>NAMEDDAY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Liz Twist</Member>
        <Constituency>Blaydon</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the publication Move to Universal Credit statistics, July 2022 to March 2024, published on 14 May 2024, if he will make an assessment of the reasons why over 180,000 Tax Credits claimants that have been sent a migration notice did not make a Universal Credit claim within the required timeframe.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Work and Pensions</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>4</Number>
        <UIN>26714</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>NAMEDDAY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Mr Nicholas Brown</Member>
        <Constituency>Newcastle upon Tyne East</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if (a) she and (b) a Minister in her Department will meet hon. Members representing Newcastle to discuss the findings of the report by the Care Quality Commission on the Newcastle upon Tyne Hospitals NHS Foundation Trust, published on 24 January 2024.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department of Health and Social Care</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>5</Number>
        <UIN>26665</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>NAMEDDAY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Mr Nicholas Brown</Member>
        <Constituency>Newcastle upon Tyne East</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent progress her Department has made on preparing a response to the principal findings of the report by the Care Quality Commission on the Newcastle upon Tyne Hospitals NHS Foundation Trust, published on 24 January 2024.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department of Health and Social Care</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>6</Number>
        <UIN>26666</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>NAMEDDAY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Navendu Mishra</Member>
        <Constituency>Stockport</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if she will make an assessment of the cost to the NHS of providing (a) treatment and (b) other support to patients with mental health conditions in each year since 1 January 2022; and if she will commission research on the potential impact of (i) social and (ii) economic factors on the prevalence of mental health conditions.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department of Health and Social Care</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>7</Number>
        <UIN>26783</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>NAMEDDAY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Navendu Mishra</Member>
        <Constituency>Stockport</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment her Department has made of the effectiveness of audiology services in England that have been outsourced to private providers by NHS (a) trusts and (b) integrated care boards.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department of Health and Social Care</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>8</Number>
        <UIN>26784</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>NAMEDDAY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Navendu Mishra</Member>
        <Constituency>Stockport</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what data her Department holds on the number of hydrotherapy centres (a) due to be closed and (b) under consideration for closure by NHS (i) trusts and (ii) integrated care boards.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department of Health and Social Care</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>9</Number>
        <UIN>26785</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>NAMEDDAY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Navendu Mishra</Member>
        <Constituency>Stockport</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps she is taking to ensure the adequacy of processing times for (a) applications for and (b) appeals relating to NHS Continuing Healthcare.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department of Health and Social Care</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>10</Number>
        <UIN>26786</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>NAMEDDAY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Neil Coyle</Member>
        <Constituency>Bermondsey and Old Southwark</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Deputy Foreign Secretary, whether his Department has made an assessment of the potential merits of rescinding diplomatic immunity from the Hong Kong Economic and Trade Office in the UK.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>11</Number>
        <UIN>26689</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>NAMEDDAY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Alison McGovern</Member>
        <Constituency>Wirral South</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether his Department plans to update the definition of serious and organised crime.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Home Office</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>12</Number>
        <UIN>26679</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>NAMEDDAY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Rachel Hopkins</Member>
        <Constituency>Luton South</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many and what proportion of people released on an End of Custody Supervised Licence were subsequently (a) recalled back to prison and (b) subject to a Death Under Supervision Review in each month since October 2023.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Ministry of Justice</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>13</Number>
        <UIN>26793</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>NAMEDDAY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Rachel Hopkins</Member>
        <Constituency>Luton South</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many and what proportion of people released on End of Custody Supervised Licence were assessed as posing a high risk of harm in each month since October 2023.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Ministry of Justice</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>14</Number>
        <UIN>26794</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>NAMEDDAY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Rachel Hopkins</Member>
        <Constituency>Luton South</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what information his Department holds on the number and proportion of prisoners that were released under the End of Custody Supervised License scheme who were homeless upon their release from prison in each month since October 2023.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Ministry of Justice</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>15</Number>
        <UIN>26795</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>NAMEDDAY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Rachel Hopkins</Member>
        <Constituency>Luton South</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many and what proportion of people released on an end of custody supervised licence were subject to a serious further offence review in each month since October 2023.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Ministry of Justice</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>16</Number>
        <UIN>26796</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>NAMEDDAY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Rachel Hopkins</Member>
        <Constituency>Luton South</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many Approved Premises referrals were submitted by probation staff to accommodate people released on an End of Custody Supervised Licence in each month since October 2023; and how many and what proportion of those referrals were rejected.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Ministry of Justice</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>17</Number>
        <UIN>26797</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>NAMEDDAY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Navendu Mishra</Member>
        <Constituency>Stockport</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will make an assessment of the potential impact of (a) staffing levels and (b) staff training on the time taken to process probate applications in each of the last 12 months.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Ministry of Justice</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>18</Number>
        <UIN>26787</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>NAMEDDAY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Dame Margaret Hodge</Member>
        <Constituency>Barking</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the oral contribution of the Minister of State, Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office, during the debate on Countering Iran’s Hostile Activities of 8 May 2024, Official Report, column 353WH, whether his Department has written to the Financial Conduct Authority on the operations of (a) Bank Melli and (b) Saderat Bank in the UK.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Treasury</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>19</Number>
        <UIN>26304</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>NAMEDDAY</Type>
        <IsTransfer>true</IsTransfer>
      </Question>
    </Questions>
    <QuestionType>Written</QuestionType>
    <ContainsWithdrawnQuestions>false</ContainsWithdrawnQuestions>
  </QuestionBlock>
  <QuestionBlock>
    <Date>2024-05-22</Date>
    <Time>11:30 am</Time>
    <Description>Oral Questions to the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology</Description>
    <Questions>
      <Question>
        <Member>Julian Sturdy</Member>
        <Constituency>York Outer</Constituency>
        <Text>What recent steps her Department has taken to improve internet connectivity.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Science, Innovation and Technology</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>1</Number>
        <UIN>903016</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>SUBSTANTIVE</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
        <Status>ToBeAsked</Status>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Mrs Paulette Hamilton</Member>
        <Constituency>Birmingham, Erdington</Constituency>
        <Text>What steps her Department is taking to help increase diversity and inclusion in the STEM workforce.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Science, Innovation and Technology</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>2</Number>
        <UIN>903017</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>SUBSTANTIVE</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
        <Status>ToBeAsked</Status>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Gary Sambrook</Member>
        <Constituency>Birmingham, Northfield</Constituency>
        <Text>What steps her Department is taking to support the life sciences manufacturing sector.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Science, Innovation and Technology</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>3</Number>
        <UIN>903018</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>SUBSTANTIVE</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
        <Status>ToBeAsked</Status>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Jerome Mayhew</Member>
        <Constituency>Broadland</Constituency>
        <Text>What recent steps her Department has taken to improve internet connectivity.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Science, Innovation and Technology</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>4</Number>
        <UIN>903019</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>SUBSTANTIVE</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
        <Status>ToBeAsked</Status>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Theresa Villiers</Member>
        <Constituency>Chipping Barnet</Constituency>
        <Text>What steps she is taking with Cabinet colleagues to ensure that Government-funded research is used to help increase levels of productivity.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Science, Innovation and Technology</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>5</Number>
        <UIN>903020</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>SUBSTANTIVE</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
        <Status>ToBeAsked</Status>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Simon Fell</Member>
        <Constituency>Barrow and Furness</Constituency>
        <Text>What steps her Department is taking to improve rural connectivity.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Science, Innovation and Technology</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>6</Number>
        <UIN>903021</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>SUBSTANTIVE</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
        <Status>ToBeAsked</Status>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Selaine Saxby</Member>
        <Constituency>North Devon</Constituency>
        <Text>What recent steps her Department has taken to improve internet connectivity.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Science, Innovation and Technology</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>7</Number>
        <UIN>903022</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>SUBSTANTIVE</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
        <Status>ToBeAsked</Status>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Richard Foord</Member>
        <Constituency>Tiverton and Honiton</Constituency>
        <Text>What steps her Department is taking to help tackle digital exclusion.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Science, Innovation and Technology</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>8</Number>
        <UIN>903023</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>SUBSTANTIVE</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
        <Status>ToBeAsked</Status>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Matt Hancock</Member>
        <Constituency>West Suffolk</Constituency>
        <Text>What steps she is taking to help support the development of AI.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Science, Innovation and Technology</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>9</Number>
        <UIN>903024</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>SUBSTANTIVE</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
        <Status>ToBeAsked</Status>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Andrew Rosindell</Member>
        <Constituency>Romford</Constituency>
        <Text>What steps her Department is taking to help reduce the use of animal testing in research.  </Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Science, Innovation and Technology</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>10</Number>
        <UIN>903025</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>SUBSTANTIVE</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
        <Status>ToBeAsked</Status>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Kim Johnson</Member>
        <Constituency>Liverpool, Riverside</Constituency>
        <Text>What steps her Department is taking to help increase diversity and inclusion in the STEM workforce.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Science, Innovation and Technology</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>11</Number>
        <UIN>903026</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>SUBSTANTIVE</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
        <Status>ToBeAsked</Status>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Duncan Baker</Member>
        <Constituency>North Norfolk</Constituency>
        <Text>If she will make an assessment of the potential merits of updating the Code of practice for wireless network development in England to make it easier for rural communities to get new mobile phone masts erected.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Science, Innovation and Technology</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>12</Number>
        <UIN>903027</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>SUBSTANTIVE</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
        <Status>ToBeAsked</Status>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Vicky Ford</Member>
        <Constituency>Chelmsford</Constituency>
        <Text>What steps her Department is taking to help protect children online.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Science, Innovation and Technology</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>13</Number>
        <UIN>903028</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>SUBSTANTIVE</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
        <Status>ToBeAsked</Status>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Kenny MacAskill</Member>
        <Constituency>East Lothian</Constituency>
        <Text>What recent discussions she has had with Cabinet colleagues on the potential impact of the Net Zero Research and Innovation Delivery Plan on the UK's target to become a science and technology superpower by 2030.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Science, Innovation and Technology</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>14</Number>
        <UIN>903029</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>SUBSTANTIVE</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
        <Status>ToBeAsked</Status>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Gen Kitchen</Member>
        <Constituency>Wellingborough</Constituency>
        <Text>What steps her Department is taking to help tackle digital exclusion among low-income households.
</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Science, Innovation and Technology</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>15</Number>
        <UIN>903030</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>SUBSTANTIVE</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
        <Status>ToBeAsked</Status>
      </Question>
    </Questions>
    <QuestionType>Substantive Oral</QuestionType>
    <ContainsWithdrawnQuestions>false</ContainsWithdrawnQuestions>
  </QuestionBlock>
  <QuestionBlock>
    <Date>2024-05-22</Date>
    <Time>11:53 am</Time>
    <Description>Topical Questions to the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology</Description>
    <Questions>
      <Question>
        <Member>Chris Elmore</Member>
        <Constituency>Ogmore</Constituency>
        <Text>If she will make a statement on her departmental responsibilities.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Science, Innovation and Technology</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>1</Number>
        <UIN>903031</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>TOPICAL</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
        <Status>ToBeAsked</Status>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Andrew Bridgen</Member>
        <Constituency>North West Leicestershire</Constituency>
        <Text>If she will make a statement on her departmental responsibilities.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Science, Innovation and Technology</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>2</Number>
        <UIN>903032</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>TOPICAL</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
        <Status>ToBeAsked</Status>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Simon Baynes</Member>
        <Constituency>Clwyd South</Constituency>
        <Text>If she will make a statement on her departmental responsibilities.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Science, Innovation and Technology</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>3</Number>
        <UIN>903033</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>TOPICAL</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
        <Status>ToBeAsked</Status>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Mrs Paulette Hamilton</Member>
        <Constituency>Birmingham, Erdington</Constituency>
        <Text>If she will make a statement on her departmental responsibilities.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Science, Innovation and Technology</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>4</Number>
        <UIN>903034</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>TOPICAL</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
        <Status>ToBeAsked</Status>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Marco Longhi</Member>
        <Constituency>Dudley North</Constituency>
        <Text>If she will make a statement on her departmental responsibilities.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Science, Innovation and Technology</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>5</Number>
        <UIN>903035</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>TOPICAL</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
        <Status>ToBeAsked</Status>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Kim Johnson</Member>
        <Constituency>Liverpool, Riverside</Constituency>
        <Text>If she will make a statement on her departmental responsibilities.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Science, Innovation and Technology</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>6</Number>
        <UIN>903036</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>TOPICAL</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
        <Status>ToBeAsked</Status>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Sarah Dyke</Member>
        <Constituency>Somerton and Frome</Constituency>
        <Text>If she will make a statement on her departmental responsibilities.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Science, Innovation and Technology</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>7</Number>
        <UIN>903037</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>TOPICAL</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
        <Status>ToBeAsked</Status>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Duncan Baker</Member>
        <Constituency>North Norfolk</Constituency>
        <Text>If she will make a statement on her departmental responsibilities.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Science, Innovation and Technology</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>8</Number>
        <UIN>903038</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>TOPICAL</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
        <Status>ToBeAsked</Status>
      </Question>
    </Questions>
    <QuestionType>Topical Oral</QuestionType>
    <ContainsWithdrawnQuestions>false</ContainsWithdrawnQuestions>
  </QuestionBlock>
  <QuestionBlock>
    <Date>2024-05-22</Date>
    <Time>12:00 pm</Time>
    <Description>Oral Questions to the Prime Minister</Description>
    <Questions>
      <Question>
        <Member>Gen Kitchen</Member>
        <Constituency>Wellingborough</Constituency>
        <Text>If he will list his official engagements for Wednesday 22 May.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Prime Minister</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>1</Number>
        <UIN>903001</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>SUBSTANTIVE</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
        <Status>ToBeAsked</Status>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Elliot Colburn</Member>
        <Constituency>Carshalton and Wallington</Constituency>
        <Text>If he will list his official engagements for Wednesday 22 May.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Prime Minister</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>2</Number>
        <UIN>903002</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>SUBSTANTIVE</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
        <Status>ToBeAsked</Status>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Danny Kruger</Member>
        <Constituency>Devizes</Constituency>
        <Text>If he will list his official engagements for Wednesday 22 May.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Prime Minister</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>3</Number>
        <UIN>903003</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>SUBSTANTIVE</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
        <Status>ToBeAsked</Status>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Simon Baynes</Member>
        <Constituency>Clwyd South</Constituency>
        <Text>If he will list his official engagements for Wednesday 22 May.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Prime Minister</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>4</Number>
        <UIN>903004</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>SUBSTANTIVE</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
        <Status>ToBeAsked</Status>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Shailesh Vara</Member>
        <Constituency>North West Cambridgeshire</Constituency>
        <Text>If he will list his official engagements for Wednesday 22 May.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Prime Minister</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>5</Number>
        <UIN>903005</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>SUBSTANTIVE</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
        <Status>ToBeAsked</Status>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Sir John Whittingdale</Member>
        <Constituency>Maldon</Constituency>
        <Text>If he will list his official engagements for Wednesday 22 May.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Prime Minister</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>6</Number>
        <UIN>903006</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>SUBSTANTIVE</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
        <Status>ToBeAsked</Status>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Alison Thewliss</Member>
        <Constituency>Glasgow Central</Constituency>
        <Text>If he will list his official engagements for Wednesday 22 May.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Prime Minister</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>7</Number>
        <UIN>903007</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>SUBSTANTIVE</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
        <Status>ToBeAsked</Status>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Janet Daby</Member>
        <Constituency>Lewisham East</Constituency>
        <Text>If he will list his official engagements for Wednesday 22 May.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Prime Minister</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>8</Number>
        <UIN>903008</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>SUBSTANTIVE</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
        <Status>ToBeAsked</Status>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Tom Randall</Member>
        <Constituency>Gedling</Constituency>
        <Text>If he will list his official engagements for Wednesday 22 May.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Prime Minister</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>9</Number>
        <UIN>903009</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>SUBSTANTIVE</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
        <Status>ToBeAsked</Status>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Kate Osborne</Member>
        <Constituency>Jarrow</Constituency>
        <Text>If he will list his official engagements for Wednesday 22 May.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Prime Minister</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>10</Number>
        <UIN>903010</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>SUBSTANTIVE</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
        <Status>ToBeAsked</Status>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Will Quince</Member>
        <Constituency>Colchester</Constituency>
        <Text>If he will list his official engagements for Wednesday 22 May.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Prime Minister</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>11</Number>
        <UIN>903011</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>SUBSTANTIVE</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
        <Status>ToBeAsked</Status>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Mr John Baron</Member>
        <Constituency>Basildon and Billericay</Constituency>
        <Text>If he will list his official engagements for Wednesday 22 May.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Prime Minister</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>12</Number>
        <UIN>903012</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>SUBSTANTIVE</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
        <Status>ToBeAsked</Status>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Bell Ribeiro-Addy</Member>
        <Constituency>Streatham</Constituency>
        <Text>If he will list his official engagements for Wednesday 22 May.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Prime Minister</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>13</Number>
        <UIN>903013</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>SUBSTANTIVE</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
        <Status>ToBeAsked</Status>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Stephen Farry</Member>
        <Constituency>North Down</Constituency>
        <Text>If he will list his official engagements for Wednesday 22 May.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Prime Minister</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>14</Number>
        <UIN>903014</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>SUBSTANTIVE</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
        <Status>ToBeAsked</Status>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Jason McCartney</Member>
        <Constituency>Colne Valley</Constituency>
        <Text>If he will list his official engagements for Wednesday 22 May.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Prime Minister</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>15</Number>
        <UIN>903015</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>SUBSTANTIVE</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
        <Status>ToBeAsked</Status>
      </Question>
    </Questions>
    <QuestionType>Substantive Oral</QuestionType>
    <ContainsWithdrawnQuestions>false</ContainsWithdrawnQuestions>
  </QuestionBlock>
  <QuestionBlock>
    <Date>2024-05-23</Date>
    <Time>10:00 am</Time>
    <Description>Topical Questions to the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport</Description>
    <Questions>
      <Question>
        <Member>Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck</Member>
        <Constituency>South Shields</Constituency>
        <Text>If she will make a statement on her departmental responsibilities.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Culture, Media and Sport</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>1</Number>
        <UIN>902993</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>TOPICAL</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
        <Status>ToBeAsked</Status>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Rob Butler</Member>
        <Constituency>Aylesbury</Constituency>
        <Text>If she will make a statement on her departmental responsibilities.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Culture, Media and Sport</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>2</Number>
        <UIN>902994</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>TOPICAL</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
        <Status>ToBeAsked</Status>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Rachel Maclean</Member>
        <Constituency>Redditch</Constituency>
        <Text>If she will make a statement on her departmental responsibilities.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Culture, Media and Sport</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>3</Number>
        <UIN>902995</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>TOPICAL</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
        <Status>ToBeAsked</Status>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Andrew Jones</Member>
        <Constituency>Harrogate and Knaresborough</Constituency>
        <Text>If she will make a statement on her departmental responsibilities.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Culture, Media and Sport</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>4</Number>
        <UIN>902996</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>TOPICAL</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
        <Status>ToBeAsked</Status>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Helen Hayes</Member>
        <Constituency>Dulwich and West Norwood</Constituency>
        <Text>If she will make a statement on her departmental responsibilities.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Culture, Media and Sport</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>5</Number>
        <UIN>902997</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>TOPICAL</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
        <Status>ToBeAsked</Status>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Kevin Foster</Member>
        <Constituency>Torbay</Constituency>
        <Text>If she will make a statement on her departmental responsibilities.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Culture, Media and Sport</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>6</Number>
        <UIN>902998</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>TOPICAL</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
        <Status>ToBeAsked</Status>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Steve Tuckwell</Member>
        <Constituency>Uxbridge and South Ruislip</Constituency>
        <Text>If she will make a statement on her departmental responsibilities.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Culture, Media and Sport</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>7</Number>
        <UIN>902999</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>TOPICAL</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
        <Status>ToBeAsked</Status>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Paul Howell</Member>
        <Constituency>Sedgefield</Constituency>
        <Text>If she will make a statement on her departmental responsibilities.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Culture, Media and Sport</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>8</Number>
        <UIN>903000</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>TOPICAL</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
        <Status>ToBeAsked</Status>
      </Question>
    </Questions>
    <QuestionType>Topical Oral</QuestionType>
    <ContainsWithdrawnQuestions>false</ContainsWithdrawnQuestions>
  </QuestionBlock>
  <QuestionBlock>
    <Date>2024-05-23</Date>
    <Time>10:10 am</Time>
    <Description>Oral Questions to the Chairman of the Public Accounts Commission and the hon. Member for Broxbourne, representing the House of Commons Commission and the hon. Member for Lancaster and Fleetwood, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission and the Member for South West Bedfordshire, representing the Church Commissioners</Description>
    <Questions>
      <Question>
        <Member>Mr David Jones</Member>
        <Constituency>Clwyd West</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Chairman of the Public Accounts Commission, if he will make an assessment of the adequacy of National Audit Office resources to scrutinise the cost of AI in government.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Public Accounts Commission</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>1</Number>
        <UIN>902963</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>SUBSTANTIVE</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
        <Status>ToBeAsked</Status>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Mr Philip Hollobone</Member>
        <Constituency>Kettering</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the Chairman of the Public Accounts Commission, if he will make an assessment of the adequacy of National Audit Office resources to undertake analysis on the efficiency and effectiveness of NHS procurement.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Public Accounts Commission</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>2</Number>
        <UIN>902964</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>SUBSTANTIVE</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
        <Status>ToBeAsked</Status>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Selaine Saxby</Member>
        <Constituency>North Devon</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the hon. Member for South West Bedfordshire, representing the Church Commissioners, whether the Church of England is taking steps to provide affordable and sustainable housing on its land.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Church Commissioners</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>3</Number>
        <UIN>902965</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>SUBSTANTIVE</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
        <Status>ToBeAsked</Status>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Kevin Foster</Member>
        <Constituency>Torbay</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the hon. Member for South West Bedfordshire, representing the Church Commissioners, what recent assessment the Church of England has made of the adequacy of the support offered by dioceses to a parish in an interregnum.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Church Commissioners</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>4</Number>
        <UIN>902966</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>SUBSTANTIVE</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
        <Status>ToBeAsked</Status>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Martin Vickers</Member>
        <Constituency>Cleethorpes</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the hon. Member for South West Bedfordshire, representing the Church Commissioners, what recent assessment the Church of England has made of the impact of church schools on the level of educational attainment in (a) Cleethorpes constituency and (b) England.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Church Commissioners</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>5</Number>
        <UIN>902967</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>SUBSTANTIVE</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
        <Status>ToBeAsked</Status>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Danny Kruger</Member>
        <Constituency>Devizes</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the hon. Member for South West Bedfordshire, representing the Church Commissioners, what steps the Church of England is taking to provide funding to parish churches.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Church Commissioners</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>6</Number>
        <UIN>902968</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>SUBSTANTIVE</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
        <Status>ToBeAsked</Status>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>George Galloway</Member>
        <Constituency>Rochdale</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the hon. Member for Luton South, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, if she will hold discussions with the Electoral Commission on the rules on the registration of descriptions of political parties.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>7</Number>
        <UIN>902969</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest>I am Leader of the Workers Party of Britain, a party affected by these seeming double standards.</DeclaredInterest>
        <Type>SUBSTANTIVE</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
        <Status>ToBeAsked</Status>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Michael Fabricant</Member>
        <Constituency>Lichfield</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the hon. Member for South West Bedfordshire, representing the Church Commissioners, what support is available to churches and cathedrals facing the risk of theft of (a) fabric and (b) contents from their buildings.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Church Commissioners</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>8</Number>
        <UIN>902970</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>SUBSTANTIVE</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
        <Status>ToBeAsked</Status>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Chi Onwurah</Member>
        <Constituency>Newcastle upon Tyne Central</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the hon. Member for Broxbourne, representing the House of Commons Commission, what recent progress the Commission has made on using digital tools to support the work of hon. Members.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>House of Commons Commission</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>9</Number>
        <UIN>902971</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>SUBSTANTIVE</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
        <Status>ToBeAsked</Status>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Sir Desmond Swayne</Member>
        <Constituency>New Forest West</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the hon. Member for South West Bedfordshire, representing the Church Commissioners, what steps the Church of England is taking to increase the number of Academy schools it sponsors.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Church Commissioners</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>10</Number>
        <UIN>902972</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>SUBSTANTIVE</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
        <Status>ToBeAsked</Status>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Rachael Maskell</Member>
        <Constituency>York Central</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the hon. Member for South West Bedfordshire, representing the Church Commissioners, what steps the Church of England is taking to provide support for people in Gaza.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Church Commissioners</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>11</Number>
        <UIN>902973</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>SUBSTANTIVE</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
        <Status>ToBeAsked</Status>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Deidre Brock</Member>
        <Constituency>Edinburgh North and Leith</Constituency>
        <Text>To ask the hon. Member for Luton South, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, whether the Committee has had recent discussions with the Electoral Commission on the potential impact of disinformation on the integrity of elections.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>12</Number>
        <UIN>902974</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>SUBSTANTIVE</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
        <Status>ToBeAsked</Status>
      </Question>
    </Questions>
    <QuestionType>Substantive Oral</QuestionType>
    <ContainsWithdrawnQuestions>false</ContainsWithdrawnQuestions>
  </QuestionBlock>
  <QuestionBlock>
    <Date>2024-05-23</Date>
    <Time>9:30 am</Time>
    <Description>Oral Questions to the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport</Description>
    <Questions>
      <Question>
        <Member>Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi</Member>
        <Constituency>Slough</Constituency>
        <Text>What steps her Department is taking to support local journalism.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Culture, Media and Sport</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>1</Number>
        <UIN>902975</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>SUBSTANTIVE</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
        <Status>ToBeAsked</Status>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Matt Hancock</Member>
        <Constituency>West Suffolk</Constituency>
        <Text>What steps her Department is taking to support the horse racing industry.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Culture, Media and Sport</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>2</Number>
        <UIN>902976</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest>Relevant interests are found in the Member's Register </DeclaredInterest>
        <Type>SUBSTANTIVE</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
        <Status>ToBeAsked</Status>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Paul Howell</Member>
        <Constituency>Sedgefield</Constituency>
        <Text>What assessment she has made of the impact of the Youth Investment Fund on opportunities for young people.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Culture, Media and Sport</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>3</Number>
        <UIN>902977</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>SUBSTANTIVE</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
        <Status>ToBeAsked</Status>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Wendy Morton</Member>
        <Constituency>Aldridge-Brownhills</Constituency>
        <Text>What steps she is taking to support the participation of women and girls in sport. </Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Culture, Media and Sport</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>4</Number>
        <UIN>902978</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>SUBSTANTIVE</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
        <Status>ToBeAsked</Status>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Holly Lynch</Member>
        <Constituency>Halifax</Constituency>
        <Text>What steps her Department is taking to protect and repurpose heritage buildings.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Culture, Media and Sport</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>5</Number>
        <UIN>902979</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>SUBSTANTIVE</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
        <Status>ToBeAsked</Status>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Rachel Maclean</Member>
        <Constituency>Redditch</Constituency>
        <Text>What assessment she has made of the impact of the Swimming Pool Support Fund on local pools and leisure facilities. </Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Culture, Media and Sport</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>6</Number>
        <UIN>902980</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>SUBSTANTIVE</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
        <Status>ToBeAsked</Status>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Greg Smith</Member>
        <Constituency>Buckingham</Constituency>
        <Text>What steps she is taking to support the participation of women and girls in sport. </Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Culture, Media and Sport</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>7</Number>
        <UIN>902981</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>SUBSTANTIVE</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
        <Status>ToBeAsked</Status>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Mr Philip Hollobone</Member>
        <Constituency>Kettering</Constituency>
        <Text>If her Department will take steps to support snooker clubs.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Culture, Media and Sport</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>8</Number>
        <UIN>902982</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>SUBSTANTIVE</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
        <Status>ToBeAsked</Status>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Adam Afriyie</Member>
        <Constituency>Windsor</Constituency>
        <Text>What recent discussions she has had with Cabinet colleagues on tackling strategic lawsuits against public participation.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Culture, Media and Sport</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>9</Number>
        <UIN>902983</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>SUBSTANTIVE</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
        <Status>ToBeAsked</Status>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Owen Thompson</Member>
        <Constituency>Midlothian</Constituency>
        <Text>What recent progress her Department has made on its review of the Gambling Act 2005.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Culture, Media and Sport</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>10</Number>
        <UIN>902984</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>SUBSTANTIVE</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
        <Status>ToBeAsked</Status>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Ruth Edwards</Member>
        <Constituency>Rushcliffe</Constituency>
        <Text>What recent assessment she has made of the impact of the Multi-Sport Grassroots Facilities Programme on access to sport for young people.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Culture, Media and Sport</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>11</Number>
        <UIN>902985</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>SUBSTANTIVE</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
        <Status>ToBeAsked</Status>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Sarah Dyke</Member>
        <Constituency>Somerton and Frome</Constituency>
        <Text>If she will have discussions with the Secretary of State for Levelling Up, Housing and Communities on the different level of usage of public parks for recreational sports by girls and boys.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Culture, Media and Sport</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>12</Number>
        <UIN>902986</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>SUBSTANTIVE</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
        <Status>ToBeAsked</Status>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Jonathan Edwards</Member>
        <Constituency>Carmarthen East and Dinefwr</Constituency>
        <Text>Whether she has had recent discussions with the Welsh Government and the independent television production sector on the appointment of a new Chair for S4C.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Culture, Media and Sport</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>13</Number>
        <UIN>902987</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>SUBSTANTIVE</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
        <Status>ToBeAsked</Status>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Rob Butler</Member>
        <Constituency>Aylesbury</Constituency>
        <Text>What assessment she has made of the impact of the Swimming Pool Support Fund on local pools and leisure facilities. </Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Culture, Media and Sport</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>14</Number>
        <UIN>902988</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>SUBSTANTIVE</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
        <Status>ToBeAsked</Status>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Chris Elmore</Member>
        <Constituency>Ogmore</Constituency>
        <Text>What recent assessment she has made of the impact of the UK's departure from the EU on the music industry.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Culture, Media and Sport</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>15</Number>
        <UIN>902989</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>SUBSTANTIVE</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
        <Status>ToBeAsked</Status>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Deidre Brock</Member>
        <Constituency>Edinburgh North and Leith</Constituency>
        <Text>What recent discussions she has had with Ofcom on enforcement of the Broadcasting Code.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Culture, Media and Sport</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>16</Number>
        <UIN>902990</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>SUBSTANTIVE</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
        <Status>ToBeAsked</Status>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Mr Alistair Carmichael</Member>
        <Constituency>Orkney and Shetland</Constituency>
        <Text>If she will make an assessment of the effectiveness of Government support for local media.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Culture, Media and Sport</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>17</Number>
        <UIN>902991</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>SUBSTANTIVE</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
        <Status>ToBeAsked</Status>
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Member>Lee Anderson</Member>
        <Constituency>Ashfield</Constituency>
        <Text>Whether she has had discussions with the BBC Board on its plans to sell adverts on audio content streamed on commercial platforms.</Text>
        <AnsweringBody>Department for Culture, Media and Sport</AnsweringBody>
        <Number>18</Number>
        <UIN>902992</UIN>
        <DeclaredInterest />
        <Type>SUBSTANTIVE</Type>
        <IsTransfer>false</IsTransfer>
        <Status>ToBeAsked</Status>
      </Question>
    </Questions>
    <QuestionType>Substantive Oral</QuestionType>
    <ContainsWithdrawnQuestions>false</ContainsWithdrawnQuestions>
  </QuestionBlock>
</ArrayOfQuestionBlock>