<root><OPHeading1>Announcements</OPHeading1>
<OPHeading2>Forthcoming End of Day Adjournment Debates</OPHeading2>
<MotionText><from_cdata>Applications for 30-minute end of day adjournment debates should be made to the Table Office by 7.00pm or rise of the House, whichever is the earlier, on the Wednesdays listed below. Members can submit their application via MemberHub, from their own email account or in hard copy. Application forms are available on the Table Office page on ParliNet. The ballot takes place on the day following the deadline. Members who are successful will be contacted by the Speaker&#8217;s Office.
<strong/></from_cdata></MotionText>
<DebateTimingRubric>Tuesday 23 to Monday 29 January (deadline Wednesday 17 January 7.00pm or the rise of the House, whichever is earlier)</DebateTimingRubric>
<DebateTimingRubric>Tuesday 30 January to Monday 5 February (deadline Wednesday 24 January 7.00pm or the rise of the House, whichever is earlier)</DebateTimingRubric>
<DebateTimingRubric>Tuesday 6 to Thursday 8 February (deadline Wednesday 31 January 7.00pm or the rise of the House, whichever is earlier)</DebateTimingRubric>
<OPHeading2>Forthcoming Westminster Hall Debates</OPHeading2>
<MotionText><from_cdata>The rota for answering Departments is listed below. Applications for 90, 60 and 30-minute debates should be made to the Table Office by 10.00pm or the rise of the House, whichever is the earlier, on the Mondays listed below. Members can submit their application via MemberHub, from their own email account or in hard copy. Application forms are available on the Table Office page on ParliNet. The ballot takes place on the day following the deadline. Members who are successful will be contacted by the Speaker&#8217;s Office.</from_cdata></MotionText>
<DebateTimingRubric>Tuesday 30 and Wednesday 31 January (deadline Monday 22 January 10.00pm or the rise of the House, whichever is earlier)</DebateTimingRubric>
<MotionText><from_cdata><span style="color: #333333; font-family: 'helvetica neue', Helvetica, Arial, sans-serif; font-size: 14px;">The following Departments will answer: </span>
<p style="margin: 0cm;"></p>
<p style="margin: 0cm;"><span class="ui-provider ed cjs bvj cjt cju cjv cjw cjx cjy cjz cka ckb ckc ckd ckf ckg ckh cki ckj ckk ckl ckm ckn cko ckp ckq ckr cks ckt cku ckv ckw ckx cky ckz">Business and Trade; Culture, Media and Sport; Defence; Health and Social Care; Justice; Levelling Up, Housing and Communities; Scotland; Transport; Treasury; Women and Equalities; Work and Pensions</span></p></from_cdata></MotionText>
<DebateTimingRubric>Tuesday 6 and Wednesday 7 February (deadline Monday 29 January 10.00pm or the rise of the House, whichever is earlier)</DebateTimingRubric>
<MotionText><from_cdata><span style="color: #333333; font-family: 'helvetica neue', Helvetica, Arial, sans-serif; font-size: 14px;">The following Departments will answer: </span>
<p style="margin: 0cm;"></p>
<p style="margin: 0cm;"><span class="ui-provider ed cjs bvj cjt cju cjv cjw cjx cjy cjz cka ckb ckc ckd ckf ckg ckh cki ckj ckk ckl ckm ckn cko ckp ckq ckr cks ckt cku ckv ckw ckx cky ckz">Attorney General; Cabinet Office; Education; Energy Security and Net Zero; Environment, Food and Rural Affairs; Foreign, Commonwealth and Development; Home Office; Northern Ireland; Science, Innovation and Technology; Wales</span></p></from_cdata></MotionText>
<OPHeading2>Election of the Chair of the Defence Committee</OPHeading2>
<DebateTimingRubric>Ballot</DebateTimingRubric>
<MotionText><from_cdata>The ballot will take place between 11.00am and 2.30pm today in the Aye division lobby.
As soon as practicable after the votes have been counted the Speaker will announce to the House the results of the ballot.</from_cdata></MotionText>
<DebateTimingRubric>Final list of Members nominated for election as Chair of the Defence Committee</DebateTimingRubric>
<MotionText><from_cdata>Candidate: Rehman Chishti
Nominated by (own party): James Morris, Jonathan Gullis, Kelly Tolhurst, Royston Smith, Ian Levy, Giles Watling, Dr Matthew Offord, Henry Smith, Tom Hunt, Mark Logan, Paul Bristow, Kwasi Kwarteng, Daniel Kawczynski, Jack Brereton, Martin Vickers
Nominated by (other parties or no party): Debbie Abrahams, Mr Khalid Mahmood, Sammy Wilson, Ms Anum Qaisar, Yasmin Qureshi
Relevant interests declared: British Army Reservist (2020&#8211;2022) as per Register of Members&#8217; Financial Interests. I have been asked to speak at a conference in Germany organised in partnership by RFI (Religious Freedom Institute) USA. I previously served as their Senior Fellow on International Religious Freedom. RFI are co-hosting the conference with USA European Command.  The topic is international religious freedom and the work of military chaplains.  Travel and accommodation will be covered and there is an honorarium for the speaking at the conference. I have agreed in principle to speak, but it will be subject to election and parliamentary commitments.
Candidate: Jeremy Quin
Nominated by (own party): Harriett Baldwin, Sir Robert Goodwill, Dr Th&#233;r&#232;se Coffey, Mr Ben Wallace, Mr Robin Walker, Angela Richardson, Dame Karen Bradley, Greg Clark, Philip Dunne, Simon Jupp, Nickie Aiken, Steve Brine, Iain Stewart, Tim Loughton, Mrs Heather Wheeler
Nominated by (other parties or no party): John Spellar, Valerie Vaz, Dave Doogan, Mr Kevan Jones, Sir Stephen Timms
Relevant interests declared: I served as Minister of State in the Ministry of Defence from February 2020 to September 2022.  I am Honorary President of the Air Cadet Squadron in my Horsham constituency.  Defence manufacturers Thales and Boeing are employers in a neighbouring constituency and Chess Dynamics, a subsidiary of defence manufacturer Cohort PLC, is based in Horsham.</from_cdata></MotionText></root>